Chapter 997 – Dare

Bet Yan Littlemoon?

All the Phoenix Cry Palace disciples felt their jaws drop as they heard Sun Cyprestar say this. They were all left staring dumbfounded. Just who was Yan Littlemoon? She was someone with a perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline. She was a proud daughter of heaven that stood out amongst all proud daughters of heaven!

If one could make love to Yan Littlemoon, then that truly would be a wonderful event!

Without discussing Yan Littlemoon’s top class appearance and figure, just her perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline would be a massive lucky chance to the man who took her primordial yin!

In the Ancient Phoenix Clan, if a man and woman had sex then their bloodlines would supplement each other. When Lin Ming was at Divine Phoenix Island, this was also the case. Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun were both Saintesses of Divine Phoenix Island, and they possessed pure vermillion bird and blue luan bloodlines. The person who took their primordial yin could strengthen their own bloodlines. However, Lin Ming was an exception at the time. With his 100 drops of Ancient Phoenix blood, his bloodline was far purer and richer than Mu Qianyu’s vermillion bird bloodline by countless times.

When Lin Ming and Mu Qianyu made love, she had actually been the one to pick up all the advantages from his body.

When a male and female had sex, the one with the thinner bloodline would obtain advantages from the one with the richer bloodline. If Lin Ming had the chance to have sex with someone with a perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline, the immense advantages could be imagined!

In particular the virginity of a woman. If one could obtain a woman’s primordial yin energy, the advantages would be even greater!

Lin Ming was indeed talented, but the bloodline within his body was far too pale. This was because he had never been a true legitimate Ancient Phoenix Clan clansman from the start; he was far from being able to compare with Huo Yanguang, let alone someone like Yan Littlemoon. If he could make love with Yan Littlemoon then the benefits couldn’t be outweighed by even several drops of phoenix heart blood!

It was exactly because of this reason that the Phoenix Cry Palace disciples were stirred up. They began to shout out loud.

“Bet Yan Littlemoon? Elder Sun is far too ruthless, Yan Littlemoon is a fairy-like figure, like an immortal celestial of heaven. When she grows in the future there will be countless handsome heroic young elites who will chase her hand for marriage. These people will likely include the future family head successors for the three great family clans, or even someone like the son of the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Patriarch. Their status surpasses Senior-apprentice Brother White Daohong by countless times, to a point that we cannot imagine. Lin Ming is talented, but that is only in relation to our Phoenix Cry Palace. If he is compared to geniuses like them, he is far from being qualified. If Yan Littlemoon marries Lin Ming, that is something beyond his status!”

“That’s right. Lin Ming is a martial artist who ascended from the lower realms. In terms of background he is no better than a common mortal disciple of Phoenix Cry Palace or Charming Phoenix Palace. His bloodline density is extremely limited. If he dual cultivates with Yan Littlemoon, then she will be the one to suffer a loss. If they have children in the future, their bloodline will be lacking too. How could her family possibly agree to this?”

“Yan Littlemoon will suffer a loss but that punk Lin Ming’s gains will be far too great and for far too little! Those benefits, it makes one crazy just thinking about them!”

The disciples of Phoenix Cry Palace were drooling just talking about it. Which one of the male disciples didn’t wish to marry such a magnificent woman like Yan Littlemoon? If they had to exchange 20,000 years of their life in exchange for a single night with her, at least 90% of the male disciples might be willing to do that.

However, someone poured water over everyone’s parade. “You make it sound as if Yan Littlemoon is already married to Lin Ming. For Lin Ming to win against Yan Littlemoon in the Ancient Phoenix smelting trial, that is just far too difficult!”

“Yeah, it does seem impossible… in the entire junior generation of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, there are only a few people with perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodlines. It won’t be easy to win.”

Sun Cyprestar’s words had caused a heated discussion throughout the disciples of Phoenix Cry Palace. Men were always enthusiastic to discuss beautiful women to begin with. Moreover, this was a topic that Elder Sun had raised himself. Even if they couldn’t obtain Yan Littlemoon, they could still drool over their imaginations.

Sun Cyprestar normally managed his disciples in a strict and severe manner. But today, as he saw the disciples of Phoenix Cry Palace heatedly discussing Yan Littlemoon, not only did he not admonish them, but he even smiled. After seeing Chu Redcloud and suffering repeated losses to her, he had finally been able to retaliate. Seeing Chu Redcloud’s flustered expression really caused his thoughts to flow much more smoothly.

“What about it Fairy Chu? Wasn’t victory already in your hands? Weren’t you sure that Yan Littlemoon could win? Didn’t you say that someone who agrees to a bet must accept their losses? Since you’re so confident, you might as well agree as you’re winning anyway.”

“Hohoho!” Chu Redcloud gingerly laughed. She shook her head, saying, “Vice Hall Master Sun doesn’t need to try and shock me. This child Littlemoon is not my daughter and I cannot take responsibility for her. Lin Ming is still a handsome and talented young man. Although he is slightly inferior in the aspect of bloodlines and Laws, those can be increased by paying a steep enough price. Unfortunately, only my big brother can take responsibility for Littlemoon’s marriage matters. However, what I can guarantee is that if Lin Ming truly does defeat Littlemoon, then I shall serve as a matchmaker and raise the issue with my big brother. As for whether or not he agrees, I can make no guarantees!”

Chu Redcloud impishly smiled. Sun Cyprestar was not satisfied with this reply. He said, “Chu Redcloud, is everything you say always a bunch of nonsense? When Lin Ming defeats Yan Littlemoon and then your big brother does not agree, then what? Is that interesting at all?”

“Elder Sun, I already said I cannot take responsibility for this matter. If Apprentice Nephew Lin has a liking for a little girl from my Chu Family, then I can take responsibility for that. However, she is only 14 years old so you’ll have to wait several more years for her.”

Chu Redcloud laughed. But at this time, a red beam of light shot out from deep within the Hells of Flame at an extremely quick speed. It was Yan Littlemoon, who had returned from the third level of the Hells of Flame.

Yan Littlemoon was very popular in Charming Phoenix Palace. When Sun Cyprestar had stirred up Chu Redcloud with his suggestions just now, Yan Littlemoon’s close confidant had quietly used a special sound transmitting talisman to send a message to Yan Littlemoon.

As soon as Yan Littlemoon heard the message, she became incensed with anger. She didn’t bother impacting into the third level and returned at full speed instead.

“Aunty, you are betting my marriage? You make a bet and you want me as part of the stakes now? Did this old man say that?” Yan Littlemoon glared at Sun Cyprestar, her small chest heaving up and down in rage. Any girl would be angry after hearing that they were made into some betting stake. Moreover, Yan Littlemoon was extremely arrogant to begin with. In these past years, there had been so many handsome heroic young elites chasing after her that she couldn’t lose them even if she tried, and yet today someone was turning her into a betting stake? How ridiculous! How preposterous! How dare they!

But unfortunately, Yan Littlemoon’s angry expression was not fierce or vicious at all. Instead, she appeared quite lovable and cute. As the male disciples of Phoenix Cry Palace looked at the angry Yan Littlemoon, they revealed happy expressions in their eyes.

Yan Littlemoon was in her twenties but her outer appearance was that of a 16 year old girl. Really, her angry expression was simply too adorable.

“What a cute and lovable girl. If Junior-apprentice Brother Lin can marry Yan Littlemoon, that will be a good fortune he can enjoy for several lifetimes.”

“Indeed. She’s a wild and playful girl, but she’s so beautiful even when she’s angry. If I could marry her I’d even be willing to give up 10,000 years of my life.”

The comments from the Phoenix Cry Palace disciples only added fuel to the fire.

“You people!!” Yan Littlemoon was furious. These people simply didn’t take her anger seriously. She felt as if she was being disregarded by them.

Sun Cyprestar smiled. He stroked his beard and said, “Yes, I am the old man who suggested this. How about it, do you dare to agree to this bet?”

“Humph, if you want to defeat me then keep on dreaming! Yan Littlemoon’s lips curved up in a charming smiled. At this time, she was fully displaying all of the arrogance and disdain in her heart.

As Chu Redcloud saw this, she felt her heart gripped. She said with a sound transmission, “Littlemoon, don’t be tricked. This old man is only trying to provoke you. You absolutely must not be impulsive and agree.”

Chapter 1005 – Lin Ming’s Choice

“We have already chosen, Lord Messenger.” Xiao Whitesnow said. He was satisfied with his own choice of totem stone. Although it was a bit regrettable that it couldn’t compare with the 100 Foot Royal Skyseal, it did match up with his Concepts more. It could be considered passable.

“Mm. Then speak out what you have chosen. Once you have made your choice you cannot change it, so think well over your decision.” The black-robed messenger said without expression.

“Reporting to Lord Messenger, this disciple has chosen the 90 Foot Burning Heaven Tablet!” Xiao Whitesnow spoke out loud. The 90 Foot Burning Heaven Tablet was 90 feet high, so it seemed only 10 feet shorter than the 100 Foot Royal Skyseal. But, the truth was that the 90 Foot Burning Heaven Tablet was shaped like a rectangle and it was only 20 feet wide. Thus, it was less than a fifth of the size of the 100 Foot Royal Skyseal.

Even so, the 90 Foot Burning Heaven Tablet originated from the ninth Patriarch of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. This person was called Burning Heaven, and he had an extremely grand and famous history within the Ancient Phoenix Clan. When Lin Ming had gone to Timeworn Phoenix City, the Burning Heaven Totem Stone he meditated over also came from this person. At that time, Lin Ming didn’t possess the ability to perceive the chaos stones, thus he stepped back and requested the next best totem stone – the Burning Heaven Totem Stone.

The 90 Foot Burning Heaven Tablet and the Burning Heaven Totem Stone were both works created by Patriarch Burning Heaven. But, the Burning Heaven Totem Stone in Timeworn Phoenix City only recorded the most preliminary Concepts of the Fire Laws. As for the 90 Foot Burning Heaven Totem Stone, that was etched with the first eight level Concepts of the Fire Laws. The mysteries inherent within were far superior. Of course, this was to be expected. The 90 Foot Burning Heaven Tablet was 1800 times larger than Timeworn Phoenix City’s Burning Heaven Totem Stone.

“Alright. The 90 Foot Burning Heaven Tablet.” The black-robed messenger recorded Xiao Whitesnow’s choice on a jade slip and then turned to Lin Ming. “Lin Ming, what choice have you made?”

As the black-robed messenger asked this question, everyone’s eyes turned to Lin Ming. They wanted to hear just what he chose. In their opinion, Lin Ming and Xiao Whitesnow had similar talent, but Lin Ming was more oriented towards actual combat, and Xiao Whitesnow was oriented towards comprehension of Laws. Originally, with Yan Littlemoon here, no one would have cared about Lin Ming so much. But now that Chu Redcloud and Sun Cyprestar had made a bet, that bet had pushed Lin Ming to the crest of the waves.

“Lin Ming is in a bind. The best 100 Foot Royal Skyseal was taken by Yan Littlemoon, anything he chooses will just be leftovers.”

“Yah, but that’s just how things are. Who let Yan Littlemoon have the perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline? I think that Lin Ming will choose the Extreme Dao Heaven Tablet. That stone tablet is 120 feet high and 15 feet wide; it’s similar to the 90 Foot Burning Heaven Tablet. Since it comes from Senior Xiao Daoji, it is also an extremely high quality work!”

“I think so too.”

Several disciples discussed amongst themselves. At this time, Lin Ming finally opened his mouth to speak. However, he didn’t state his choice directly. He first asked the black-robed messenger, “Lord Messenger, I have a question. If I choose those stone tablets that no one else has chosen, can I choose more than one?”

“Mm?”

Lin Ming’s suddenly question left all the martial artists present dumbfounded. What was the meaning of this? Lin Ming wanted to choose totem stones that no one else had chosen?

Fire Spirit Star’s Totem Tower had an incomparably rich collection of totem stones. There were far more totem stones than disciples that had come, this was without doubt. But, those totem stones that no one chose did not originate from Patriarchs of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, but from the hands of Elders.

A true Ancient Phoenix Clan Elder was on the same level as a branch palace’s Palace Master. It was more accurate to say that there were far more Elders than there were Palace Masters. This was because the Ancient Phoenix Clan Headquarters had a great number of Merit Elders, Disciplinary Elders, Highest Elders, and all sorts of other Elders. When combined with the 72 Palace Masters, there were well over a hundred Elders.

One could look at the number to see what the difference in strength was between a Patriarch and an Elder. The Ancient Phoenix Clan only had a single Patriarch, but there were over a hundred Elders!

The Ancient Phoenix Clan had existed for countless tens of thousands of years. When all past and present Elders were added together, they had to be counted with 10,000 as the base unit!

Of these Elders, many would leave behind totem stones before they died. These totem stones certainly couldn’t compare with one made by the Patriarch. Thus, most of them were used by martial artists of the lower realms, and only the highest quality ones would be kept in the Divine Realm Totem Towers.

Of course, the so-called highest quality totem stones still couldn’t compete with those like the 90 Foot Burning Heaven Totem Stone.

So when Lin Ming suddenly asked this question, the black-robed messenger and the other disciples had all been extremely shocked.

“What’s Lin Ming trying to do? Is he going to wait until all the other disciples have chosen before he chooses again?”

“How could that be? Do you think that he is an idiot? Even if 100 of those poor quality totem stones are combined, it still wouldn’t match up to a single top quality totem stone!”

Lin Ming’s words left all the disciples scratching their heads. Even Yan Littlemoon was puzzled as she stared at Lin Ming. “What sort of tricks is this fellow trying to play?”

The black-robed messenger was a bit startled as he looked at Lin Ming. Then he gently smiled and said with some interest, “If you choose the totem stones that no one else has chosen, then I will allow you to choose multiple!”

“Great! Thank you Lord Messenger for the help. This disciple has chosen four totem stones. They are respectively: Atlas World’s chaos stone number one, the Yin Yang Chaos Stone! Atlas World’s  chaos stone number two, the Endless Years Chaos Stone! Atlas World’s chaos stone number three, the Universe Space Chaos Stone! Atlas World’s number chaos stone four, the Five Elements Chaos Stone!”

Lin Ming’s clear voice spread throughout the entire audience. For a time, a pall of stunned silence fell over the entire crowd. All of the disciples were stunned silent. Lin Ming had listed four stone tablets in a single breath, and all of them were chaos stones!

The chaos stones had always been mostly ignored in the Ancient Phoenix smelting trial, and there were rarely any trial challengers who chose them. But, there was still the occasional person, and those people tended to be Divine Transformation realm powerhouses on the level of White Daohong and Lu Xiaoyun. They had already meditated on the other totem stones many times, and it was difficult to make further breakthroughs. Only then would they choose a chaos stone in the hopes they would obtain some inspirations and make a breakthrough. But now, a junior disciple had actually chosen the chaos stones, and moreover, he had also chosen four. This had simply never happened before.

“Just what is Lin Ming thinking? He actually chose four chaos stones, and listening to their names, Yin Yang Chaos Stone, Universe Space Chaos Stone, Endless Years Chaos Stone, and Five Elements Chaos Stone, only that last Five Elements Chaos Stone has anything to do with the Fire Laws. Is he planning on perceiving the Fire Laws through the Five Elements Chaos Stone?”

This was what all the martial artists present were thinking. Even White Daohong and Lu Xiaoyun weren’t too sure just what was happening. Yan Littlemoon’s eyes were wide like plates; she didn’t think Lin Ming would make this choice.

As for Xiao Whitesnow, who had entered Totem Tower with Lin Ming, he was looking at Lin Ming with a floored expression, as if he were trying to say, “Are you kidding me here?” However, even though he opened his mouth, no words came out. He had been left speechless. He had already mentioned this point to Lin Ming, and since this was the choice Lin Ming had made, he naturally couldn’t say anything else.

Those that walked down the road of martial arts most respected and admired characters with great ambition and drive. The Laws within the chaos stones were undefined and mysterious, without any specific content. To make an analogy, the totem stones left behind by all the previous Patriarchs of the Ancient Phoenix Clan could be considered extremely rare and detailed martial arts manuscripts. But, the chaos stones represented a general outline of every single martial arts manuscript that existed in the world. If one didn’t even learn martial arts but wanted to see the general outline of everything, this sort of approach even had Sun Cyprestar frowning, and Sun Cyprestar was the one here with the most confidence in Lin Ming. He simply didn’t understand Lin Ming’s reasoning behind all this.

“Lin Ming, do you know what you are doing? Those chaos stones are normally for Divine Lord realm powerhouses to meditate on, and that is only occasionally too. We cultivate the Fire Laws, and the Laws within the chaos stones are simply too general and mysterious. Even if you meditate on them for a long time, you still won’t be able to learn much from them; you will only be able to use them as a reference point. You are a first time rookie disciple so you have the advantage within Totem Tower. Didn’t you notice that even White Daohong and Lu Xiaoyun have lower priority of choice than you? This is your most precious opportunity. If you miss this chance then the next time you come here you won’t be a rookie disciple anymore, and it will be more difficult to choose a totem stone that you like. I know that you don’t feel too well about not being able to choose the 100 Foot Royal Skyseal, but the Extreme Dao heaven Tablet is also a very good choice. Many disciples who want to meditate on that totem stone don’t ever have the chance to do so.”

Sun Cyprestar sent Lin Ming a true essence sound transmission, sincerely worried for him.

Lin Ming faintly smiled and responded with a sound transmission, “I thank Senior Sun for the advice, but since I have made my choice I naturally have confidence in myself.”

“Well… okay.” Sun Cyprestar thought of saying something else but shook his head. Thinking about it, up until now, everything Lin Ming did or said had a clear goal behind it. In the past when no one believed in him, he had still emerged victorious. Perhaps he also had a special reason this time too?

As Sun Cyprestar thought this, he no longer stopped Lin Ming. He only ordered him, “Put your best into it!”

“This disciples understands.”

In the square of Totem Tower, the black-robed messenger had waited for 20 breaths of time. He meaningfully gazed at Lin Ming and said, “Lin Ming, have you determined your choice? Once you’ve made it, you can no longer change it. Do not regret the decision you made!”

“This disciple has chosen.”

“Good, then I shall write them down!” The black-robed messenger flourished a brush and drew a seal mark on a jade slip. “The third group of people to enter the Totem Tower – White Daohong and Lu Xiaoyun!”

Amongst talents of the same level, junior disciples went first. The black-robed messenger had used this method to tacitly signify that Lin Ming and Xiao Whitesnow were on the same level as White Daohong and Lu Xiaoyun. But, Yan Littlemoon was yet another level higher than them.

White Daohong and Lu Xiaoyun quickly flew into Totem Tower and made their choices.

After them was Huo Yanguang. Huo Yanguang was the only Ninefall Life Destruction martial artist of Phoenix Cry Palace, moreover he was also a four layered heavens Ninefall martial artist. In Phoenix City Palace, he was second only to Lin Ming within the group of junior disciples. All other geniuses that were superior to Huo Yanguang were no longer junior disciples.

After Huo Yanguang, the Ninefall Divine Transformation senior disciples went to choose.

Everyone slowly filtered in and out. It took a full day and night for the disciples of the three branch palaces to complete their choices.

“Very well. All disciples have finished their choices. From this point on, you may freely cultivate. Whether it is the 18 Hells of Flame or the Totem Tower, you may do as you wish. Two years from now we shall test your final results. This smelting trial is divided into two aspects. One is the 18 Hells of Flame that tests your comprehension of Laws and Concepts and the other is the Illusionary God Combat Array that tests your actual combat prowess! Those with extraordinary trial results may obtain rewards passed down from the Ancient Phoenix Clan Headquarters! Fire Elementals, top grade pills, top grade saint artifacts, phoenix heart blood, phoenix plume blood, and even phoenix coronet blood and transcendent saint artifacts! As long as you have the ability, everything is yours for the taking!

“Now, you are all dismissed! Cultivate as you will!”

Chapter 1018 – Fusing the Three Concepts

“What? Law phenomenon?” Duke Golden Sword was startled as he heard Monarch Sweetyfox speak. “What sort of phenomenon?”

“I have no idea. I’ve never seen it before!” Monarch Sweetyfox shook her head.

There were all sorts of phenomena that a martial artist could produce, and they were separated into many different categories. Among them were some directly related to combat, and some related to Laws.

Martial artists had different bloodlines, talent, good fortunes, bad fortunes, destiny, physique, perception of Laws, cultivation methods, and thousands upon thousands of other variables that were always changing. Thus, there were countless different phenomena that could appear within a martial artist, so it wasn’t strange for Monarch Sweetyfox to encounter one she hadn’t experienced before.

The Blue Lotus Domain and Lotus Blooming Step by Step could be considered types of phenomenon. The definition of a phenomenon was extremely broad, and even vague.

Back on the Sky Spill Continent when Lin Ming fought with Situ Yaoyue, she had the Extreme Violet Dantian, thus she could form the Extreme Violet Domain. That could also be considered a type of phenomenon. When he fought with Whitedemon, Whitedemon had been able to use his hydra bloodline to form a hydra phantom; this was also a type of phenomenon.

Phenomena were divided into varying quality, with those that were better and those that were weaker. A low level phenomenon wasn’t anything at all, but a high level phenomenon like Lotus Blooming Step by Step was impressive enough to amaze others.

And above Lotus Blooming Step by Step there were even more extraordinary phenomena. For instance, some phenomena were directly involved with a martial artist’s inner world. There were some Divine Lord realm powerhouses that had a phenomenon where their inner world was 10 times greater and 10 times tougher than others’. And, the source of a Divine Lord powerhouse’s strength was the heaven and earth origin energy condensed within their inner world, as well as the worship of those existences within. If there was a 10 times difference in inner worlds, then the disparity in combat strength could be imagined.

As for the phenomenon occurring within Lin Ming’s body, Monarch Sweetyfox had never seen or heard of it before. Even so, he was able to swallow the wild fire origin energy within the Hells of Flame’s sixth level, and he was even able to affect the surrounding revolution of Fire Laws around him. Thus, the rank of this phenomenon could be imagined!

“Just what adventures has Lin Ming gone through, what experiences and what fortuitous encounters has he had? The strength of his bloodline is clearly so light, yet why was he able to comprehend such a formidable phenomenon?”

Monarch Sweetyfox muttered to herself. “If it was said that Lin Ming has some amazingly powerful Law phenomenon within his body, then in addition to his marvelous perception, him obtaining such comprehensions is… no, I still can’t believe it. This can only be described as… a monstrous genius!”

As Monarch Sweetyfox was marveling over the Law phenomenon within Lin Ming’s body, all of the other martial artists present were gawking at Lin Ming’s gold battle spirit. In truth, they simply weren’t able to feel or make out the phenomenon of the Heretical God Sprout.

They knew that Lin Ming was a battle spirit genius. Moreover, he had used that as his foundation to perfectly open the Gate of Opening, gaining a perception that transcended common understanding.

But, no one imagined that Lin Ming would be able to push his battle spirit into the gold level at just the sixth stage of Life Destruction!

There was a fundamental difference between a gold battle spirit and a silver battle spirit.

A silver battle spirit could be used to strengthen a martial artist’s attacks, but it wasn’t a decisive and direct factor in a martial artist’s combat strength. Its greatest function in a fight between martial artists of similar boundaries was to strengthen weapons, making them sharper and more durable. If two martial artists fought and one of them had their weapon cut off, how could the battle continue?

However, if both sides had a high-grade saint artifact, then the effect of a battle spirit would be greatly weakened. This was because an ordinary Life Destruction or Divine Sea martial artist didn’t have the ability to destroy a high-grade saint artifact in a collision of weapons.

A silver battle spirit could be said to only be improving on perfection.

But a gold battle spirit was different. Once one achieved a gold battle spirit, the battle spirit would be so powerful that it could form a projection of their world of will and affect the real world.

From a silver battle spirit to a golden battle spirit, there was a great moat that separated them. And to cross over this moat, one needed to accumulate a massive amount of energy and experience. But Lin Ming had managed to form his gold battle spirit at the sixth stage of Life Destruction. How could this not cause the other young disciples who labeled themselves as geniuses to feel powerless and frustrated?

In the sixth level of the Hells of Flame, a sea of fire filled the world. Lin Ming was completely unaware of everything happening in Totem Tower’s square as he focused his concentration on fusing the Concepts.

Heretical God Sprout – !

Three flame leaves!

Three thunder leaves!

Of the three flame leaves, one was shaped like a heart, one was shaped like a stone tablet, and the last was shaped like a blue lotus.

Of the three thunder leaves, one was shaped like a sword, one was shaped like a golden tripod with a purple lion relief carved into it, and the last was shaped like a sovereign heavy sword.

The six leaves each represented a different Law. At this time, all of these leaves emitted a luminous light, continuously swallowing up all the surging fire origin within Lin Ming’s body! At this moment, the fire origin energy that was able to destroy all life was nothing but fertile land to the Heretical God Sprout!

The fire origin energy of the Hells of Flame’s sixth level was extremely fierce. But, underneath the dual suppression of the gold battle spirit’s world of will projection and the Heretical God Sprout, this formed a tentative balance within Lin Ming’s body. And the moment that this balance was reached, there was a change within the three levels of Concepts in Lin Ming’s body. In this blazing hot heat, there were all sorts of wondrous changes!

If one used their senses to investigate Lin Ming’s body, then they would discover that there were runes appearing on Lin Ming’s skeleton. These runes began to shine. They symbolized the first three levels of Concepts of the Fire Laws!

Originally, Lin Ming’s Laws were etched onto the Heretical God Sprout where they condensed into little totem runes. But now, Lin Ming had perceived the Laws and the Heretical God Sprout took a supporting role. Thus, the Law runes naturally inscribed themselves onto his body instead, where the formed mysterious marks on his bones.

These runes were carved onto Lin Ming’s bones and flesh. But now it seemed as if they were melting together, fusing as one.

The runes on his bones were of three different colors. The rune that symbolizing the Concept of Burning Heat was a vivid red, the rune that symbolized the Concept of Annihilation was black red, and the rune that symbolized the Concept of Creation was blue green. And now, these three runes were gathering on top of Lin Ming’s bones, fusing together as one. This was different from when Lin Ming created his martial skills in Thunderfire Annihilation and Penetrating Rainbow; they were only a combination of the Concepts of Thunder and Fire. But what was happening within his body, on his bones, was a true Law fusion!

“Lin Ming, he… he succeeded!?”

Monarch Sweetyfox sucked in a breath of cold air. From perceiving the Fire Laws, to impacting the sixth level of the Hells of Flame, and now where he began the preliminary fusion of three different levels of Concepts, everything that happened to Lin Ming today was simply a legend!

Because of Lin Ming’s abnormally fierce perception, the Heretical God Sprout’s ability to control the power of fire, and also the effect that the Primordius martial intent had on the Chaos Laws that allowed Lin Ming to perceive the chaos stones and see the evolution of matter and energy, and also the forming of the universe, all of these powerful advantages had resulted in this present miracle.

Of course, this was inseparable from Lin Ming’s solid foundation. If it weren’t for his impossibly deep true essence and his meridians that were tough to a ridiculous level that allowed him to withstand the violent and tyrannical power of fire, everything else would have been useless!

After less than half an incense stick of time, the three different kinds of runes that were etched into Lin Ming’s body melted and reformed, slowly fusing into one.

The three different levels of Concepts had finally completed their preliminary fusion.

Lin Ming knew that this was only the start. The Laws of the universe were infinitely mysterious. In the future as his strength increased, his comprehension of the source of matter and the source of the universe would become increasingly deep, and this fusion would become increasingly thorough!

Even so, among all the disciples of the three branch palaces present, including even the Divine Transformation realm disciples, in terms of just the first three Concepts of the Fire Laws, Lin Ming’s comprehension far surpassed all of theirs!

In the 18 Hells of Flame, the crazy and violent fire origin energy astral winds gushed into Lin Ming’s body. They were first weakened by the dual Concepts of Burning Heat and Annihilation, then transformed into pure energy by the Concept of Creation before being easily absorbed. With the strength of the three fused Concepts, the fiery astral winds were easily melted away. Lin Ming continued shooting down the 18 Hells of Flame with a near-unstoppable momentum!

Boom!

In that moment, an intense explosion blew up around Lin Ming. The thick fire origin energy around him was savagely thrown away by the shockwaves. Lin Ming’s body shot down like a meteor, continuing to rush towards the Hells of Flame’s seventh level!

The speed of sound…

Two times the speed of sound…

Three times the speed of sound…

All the way until 10 times the speed of sound!

Lin Ming’s speed once again increased to 10 times the speed of sound!

Bang bang bang!

Because Lin Ming’s speed was too quick and the dense fiery astral winds were crudely and rapidly separated by him, this caused rolling thunderclaps to fill the air, reverberating within the interior of Fire Spirit Star. Everyone standing on the ground could feel the earth beneath them tremble, as if an earthquake was happening!

Sixth level 2000 miles, sixth level 3000 miles, sixth level 4000 miles, the depth rapidly increased!

The three branch palace’s disciples, as well as the several Elders present, were completely dumbfounded, some of them panic-stricken. They didn’t know what sort of change had happened in Lin Ming’s body just now. All they saw was Lin Ming coming to a near standstill in the purgatory like flames of the sixth level. Then, his speed shot up and he began rushing towards the center of Fire Spirit star with unstoppable momentum!

Fire Spirit Star was a massive planet that gathered an infinite amount of wild and raging fire origin energy from all over. Although it was a planet, the truth was that the temperature and intensity within the core was no less than that of a small sun. But now, Lin Ming was passing through the sixth level with monstrous speed, as if he were flying through the skies of a windswept prairie!

“This…”

“This defies the heavens! This goes against heaven’s will!”

“Didn’t Lin Ming reach his limit? Why did he suddenly break out with such speed? Was he hiding his strength just now?” Many disciples didn’t know just what happened to Lin Ming.

“That’s impossible… Lin Ming should have completed a breakthrough just now. He is truly a monstrous genius… in the trial of the 18 Hells of Flame, everyone is giving their all to go as deep as they can go. They already thank the heavens and earth if they can display their best results. But now, Lin Ming actually used this time to make a breakthrough in such a dangerous situation… monster… he is a monster!”

The one who spoke was White Daohong. Towards this junior-apprentice brother of his, White Daohong had to admit complete defeat. After a few more years he would have to leave Phoenix Hall and become a Hall Protector. This would be his last Ancient Phoenix smelting trial. Even so, he had no regrets. He never imagined that during his last smelting trial he would be able to personally witness something that would be forever recorded in the annals of the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s history.

“Is he going to break through to the seventh level in a single attempt?”

Lu Xiaoyun sucked in a cold breath as she mumbled to herself. And behind Lu Xiaoyun was Yan Littlemoon.

Yan Littlemoon was pale and her lips were gently trembling. If there was someone present that had the strongest changes in emotions due to the miracles being created by Lin Ming, that would be Yan Littlemoon.

Today would be a day that would be eternally engraved into Yan Littlemoon’s mind. She would never be able to forget it!

Chapter 1019 – Hells of Flame’s Seventh Level, The Domain of God

Rumble rumble rumble!

With irresistible momentum, Lin Ming broke through to the sixth level 5000 miles distance!

The Ancient Phoenix Clan used every 5000 miles as a separate grade. The sixth level 5000 miles, even in the entire Ancient Phoenix Clan with the 72 branch palaces, three great families, and headquarters added in, was a target that was only met by a few individuals every several thousand years! It was an extremely rare occurrence!

And that was only at the end of the Ancient Phoenix smelting trial. To reach this goal halfway through the Ancient Phoenix smelting trial, that was more difficult than ascending to the heavens!

But now Lin Ming had broken through the sixth level 5000 mile distance without slowing down at all. He continued barreling towards the seventh level of the Hells of Flame!

As everyone saw this, they were shocked numb. Using a sixth stage Life Destruction cultivation to rush into the Hells of Flame’s seventh level, just what sort of wondrous feat was that!

The impossible standard that had been laid down by the Ancient Phoenix Clan was now actually soon to be met by Lin Ming!

After successfully reaching the seventh level of the Hells of Flame, no one dared to doubt Lin Ming any longer. It was likely that Lin Ming would continue onwards to complete the Thousand Slaughter within the Illusionary God Combat Array!

It had to be known that true combat was Lin Ming’s strong point, and his comprehension of Laws was his weak point.

If his weak point was still enough to reach the seventh level, then what about his strong point?

Perhaps this argument was no longer accurate. It could be said that Lin Ming no longer had a weakness.

If one had to insist, then maybe Lin Ming’s weak point could only be his cultivation speed. Lin Ming was 29 years old with a sixth stage Life Destruction cultivation. Compared to other top geniuses of a similar level throughout history, he was much older!

However, this wasn’t an absolute. A genius’ cultivation wasn’t necessarily better the faster it progressed. During the process of cultivation, if one desperately impacted towards the next realm they could certainly quickly rise in cultivation realms. But, their combat prowess might not be too amazing and their foundation could be unsteady.

During the cultivation process, if one was enlightened on all sorts of Laws and perceived many Concepts, such as Lin Ming, and also dual cultivated in body and energy, then it would be difficult to rise in cultivation realms rapidly.

But this wasn’t a problem. For someone like Lin Ming, once he stepped into Ninefall, the origin energy cloud he summoned would be titanic, and the baptism of Laws he would have to withstand would also be much greater. After undergoing this baptism of Laws and slowly verifying his comprehension, his future achievements would be unimaginable!

“Can Lin Ming really succeed in obtaining the drop of phoenix blood essence?”

Sun Cyprestar gripped his fists. He could feel his palms slick with sweat. From the depths of his heart, he hoped that Lin Ming could succeed in his endeavors and leave an endlessly glorious reputation within the tomes of history!

At this time, he had a sudden thought. He turned towards Charming Phoenix Palace’s direction and saw that Chu Redcloud’s face was wan as she floated in the air, her fingers gently shivering.

At the moment that Lin Ming had broken through the sixth level 5000 mile distance at 10 times the speed of sound, all of her pride, all of her machinations, and all of her cunning had been mercilessly smashed apart.

In the presence of absolute strength, everything she did had become a joke.

It could even be said that the bet between her and Sun Cyprestar had already become a joke. The betting stakes were only a spirit artifact level Heaven Eclipsing Cauldron, an arctic ice immortal stamen, and a drop of phoenix heart blood. Those treasures were undoubtedly precious, and the Heaven Eclipsing Cauldron was an object that even a Divine Lord powerhouse would struggle for. But compared to a drop of phoenix blood essence, all of it was nothing more than sand and wind.

When Lin Ming first involved the phoenix blood essence in this smelting trial, the bet for the Heaven Eclipsing Cauldron had already lost all meaning! This was a grand milestone that would be etched into the history of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. It was destined to be a story that would be spread down for all of eternity, turned into a myth by the clansmen of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. How could a mere Heaven Eclipsing Cauldron possibly compare?

Sixth level 8000 miles!

The temperature here was already 360 times the temperature of magma, and even the surrounding space was scorched so hot that it began twisting. The fiery astral winds were far more powerful, crazily howling as they flowed all over. Even if a 10,000 foot high mountain of divine iron were placed here, it would still be turned into gas by the air currents!

Luckily, Lin Ming’s three levels of Concepts had completed their initial fusion state. Moreover, no matter which one of these three Concepts was taken out, his understanding of them far surpassed that of all other disciples present. But now, in this environment, Lin Ming still had no choice but to slow down.

From 10 times the speed of sound he plummeted to five times the speed of sound. Then, he gradually slowed to three times the speed of sound.

As his speed reduced, the pressure he had to bear was much lower and he would also consume less energy.

In truth, after reaching this depth, no matter how extraordinary Lin Ming’s restorative ability was, it was impossible for him to continue with such a terrifying consumption rate of energy. He was able to maintain 80% of his strength, and the only reason for this was that he was using the Concept of Creation to transform the violent fire origin energy into a gentler form that he could use for himself.

Sixth level 9000 miles!

Lin Ming’s speed fell below the speed of sound. As he no longer passed through the sonic barrier, his consumption of true essence was reduced yet again.

Wishing to break into the Hells of Flame’s seventh level was more difficult than ascending to the heavens. But now, all the miracles that occurred on Lin Ming’s body had allowed him to reach this step. Even so, he was still reaching the end of the line!

All of the martial artists in the square held their breath, their eyes glued onto the light screen in the sky. They were all waiting for this historical moment to occur.

A sixth stage Life Destruction, 29 year old rookie disciple on his first smelting trial, would actually break through to the seventh level of the Hells of Flame!

At this step, all of Phoenix Cry Palace’s disciples, including even Huo Yanguang, were cheering Lin Ming on. Although many of Phoenix Cry Palace’s disciples had envied Lin Ming, now that his talent far surpassed all of theirs, they finally understood that it was impossible for any of them to chase after him, and all of that envy had slowly faded away.

On the contrary, Lin Ming’s growth would instead bring glory and prosperity to Phoenix Cry Palace. In the future, when everyone talked about Lin Ming, these disciples could proudly brag that they came from Phoenix Cry Palace, the same branch palace that Lin Ming came from!

Also, in the future when Lin Ming became a vital figure at headquarters, he would be able to bring good fortune to Phoenix Cry Palace. For the 72 palaces of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, it was impossible to be fair and even with all of them. There would always be some palaces that received far more resources than others, and there would always be some palaces that were stretched for resources.

In such a situation, no one in Phoenix Cry Palace would dare to offend Lin Ming anymore. Even someone like Sage Jiuyang, who almost controlled the entire Phoenix Cry Palace, would not think of moving against Lin Ming. This was because Lin Ming was now destined to become a paramount character of headquarters, someone that was the focus of attention.

9600 miles; Lin Ming’s speed dropped to half the speed of sound.

9800 miles; Lin Ming’s muscles bulged all over, blue veins popping up from his skin.

9900 miles; cracks began to form in Lin Ming’s protective true essence once again.

However, this didn’t matter. Even if some fire origin energy astral winds managed to break through his defenses, they would still be suppressed by the Heretical God Sprout and then absorbed by Lin Ming. With his tough meridians he was capable of withstanding such an impact.

50 miles… 40 miles… 30 miles… 10 miles… one mile!!!

Bang!

With a light sound, it seemed as if the entire 180,000 mile long 18 Hells of Flame quietly trembled at that moment. Lin Ming broke through the space barrier that separated the sixth and seventh levels, officially stepping into the space of the seventh level!

The seventh level of the Hells of Flame; the domain of god!

“He did it!!!”

“Too fierce… I never imagined that I would be able to witness history occurring with my own eyes…”

“Although I might never reach this boundary in my entire life, for better or worse, no matter what, Lin Ming is still a disciple who came from our Phoenix Cry Palace. I can feel proud just stating this fact in the future.”

“That’s right. Maybe headquarters will place a bit more focus on our Phoenix Cry Palace now?”

The Phoenix Cry Palace disciples spoke amongst themselves with fervid excitement. At this time, if Lin Ming were among them, he would have been surrounded and grabbed by them, tossed up into the air!

This was Lin Ming’s glory! This was also the glory of Phoenix Cry palace!

“He really reached the seventh level. It seems like the drop of phoenix blood essence will really be obtained by Lin Ming. This child, as long as he doesn’t perish in the future he will surely become an incomparably wonderful character!”

Duke Golden Sword said with zest.

“That’s right. Moreover, with Lin Ming’s background, it is already a miracle that he was able to reach this step. He has a great destiny, strong mentality, and unshakeable will. He can only be called extraordinary. It isn’t easy for such a person to perish. I believe that our Ancient Phoenix Clan is destined to produce another extreme character. Even the current Lord Patriarch could not compare to Lin Ming when he was at the Life Destruction realm!” Monarch Sweetyfox gave her own evaluation.

The Patriarch of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, that was a Divine Realm Holy Lord. Placed in the Divine Realm, a Holy Lord was a top character that could dominate their own stretch of the world. However, this didn’t mean that Lin Ming would inevitably become a Holy Lord in the future. After all, there were countless variables and uncertainties on the road of martial arts.

The current Patriarch of the Ancient Phoenix Clan indeed couldn’t compare with Lin Ming when he was at the Life Destruction Realm. But, the Patriarch had experienced immense lucky chances during the Divine Sea, Divine Transformation, and Divine Lord realms. These also had to be placed into consideration.

If Lin Ming wished to become a Holy Lord, he would need to continue the momentum that he currently had at Life Destruction.

This was the reason why the Ancient Phoenix Clan wasn’t willing to invest a drop of phoenix blood essence in a Life Destruction realm martial artist. There were simply too many unknown factors that could affect a genius’ future. Even if a genius died, they might be lost within the rising talents in the future. A genius needed destiny and lucky chances to continue walking down the road of martial arts.

And at this time, Lin Ming’s smelting trial still hadn’t ended. This was the first time that he had entered the seventh level of the Hells of Flame. To a rookie disciple, this mysterious space was called the domain of god!

To a Life Destruction realm martial artist, this was an absolute forbidden zone!

The seventh level of the Hells of Flame no longer had fire origin energy astral winds. Rather, they were replaced by an aurora of glowing red light!

This glowing light was illusive like a dream. It filled the world, incomparably vivid, similar to a paradise of immortals. But, if a martial artist who didn’t comprehend the Fire Laws was covered by this glowing light, then their entire being would evaporate without even ashes left over!

At this time, it was already Lin Ming’s limit to break into the seventh level. And now that he suddenly had to bear the impact of this glowing red light, his protective true essence began to rapidly rupture!

Beams of glowing light shot into Lin Ming’s body, burning through his meridians!

Lin Ming focused all of his will into the Heretical God Sprout, resisting the impact of the multi-hued light. But, he found himself verging on the edge of collapse. His body burned. His skin was scorched black, cracking, and his flesh was cooked, emitting sizzling sounds.

Lin Ming’s current condition was extremely poor. He had less than 60% of his true essence remaining. Moreover, he was consuming it at a ridiculous rate.

But Lin Ming still held on. He grit his teeth and persisted. The role of the 18 Hells of Flame was originally not to check the level of a disciple and how far they could go. Rather, it was a smelting trial that pushed one’s potential to the limits. In the smelting trial of the 18 Hells of Flame, when one arrived at their limits, the longer they stayed in that dangerous zone, the greater their harvests would be.

When Lin Ming first started the initial fusion of the three levels of Fire Concepts, he had used the pressure of this environment as the turning point of his comprehension of Laws.

As they said, one had to strike the iron while it was hot. To use the 18 Hells of Flame at this time to temper his own Laws was the best method to do so. If he gave up now then his benefits would be significantly lessened and he would have to take many more detours.

Lin Ming grit his teeth and actually pulled the glowing red light into his bones and flesh, allowing that glowing light to burn the Law runes on his bones!

Zi zi zi!

As his flesh burned, the pure jade-white bones were also scorched black, and they even began to wither and crack.

To draw fire into one’s body and set their own bones on fire, just what sort of pain was that? Even so, Lin Ming clenched his teeth and withstood it all!

Chapter 1025 – Rushing the Illusionary God Combat Array

Fire Spirit Star’s Illusionary God Combat Array already had a history of a million years. After the supreme elder of the past laid down this array formation, it had recorded the countless heroic young elites that had passed through it. Then, a simulacrum of these heroic young elites was reproduced through the array formation and energy, forming a killing array. When a trial challenger rushed through the Illusionary God Combat Array they would have to face the onslaught of these numerous geniuses.

Lin Ming silently extracted the Phoenix Blood Spear and slowly flew into the Illusionary God Combat Array. It had already been over a full year since he had last had a hearty and fulfilling battle. Now, his body was bursting with energy, impatient to erupt!

“I wonder how many people Lin Ming can slay. What happens if he surpasses the Thousand Slaughter?” Several young girls from Charming Phoenix Palace whispered to themselves, lost in a daze as they stared at Lin Ming’s fading back, dreaming of him.

In fact, Lin Ming was indeed a peerless young heroic elite. Not to mention the great marvels that occurred when he crossed the seventh stage of Life Destruction or his handsome appearance and ethereal temperament, but just based on his talent, future, and also the possibility that he would be able to absorb a drop of phoenix blood essence and obtain the characteristics of a God Beast’s blood essence in his veins, that alone was enough for countless young beauties to wish that they could marry him.

After having reached this step, it was normal for young girls to be captivated by him.

“Who knows? No one has managed to complete the Thousand Slaughter in 40,000 years. To complete the Illusionary God Combat Array’s Thousand Slaughter is more difficult than reaching the seventh level of the Hells of Flame. Lin Ming is powerful, but wanting to accomplish this feat won’t be easy. Just a few days ago he had barely managed to reach the seventh level of the Hells of Flame too.”

At this point not many people doubted that Lin Ming would be able to obtain the drop of phoenix blood essence. They were only guessing on how far Lin Ming could go in his first attempt within the Illusionary God Combat Array.

Hu –

Lin Ming suddenly shot forwards. His body turned into a ray of light that directly broke into the Illusionary God Combat Array.

When Lin Ming arrived within the Illusionary God Combat Array, he discovered that he had entered a very broad expanse of space.

Lin Ming was in a land of fire. Beating flames surrounded him on all sides, dancing in groups around him. Besides that, there was nothing here but a vast, dark and deathly silent plain, incomparably quiet.

Several hundred feet in front of Lin Ming, a dark gray-clothed person slowly surfaced from the ground. This person was eight feet tall and his features were fierce and demonic. He held a great curved knife in his hand.

“Mm? This isn’t a human?”

Lin Ming looked at this gray-clothed man. He had a fifth stage Life Destruction cultivation, two stages lower than Lin Ming himself. This was equal to the most ordinary standard for being a genius in the Divine Realm.

According to age, as a 29 year old seventh stage Life Destruction martial artist, Lin Ming was considered a standard top talent of one of the 72 branch palaces. But, when placed within the entire Ancient Phoenix Clan, this wasn’t too amazing at all. For instance, Yan Littlemoon had a seventh stage Life Destruction cultivation and was two years younger than he was.

In other words, once Lin Ming had slain around 500 or 600 people, he would begin to face groups of top seventh and eighth stage Life Destruction masters. When he neared a thousand people, he might even face large squads of ninth stage Life Destruction elites.

Moreover, these people would not be normal ninth stage Life Destruction masters. That would be the true start of the battle!

Sii – !

The gray-clothed man raised his curved knife and rushed forwards. This curved knife was a high-grade saint artifact. As the gray-clothed man slashed it down, a knife light shot out like a 10,000 foot bolt of white lightning, splitting apart the atmosphere.

Lin Ming turned his hand. His body turned into a haze of blue smoke as the Phoenix Blood Spear shot forth like a laser beam!

Kacha!

The 10,000 foot knife light was torn apart by the Phoenix Blood Spear’s spear light. The spear light continued forth unabated, piercing through that gray-clothed man’s protective true essence and stabbing through his heart.

Blood splashed all around! The gray-clothed man flew backwards. He smashed into the ground, and then his body began to slowly fade away.

Lin Ming effortlessly killed his first opponent. This was also a matter of course. Up to this point, Lin Ming had never yet met a genius at his level whose combat strength had surpassed his own. Moreover, this gray-clothed man had only been at the fifth stage of Life Destruction: he was two stages of Life Destruction lower. Killing him was as easy as turning his hand.

At this time, outside the Illusionary God Combat Array, a star lit up on the arch of the gate. This star represented Lin Ming having slain the first opponent.

Only two breaths of time had passed for Lin Ming to complete the first kill. No one was surprised by this. They waited for the other stars to start shining, especially the ninth star; that represented completion of the Thousand Slaughter.

At this time, Monarch Sweetyfox’s thoughts moved. She looked up at the sky and mumbled to herself. “Mm? Some people have arrived. This aura is… high-grade spirit artifact?”

Just as her voice fell, a rumbling sound filled the sky like endless thunderclaps. The skies above Fire Spirit Star were torn asunder, and a massive scroll flew out from that shattered space. It slowly unfurled in the skies, forming countless beautiful and exquisite images. These scenes were clearly part of the scroll, and yet when they were projected into the skies of Fire Spirit Star they seemed completely lifelike. They formed a separate domain of space in the skies.

“That is the Sacred Flame Samsara Scroll! It is someone from the Huo Family, and someone extremely important at that!”

Monarch Sweetyfox was surprised. The Sacred Flame Samsara Scroll was one of the Huo Family’s high-grade spirit artifact magic treasures. Not just that, but it was an outstanding existence amongst all high-grade spirit artifacts. To be able to activate the Sacred Flame Samsara Scroll and drive it through the void, only a high level figure of the Huo Family would be able to do that. “The news of this was just passed out and yet the Huo Family personally sent someone to Fire Spirit Star in order to win over Lin Ming? That’s a bit too much isn’t it? I wonder who came this time?”

Monarch Sweetyfox glanced over at Duke Golden Sword. Duke Golden Sword shrugged. He had only sent the news, he didn’t know who had come from the Huo Family.

The disciples of the three branch palaces as well as their leading Elders all stopped talking about Lin Ming attempting the Illusionary God Combat Array and looked up at the Sacred Flame Samsara Scroll in the sky.

“That is actually a… high-grade spirit artifact?” Sun Cyprestar said, startled. There was an enormous difference in value between every small grade of spirit artifacts. His Heaven Eclipsing Cauldron was in truth only a top low-grade spirit artifact, and yet that was enough to cause Chu Redcloud plot to make a bet with him. As for the Samsara Scroll floating in the sky, that was something that his Heaven Eclipsing Cauldron could not hope to compare with.

Without a doubt, whoever had come was a great figure from either headquarters or the three great families.

As the Sacred Flame Samsara Scroll unfurled, three red-robed Elders slowly floated down, flanked by a pair of golden-armored warriors.

As Monarch Sweetyfox, Blackwood, and Duke Golden Sword saw these three Elders, especially the one in front, all of their eyes widened to the point of nearly falling out. Their hearts nearly stopped beating in their chests.

As for Sun Cyprestar and Chu Redcloud, both of them had a perplexed expression as they didn’t know who had arrived. But, this confusion only lasted for a brief moment before they were frightened out of their wits.

This was because Monarch Sweetyfox, Blackwood, and Duke Golden Sword all deeply bowed to the red-robed Elder at the front.

“Disciple Sweetyfox respectfully welcomes the Highest Elder!”

“Disciple Blackwood respectfully welcomes the Highest Elder!”

“Disciple Golden Sword respectfully welcomes the Highest Elder!”

Highest Elder!?!?

This red-robed old man was actually a Highest Elder of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, someone whose status could compare with the Patriarch’s!? That was simply a god-like figure! Just what would he have come to Fire Spirit Star for?

Chapter 1026 – Kill Them All

As Monarch Sweetyfox and the others called out the title of the Highest Elder, Chu Redcloud, Sun Cyprestar, and the many disciples of the three branch palaces were all left dumbfounded. They didn’t think that this red-robed old man was actually the Highest Elder of the Ancient Phoenix Clan.

The Highest Elders were titanic figures. Whether it was strength or status, they were equal with the Patriarch. There were even some Highest Elders that had been the Patriarch in the past, but then had abdicated the throne in order to go into seclusion and cultivate. Their strength was even higher than the current Patriarch’s.

These characters were lofty and existed above others. Normally they would never come into contact with low level disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, nor would they visit the 72 branch palaces. If a Palace Master of one of the 72 branch palaces went to the Ancient Phoenix Clan Headquarters to request an audience with the Highest Elder, they would also have to respectfully bow.

As for low level palace Elders like Chu Redcloud and Sun Cyprestar, they would simply never see any of the Highest Elders in their lifetimes. At most they would see someone at a lower level like the Internal Affairs Envoy or the Merit Elder. And in their opinion, these types of people were already extraordinary figures. Meeting them was similar to a countryside magistrate seeing an imperial emissary. As for the Highest Elder, that was the emperor.

Now the Highest Elder had come to Fire Spirit Star. There could only be one explanation for it, and that was that he had come here to observe Lin Ming’s trial!

As Chu Redcloud and Sun Cyprestar thought of this, both of them gulped. Lin Ming had even managed to arouse the interest of such a grand character!

“Lin Ming is inside?”

The red-robed old man indifferently asked Duke Golden Sword as he floated high in the sky.

“Yes.” Duke Golden Sword swallowed a mouthful of saliva. This old man speaking to him was named Huo Violentstone and was also his father-in-law’s grandfather. In the face of a Highest Elder whose status was so great it could frighten others to death, even the normally impertinent Duke Golden Sword felt an immense pressure.

Huo Violentstone looked over to the single star shining on the arch of the Illusionary God Combat Array. Of the nine stars, only one had lit up. This signified that Lin Ming had slain his first opponent.

“He just entered?”

“Yes, it’s only been a dozen or so breaths of time.”

“Mm.” Huo Violentstone nodded. Normally the Illusionary God Combat Array trial took an extremely long period of time to complete. In a battle between two geniuses where their strength wasn’t too far apart, a battle could last several quarter hours or even several hours, not to mention the time it would take to complete the Thousand Slaughter. Even though the beginning would be a bit faster, the further one progressed, the longer each battle would take.

Normally, it would take around a few hours to slay 600 to 700 people. But to kill 800 people, that would take most of the day. As for 900 people, that might take a full day.

40,000 years ago, when someone completed the Thousand Slaughter, that had lasted for two days and two nights!

The last section of the battles was particularly difficult. Withstanding such an endeavor was far easier said than done! A martial artist that completed the Thousand Slaughter would have to have terrifying endurance, and a recovery ability that would allow them to continue through a near-endless revolving war. They also had to possess strong nerves and a powerful will. Otherwise, in a high intensity battle where one’s mind was stressed from maintaining total concentration, even if one’s body and true essence could withstand it, their mind might not. In a battle between masters, a single distraction could prove to be fatal!

Huo Violentstone thought for a moment and then fell onto the ground in front of Totem Tower. As for everyone else, they retreated in unison, giving ground to Huo Violentstone. In front of a Highest Elder, all of these people were vigilant and also cautious in their discussion.

At this time, the second star lit up; this star symbolized that 10 people had been slain.

Currently, Lin Ming had only been in there for 20 breaths of time. The first 10 people within the Illusionary God Combat Array came out one at a time. After killing one, it would take one or two breaths of time for the next opponent to appear. For Lin Ming to slaughter 10 opponents within 20 breaths of time, that proved that he had instantly killed his opponents as they showed up.

This was also natural. The opponents at the beginning wouldn’t surpass the sixth stage of Life Destruction. With Lin Ming’s killing strength, it was no different from cutting vegetables.

Then, the third star also lit up. Lin Ming had slain 50 opponents within the Illusionary God Combat Array.

Starting at the 51st opponent, Lin Ming would have to face three at a time.

In this battle, three opponents would appear. Moreover, two of these three would have a seventh stage Life Destruction cultivation, the same as Lin Ming.

These three people appeared and then joined forces to rush at Lin Ming. Each one was fully focused on attacking without giving a single thought to defense. Their moves were all designed for them to perish together with Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s expression was calm. He waved the Phoenix Blood Spear and endless spear lights covered his body. With a ‘peng peng peng’ sound, the combined attack of the three was blocked by Lin Ming.

Then, Lin Ming swept his spear out. A beautiful spear light drew a brilliant arc, a simple move capable of sweeping through an army. The spearpoint slashed the throats of the three opponents, instantly beheading all of them. They collapsed and vanished in a bloody light!

Lin Ming’s moves were extremely simple, but they could be described with a single word – fast, so fast that they reached the extremes of velocity. With such a high speed, the might that such a simple move could display was unimaginable.

After slaying these three people, more and more opponents emerged. However, none of them were Lin Ming’s match.

100 slaughtered!

200 slaughtered!

300 slaughtered!

400 slaughtered!

After killing 400 people, the geniuses Lin Ming faced were all at the seventh stage of Life Destruction and above, with many at the eighth stage of Life Destruction.

Lin Ming discovered that the number of opponents he had to face at the same time increased by three for every 100 people he killed. For instance, he faced 12 enemies simultaneously after killing 400 people, and now he faced 15 enemies simultaneously after killing 500 people!

The cultivation of these opponents didn’t sound too high. In the past, let alone Life Destruction powerhouses, Lin Ming had even slain numerous Divine Sea powerhouses. But, those Divine Sea powerhouses he had killed couldn’t compare with these people in front of him.

If any one of these opponents were chosen, they would be equal to a 29 year old Huo Yanguang or Zhou Fei. In the future they would become characters that crossed the ninth stage of Life Destruction.

Moreover, these people all attacked as if they didn’t care for their lives. Their coordination was impeccable and their various attack moves sealed away all avenues of retreat!

However, in the face of absolute strength, all of that was useless!

Spear light swept out and blood splashed out. The Phoenix Blood Spear was like a red dragon diving through a sea of blood. Wherever it visited, flesh and blood would rain down!

Outside of the Illusionary God Combat Array, another star lit up.

Before, because fewer enemies had appeared, Lin Ming’s kill count had increased slowly. But now that over 10 opponents appeared each time, the number of them he slaughtered rapidly grew!

An hour later, Lin Ming had already slaughtered 600 people within the Illusionary God Combat Array. This was the same distance that Yan Littlemoon had reached.

Once he passed the checkpoint of slaying 600 enemies, 18 of them appeared at a time!

Moreover, these 18 people all had eighth stage Life Destruction cultivations, a single stage higher than Lin Ming. This meant that if they were real people, their cultivation speed would surpass Lin Ming’s, reaching the same level as White Daohong and Lu Xiaoyun!

Correspondingly, their combat strength wasn’t very different from a 29 year old White Daohong and Lu Xiaoyun. Now, Lin Ming had to face 18 of these enemies at a time!

“Trial challenger, for you to rush this far, you have done well. But, this is where your journey ends. Starting from slaughtering 600 opponents, the difficulty will soar to another level. Us 18 people will send you on your way out of here!” The leader of the 18 people suddenly said out loud.

“Mm?” Lin Ming was slightly surprised. He didn’t think that these people would actually speak out like real living persons. It was clear that these 18 people were different from his previous opponents, and this difference was that they all had spiritual wisdom. They weren’t too different from true living opponents. They weren’t like the previous opponents, without the slightest bit of will, risking everything to bring down Lin Ming.

“Then bring it on!” Lin Ming faintly began to stir with excitement. His opponents so far hadn’t been able to place the least bit of pressure on him. But now, he felt a tiny bit of threat from these 18 enemies. He could finally be a bit serious about this, even if it was only a little bit.

“Kill!”

The black-clothed man in the lead roared out and then all 18 of them attacked together as if they were a single person. They moved in in sync, launching a barrage of attacks at Lin Ming.

And, the weapons they used to attack were all top grade saint artifacts!

These weren’t weapons formed from energy, but true top grade saint artifacts!

Within the Illusionary God Combat Array, there were many top grade saint artifacts stored. Their purpose was to stabilize the eye of the array formation. Now, these weapons were used by these virtual energy simulacrums to attack.

The previous opponents Lin Ming faced had only used high-grade saint artifacts, and the majority of them were formed by energy so their strength was limited. But now, all the weapons used were top grade saint artifact. The might of a top grade saint artifact was far from what a high-grade saint artifact could ever hope to compare with!

18 top grade saint artifacts!

Although there was still a great disparity between these top grade saint artifacts and the Phoenix Blood Spear that neared being a transcendent saint artifact, when these 18 weapons were combined together, their power absolutely surpassed the Phoenix Blood Spear’s!

In the moment when the 18 enemies attacked, Lin Ming felt a great pressure fall over him. This was the might and glory of a top grade saint artifact, as well as the influence of a domain!

18 layers of domains!

Each of these enemies Lin Ming currently faced actually possessed a domain!

The grade of these domains was no worse than the Blue Lotus Domain. If any of these people were placed in the 72 branch palaces, they would be splendid and famous characters. 99% of the disciples that attended the Fire Spirit Star smelting trial this round would be unable to be a match for any of them!

18 different domains superimposed on each other! And then, the pressure of 18 top grade saint artifacts was added on top of that!

Because these different domains could directly multiply each other’s strength due to the competing influences, this was still not a pressure that the average person could withstand. If one’s combat strength wasn’t high enough, they wouldn’t even be able to move their true essence in this combined domain field. In other words, if any of the other trial challengers from the three branch palaces were to be in his shoes, they would find it difficult to even stand, so how could they begin to fight back?

“Great!”

Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. After killing 600 people and reaching this point, he finally felt pressure! Only such a vigorous battle could stir his excitement and rouse his heart. He simply hadn’t been able to display his strength before this. Since breaking through to the seventh stage of Life Destruction, this would be his first chance to verify the insights he comprehended from within the 18 Hells of Flame!

Bang!

With an explosive sound, Lin Ming’s figure instantly disappeared, avoiding the combined strike of the 18 people. And this strike ruptured the earth, able to cause mountains to collapse. Endless amounts of crushed stone flew into the air.

Lin Ming raised the Phoenix Blood Spear as he floated in the air. He didn’t have a serious expression on at all. Instead, he grinned with fervor. “You’re not bad, but you’re still far short of being able to defeat me.”

“Haha! Don’t worry, the fun part is still coming. Combined martial skills, kill!”

The black-clothed man in the lead gave a loud shout. The 18 people combined forces to attack. The entire sky was filled with the light of top grade saint artifacts!

Chapter 1032 – Old Sorrows, New Hate

“What!? Crimson Strifecloud!?”

“The Battle King! He is fighting the Battle King!?”

As Huo Violentstone spoke, the jaws of the all the martial artists present dropped to the floor, greatly shocked.

“I never thought that Lin Ming’s opponent would actually be Crimson Strifecloud!” Huo Violentstone stared at the phantom figure of the Battle King reflected in the fire spirit mirror. His eyes shot open, and fire seemed to pour out from his heated gaze. He never thought that everything would line up in such a coincidental manner!

“Yes… in the past when Crimson Strifecloud rushed through the Illusionary God Combat Array, he was also 29 years old. That is why he has appeared as Lin Ming’s opponent!”

A rookie disciple could attend their first Ancient Phoenix smelting trial anytime before they were 33 years of age. But, the most common age was between 28 and 31 years. This was because at that period of time, most martial artists were beginning to form their comprehension of the Fire Laws, and their cultivation would also be at the seventh, eighth, or ninth stage of Life Destruction. If they attended the Ancient Phoenix smelting trial in this period, it would have the best effects in enhancing their comprehensions of Laws.

If they came too early, their comprehensions would be lacking and the benefits they gained would be limited. However, if they came too late, their foundation would be far more settled and the benefits they gained would be far less.

Thus, Crimson Strifecloud and Lin Ming had both rushed through the Illusionary God Combat Array at the same time. It could be called a coincidence, but also the truth.

And the Illusionary God Combat Array would record the information of every person that entered, and would then be able to produce a perfect energy form simulacrum of them. Lin Ming and Crimson Strifecloud were of the same age, so it was natural for them to encounter each other.

This was an unrivalled powerhouse of 40,000 years in the past, duking it out with the current top talent!

“Who is Crimson Strifecloud? He was the Battle King of 40,000 years ago, the son of a World King, the current Crimson Dragon Envoy of Crimson Light World! His status, his power, his influence, all of it surpasses the current Patriarch of the Ancient Phoenix Clan! When such a character was young, just how powerful would they have been?”

It had to be known that many of the current high level figures of the Ancient Phoenix Clan had once been rolled over by the Battle King. The disparity was far too obvious!

“Can Lin Ming win? His opponent is the Battle King!”

“I think it’s over. This Battle King is too kick ass, he is the son of a World King!”

“It really is hard to win, but that doesn’t mean there isn’t a chance. For better or worse, Lin Ming is still the best talent to appear in my Ancient Phoenix Clan for the last few tens of thousands of years!”

“How laughable. I once thought that Lin Ming would be able to smoothly complete the Thousand Slaughter, but now I can see just how abnormal the difficulty of it is. Moreover, Lin Ming’s Thousand Slaughter is far harder to complete than the Battle King’s Thousand Slaughter from 40,000 years ago!”

40,000 years ago, Crimson Strifecloud was someone who had defeated his opponents to achieve the Thousand Slaughter. But now, Lin Ming had to face Crimson Strifecloud himself; the difficulty was certainly higher!

“Looking at the results, this should be an equal battle between a dragon and a tiger! If Lin Ming can really win then he will be even more freaking amazing! Even if he can’t win, if he can fight with Crimson Strifecloud for several dozen rounds, that will still be enough to etch his eternal name down in the annals of history!”

As people were discussing, Lin Ming couldn’t hear them within the Illusionary God Combat Array. Instead, he was carefully observing his opponent.

“Eighth stage Life Destruction cultivation?”

Lin Ming was surprised. He thought that his opponent now would be a Ninefall master, or perhaps even a Divine Sea master. He didn’t think that they would only be at the eighth stage of Life Dsetruction!

An eighth stage Life Destruction cultivation at 29 years of age wasn’t considered too fast for an extreme cultivating talent.

But, Lin Ming didn’t underestimate his opponent. Cultivation speed wasn’t everything. In this world there were countless extreme geniuses that would intentionally suppress their cultivation at the eighth stage of Life Destruction, staying there for several years. This was in order to further increase their comprehension of Laws and consolidate their foundation, so that when they stepped into Ninefall, they would undergo a greater baptism of Laws. Then they would truly be a dragon that ascended to heaven!

Perhaps this man in front of him was such a person!

“Hahaha, I never imagined that after so many years someone would finally be able to reach this step! Ancient Phoenix Clan, you fellows aren’t as shabby as I thought you were!”

Crimson Strifecloud looked at Lin Ming and guffawed. Lin Ming faintly frowned. This person’s attitude was arrogant enough, and listening to his words, he wasn’t from the Ancient Phoenix Clan either.

“Speak your name, peasant! When I completed the Illusionary God Combat Array’s Thousand Slaughter in the past, all of the so-called ‘geniuses’ that attempted the same smelting trial as me were simply nothing more than a pile of unsightly garbage, nothing but a crowd of trash! To think that they dared to call themselves the chosen prides of heavens, how ridiculous! I left behind a wisp of my divine sense to see just what genius of the Ancient Phoenix Clan would barely be able to reach here. But, I was left disappointed. For 40,000 years no one appeared, until you. You just manage to qualify for the likes of I to remember your name. Now, tell me your name!”

“Mm?” Lin Ming was surprised. From Crimson Strifecloud’s speech just now, Lin Ming was able to discern his identity. “You are the Battle King!”

“Correct! I am the Battle King, Crimson Strifecloud!” Crimson Strifecloud heartily laughed. His laughter was filled with a wild self-confidence and rampant arrogance. But, he indeed had the capital to act so recklessly!

At this time, outside of the Illusionary God Combat Array, Huo Violentstone’s hair nearly stood on end from anger! Even the air around him began to twist from a burning heat. This was the fire energy that he subconsciously released due to the extreme rage in his heart. This was a violent animosity worthy of his name!

How could he not be angry!? What Crimson Strifecloud just said was, ‘in the past, all of the so-called ‘geniuses’ that attempted the same smelting trial as me were simply nothing more than a pile of unsightly garbage, nothing but a crowd of trash! To think that they dared to call themselves the chosen prides of heavens, how ridiculous!’

And this clearly included Huo Violentstone in the same group!

“Good! Good! Very good! In this old man’s life, this is the first time anyone has dared to call me trash! Very good! Crimson Strifecloud, you are a crazy bastard! I want to see just how kick ass you actually are! 40,000 years ago, you managed to trample all over our faces, but now I want to see if you still have this ability 40,000 years later!”

Huo Violentstone seemed like an erupting volcano. At this moment, anyone or anything that dared approach within three feet of Huo Violentstone would have been instantly burnt to ash!

It had to be known that the geniuses within the Illusionary God Combat Array were energy form simulacrums reproduced by the information recorded in the array formation. Even their intelligence was a copy. But, what Crimson Strifecloud had said was that he had left a wisp of his divine sense behind. In other words, the opponent Lin Ming faced was nearly the exact same as Crimson Strifecloud. And, the words he spoke also represented the true ideas of Crimson Strifecloud.

How could Huo Violentstone not be enraged? Crimson Strifecloud had swept away not just countless resources of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, but also their little princess. At that time, numerous heroic young elites wished to cut down Crimson Strifecloud’s glory in the Ancient Phoenix smelting trial. But, the result was that they had been beaten up so badly that their mothers and fathers wouldn’t have recognized them. And now, Crimson Strifecloud laughed in their faces and called them a crowd of trash.

This was the same as poking at their reverse scale, the source of all rage!

If this could be tolerated, what else could be tolerated!?

At this time, behind Huo Violentstone, Monarch Sweetyfox and Duke Golden Sword were holding their breath as they teetered on edge, careful not to exacerbate the situation.

As for Huo Highdragon and Huo Whitejade, they ruefully smiled at each other. This High Ancestor of the Huo Family was indeed just like his name. His anger was not ordinary anger!

When he was angered, even the Elders of his own family would be publicly abused and scolded. He wouldn’t even care about maintaining face in front of the juniors. Now, the Crimson Strifecloud in the Illusionary God Combat Array could be described as having opened the forbidden box of shame and humiliation. How could Huo Violentstone not turn mad with rage!?

Those near him could feel that Huo Violentstone was a volcano ready to erupt at any moment. If they approached him at this time it was possible they would really eat shit; they might even become the target of some collateral anger. However, none of them dared to draw back. They could only stand where they were in utter silence.

“I pray to the heavens that Lin Ming can contend with him. At least, the manner in which he loses cannot be too ugly. He needs to last at least several dozen moves, and it would be best if he could wound Crimson Strifecloud…” Huo Highdragon gulped as he spoke to Huo Whitejade with a true essence sound transmission.

Huo Whitejade forced a smile, saying, “Yeah. Otherwise, once this old man turns angry, none of us will have a good time. Once he is angry, he doesn’t distinguish between right and wrong and vents his anger on anyone close to him. It is a 100% possibility that we will be the punching bags this time. Before, the two of us have already committed a number of mistakes and screwed up some matters. If the old man is happy then he won’t bother investigating these matters, but if he’s angry, then both of us are done for!”

“Aiyaya, we can only hope that Lin Ming can claw back some honor for us so that the High Ancestor can calm his anger a bit. If he can do this then I’ll gift him some resources from the Office of Internal Affairs in the future.” Huo Highdragon said. His position was that of the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Internal Affairs Envoy.

And at this time, within the Illusionary God Combat Array, just as Lin Ming was beginning to fight, an old voice abruptly sounded out from the skies.

“Lin Ming! This old man is the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Highest Elder, Huo Violentstone! I am also the Patriarch of the Huo Family! You listen well to me. In the past, this little bastard stole our resources and wrested away the little princess of our Ancient Phoenix Clan along with her perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline! In this battle, you must do everything you can to win for me! Even if you have to risk your life, you have to win at all costs! Even if you must wrestle with Buddha for a single incense stick of time, that is what you must do! If you want to become an unrivalled genius, then you must sweep away all obstacles that block your path! You must kick that Crimson Strifecloud into the ground and beat him up so that his teeth scatter over the ground! I want you to slap him so hard that not even his parents will recognize him! If you can do this then I will immediately give you the phoenix blood essence! Not just that, but resources, phoenix blood, beautiful women with pure bloodlines, anything else you desire will be yours! I will even happily lend you the Sacred Flame Testament to perceive for an entire year! The Huo Family will support you with the entirety of our strength!”

This sudden voice left Lin Ming in a daze. Ancient Phoenix Clan Highest Elder? Huo Family Patriarch, Huo Violentstone?

How… how could such a top character suddenly appear in Fire Spirit Star, and also be observing his smelting trial? Moreover, his words just now had been extremely vulgar. Especially when he said he would gift ‘beautiful women with pure bloodlines’; Lin Ming didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry. In his impression, Highest Elders were noble and respected characters. They quietly sat atop their lofty thrones, looking down at others, so where would one appear that was so ribald. Did this Huo Violentstone have a deep-seated grudge with Crimson Strifecloud?

But soon after, the Crimson Strifecloud in front of Lin Ming responded. He loudly laughed and said, “The one who spoke, aren’t you someone from 40,000 years ago, someone referred to as the Fire Lion or something like that? I also have a tiny impression of you. I never imagined that with your strength you could actually manage to become a Highest Elder of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. It seems that the Ancient Phoenix Clan is really in trouble. Ever since those extreme characters like Huo Burning Heaven and Xiao Daoji appeared, your Ancient Phoenix Clan has become worse with every generation.”

As Crimson Strifecloud spoke, Huo Violentstone became even angrier. “Crimson Strifecloud, whether or not my Ancient Phoenix Clan is in trouble is not for the likes of you to say. Enough with the trash talk; fists speak the only truth. The opponent in front of you is my disciple. This father wants to see whether or not you will get beaten up so badly by my disciple today that not even your mother and father will recognize you!”

Crimson Strifecloud’s current status neared that of a World King. Although Huo Violentstone was far inferior, his temper was hotter than flames, and he had a fearless disposition; he simply didn’t fear offending Crimson Strifecloud. He didn’t even ask for Lin Ming’s opinion and directly became Lin Ming’s cheap master.

Lin Ming didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry.

Chapter 1035 – Concept of Manifestation

“That is the fourth level Concept of Fire!”

As the branch palace disciples saw fire dragons, fire snakes, fire cranes, fire golden birds, fire parasol trees, and all sorts of fire existences spin into life around Crimson Strifecloud, all of them sucked in a deep breath of cold air.

These things around Crimson Strifecloud that transformed from flames were not lifeless. Rather, they were spiritual beings with their own intelligence. They were life forms composed of living flames. In fact, these spiritual existences were not condensed by Crimson Strifecloud, but produced by fire origin energy that was controlled by the Laws.

The was the symbol of the fourth level Fire Concept – Manifestation!

Metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wind, thunder, these elemental Laws all had different types of Concepts for the first three levels. However, all of them shared the same fourth level Concept.

And that was… Manifestation.

After arriving at this step, energy would have life and intelligence of its own.

Fire origin energy could manifest as fiery vermillion birds or fiery crows. Thunder origin energy could combine into a thunder kirin. Earth origin energy could develop into an earthen black turtle, or earthen snake. Wind origin energy could form gale birds, great rocs, and so on!

Without having comprehended the fourth level Concept, a martial artist’s true essence and energy would only be lifeless. In order for martial artists to kill an enemy, they would have to control their true essence with every attack. Without a martial artist’s thoughts controlling their own true essence, it would be nothing but a pile of scattered sand without any lethal killing force.

But for someone that had comprehended the Concept of Manifestation, that was different.

Their true essence would have life. Sometimes it would scatter, sometimes it would gather, it would have endless and infinite changes. A martial artist could use their true essence to kill an enemy without the need to control it!

This type of true essence was far easier to manipulate. With just a thought, hundreds and thousands of supernatural powers could be displayed; this was almost impossible to defend against!

When two martial artists used a similar amount of energy, the one that understood the Concept of Manifestation would be able to display a far greater power. This was because their energy contained a life of its own!

“The Concept of Manifestation, Crimson Strifecloud has actually managed to comprehend the Concept of Manifestation! How can Junior-apprentice Brother Lin still fight?”

“Their speed is similar and their true essence foundation is similar. But, Crimson Strifecloud’s cultivation is greater and his comprehension of the Laws is actually an entire boundary ahead. Moreover, he has the Scorching Blood Battle Body. In all other aspects Junior-apprentice Brother Lin doesn’t have any advantages. I’m afraid he will lose here.”

Although all the disciples present passionately wished for Lin Ming to win, they weren’t too confident about whether he could truly defeat Crimson Strifecloud. Just now, Lin Ming’s heroic words and daring spirit had set their blood boiling over with zeal, but in the end, Lin Ming was only speaking about how great his potential was. In terms of their current bloodline strength, he was still inferior to Crimson Strifecloud.

“Come out, Crimson Flame Dragon!”

Crimson Strifecloud gave a loud shout and all the fire existences that formed around him gathered together, forming a flaming red dragon. With a loud roar, this flaming red dragon rushed towards Lin Ming!

This flame dragon was itself a Fire Elemental!

To use a Fire Elemental as the foundation, and pouring in fire origin energy with the Concept of Manifestation, that made this flame dragon nearly have a life of its own.

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. The Phoenix Blood Spear shot out like a bolt of lightning. The 999 small blood spears around the spear shaft twisted into a scarlet storm that swept towards the Crimson Flame Dragon.

Blue Lotus Flame Dance!

As Lin Ming used the source energy of the Phoenix Blood Spear, he also fused the power of Laws into it. On top of the Phoenix Blood Spear’s point, a blue lotus of flame slowly appeared, blooming in brilliant glory.

The blue flame lotus was surrounded by 999 sword-like blood spears!

The two massive energies violently smashed into each other!

However, there was no chaotic explosion as expected. Instead, the Crimson Flame Dragon actually opened its great jaws. Its body suddenly expanded 10 times over and swallowed up Lin Ming along with the blue lotus!

The martial artists watching this battle at Totem Tower’s square widened their eyes. Their hearts jumped into their throats.

“Hahaha! Useless! Although I am inferior to you in the first three level Concepts of the Fire Laws, my Concept of Fire is still an entire boundary higher than your own. With the fourth level Concept of the Fire Laws, the Concept of Manifestation, combined together with the Crimson Flame Dragon Fire Elemental, that has created an energy form with a life of its own. Its might is beyond your imagination! Now, die for me!”

Crimson Strifecloud raised his hands, wanting to galvanize the energy within the Crimson Flame Dragon to grind Lin Ming to death. The stomach of the Crimson Flame Dragon was a separate space. As long as one entered within, the space would collapse and the violent power of fire would rush in. That incomparably terrifying destructive power was able to tear everything to bits and pieces!

But at this moment, a scene that left Crimson Strifecloud shocked occurred.

Suddenly, a boundless, ancient, and yet simple power erupted from within the belly of the Crimson Flame Dragon. It turned into a gray beam of light that shot out from within the flame dragon.

Lin Ming had poured the Heavenly Demon martial intent into his spear attack, hiding the blooming blood red lotus. With the grandmist space fused into his spear, he thrust out, a strike to annihilate all Laws!

Whether it was the first three level Concepts of the Fire Laws or the fourth level Concept, whether or not Crimson Strifecloud’s true essence had a spirituality of its own, in the face of the all-annihilating grandmist space, everything would come under tremendous suppression.

This move could not be fully used – after all, it was related to Empyrean Primordius. Although he had disguised it as a type of suppressive force field, if there really were a character that had managed to come into contact with Empyrean Primordius, there was a chance that they would recognize Lin Ming’s attack styles!

A martial intent type of skill could not be stolen away by others. But, Lin Ming might be forced into revealing the process of how he obtained this martial intent. If that happened, there would be endless trouble awaiting him.

Within the spear, the energy of the Heavenly Demon martial intent erupted outwards along with the dark gold battle spirit. The Crimson Flame Dragon howled miserably, then, it was suddenly sliced in half from the center!

“Mm!?” Crimson Strifecloud’s eyes shot open. “You tore apart my Crimson Flame Dragon? How can you possibly possess such great strength!?”

Through their battle so far, Crimson Strifecloud had gained an approximate understanding of Lin Ming’s strength. Blue Lotus Flame Dance was already Lin Ming’s strongest move. When it was fused with the Phoenix Blood Spear’s attack yet again, that had become Lin Ming’s greatest attack so far. But even such an attack would not be able to tear apart the Crimson Flame Dragon!

Yet now, the Crimson Flame Dragon had been torn asunder!

“What is going on!? Is that a force field!? Lin Ming’s strength was increased by such a force field and at the same time this force field suppressed my strength!? At just a seventh stage Life Destruction cultivation, Lin Ming was able to comprehend such an aberrant force field!!?”

These thoughts instantly cut through Crimson Strifecloud’s Laws. A force field ability was rare. A Law type force field like the Blue Lotus Domain was a bit rarer, and a martial intent force field was even rarer than that. Normally, anyone that could comprehend just a single force field, or even multiple force fields, were extreme geniuses!

This force field that Lin Ming displayed seemed like a martial intent force field but it also seemed like a Law force field. Crimson Strifecloud was simply unable to see through it. This wasn’t strange. This was because while Law force fields were similar when a martial artist comprehended them, martial intent force fields were different. Martial intent force fields were developed based on a martial artist’s cultivation method, true essence, physical characteristics, and countless other constantly shifting variables. There was simply no single standard to identify them. A martial intent force field was similar to a martial artist’s thumbprint, or the unique composition of their very being; every one was different, thus it was normal to not recognize it!

A battle between masters was filled with changes. Before Crimson Strifecloud was able to understand exactly what happened, Lin Ming had already rushed in front of him!

“Phoenix bloodline, combust!”

In that moment, golden light burst out from the entirety of Lin Ming’s body. Crimson Strifecloud’s Scorching Blood bloodline could transform the body into a Scorching Blood Battle Body. Of course, the Ancient Phoenix bloodline also had a corresponding state of erupting energy. And that was to burn the blood of the Ancient Phoenix!

When Lin Ming crossed the seventh stage of Life Destruction, he had used an immense amount of precious Ancient Phoenix blood. Now, this was his first time completely combusting his phoenix bloodline!

The stronger one’s Ancient Phoenix bloodline was, the greater the burden combustion would place on the body. When a martial artist with a perfect Ancient Phoenix Bloodline combusted their blood, they would only do so with one ten thousandth of their bloodline. This already produced a titanic level of power. But now, Lin Ming had fully combusted all of the phoenix blood within him, without leaving the least bit behind!

After entering the Illusionary God Combat Array, Lin Ming had saved his strength and true essence. All of it was done so that he could completely erupt with his strength at the crucial moment!

By relying on the support of the Gate of Healing and also relying on his deep and solid foundation, Lin Ming forcefully withstood combusting the equivalent of 70 drops of phoenix heart blood. His strength suddenly multiplied to an extent even greater than Crimson Strifecloud’s Scorching Blood Battle Body!

As the branch palace disciples saw Lin Ming’s entire body burning in an inferno of flames, and a dark golden light radiating from all over him, all of them cried out in alarm and shock!

“Lin Ming has burnt all of the Ancient Phoenix blood within his body!”

“Heavens! He absorbed so much phoenix blood when he crossed Life Destruction, and yet he’s ignited it all!”

“I thought that Junior-apprentice Brother Lin would be swallowed up and eaten by that Crimson Flame Dragon Fire Elemental fused with the Concept of Manifestation, but he actually managed to break through the prison of that Fire Elemental and rush out!”

All of the disciples present held their breath, watching with helpless eyes as Lin Ming shot forwards like a beam of light, hurtling towards Crimson Strifecloud like a falling meteor!

Blue Lotus Flame Dance!

Lin Ming gave a loud shot and all of his true essence poured into the Phoenix Blood Spear. A blue lotus 10 times larger than the last shot out, and on top of this blue lotus was a dark gold phoenix phantom!

The dark gold phoenix within Lin Ming’s body had fused together with the Blue Lotus Flame Dance!

“Explode!”

In that moment, time seemed to come to a standstill. The blue lotus exploded and an inexhaustible gold light flooded through the entire world of the Illusionary God Combat Array!

Facing such an attack, Crimson Strifecloud’s pupils shrank. He fiercely cut down with his sword!

Boom!

Crimson Strifecloud’s body shook and he was sent soaring backwards. As his body flew through the air, blood gushed out from the shattered scales on his chest, staining his body. Blood also leaked out from the corners of his lips.

As for Lin Ming, he wasn’t much better off!

Although he didn’t vomit blood, his face was still paper white. In that strike just now he had burnt all of his Ancient Phoenix blood so he was able to rush forth with unstoppable momentum and gain the advantage. But before then, Lin Ming had been swallowed up into the stomach of the Crimson Flame Dragon. And when Crimson Strifecloud had caused fire origin energy to explode within, this had injured Lin Ming, causing all the blood within his body to tumble around, and also forcing him to expend a massive amount of true essence.

This battle between two great masters was extremely intense!

“Crimson Strifecloud, son of a World King, the current Crimson Dragon Envoy, he… he was injured by Lin Ming!”

Several disciples cried out in shock. With Lin Ming’s seventh stage Life Destruction cultivation and his Concept of Fire that was an entire boundary lower, he had managed to injure the eighth stage Life Destruction Crimson Strifecloud. This achievement was enough to ring out for all of eternity!

“Lin Ming…” On Charming Phoenix Palace’s side, Yan Littlemoon’s two fists were clutched tightly together. Her lips slowly moved.

“Maybe… just maybe… Lin Ming can win!”

Chapter 1049 – Supreme Dragon Bone

Was there a Divine Dragon here?

That was impossible!

Dragon One’s eyes widened. The majesty and absolute dignity contained in this echoing roar could not be wrong! As this sound fell into his ears, it even caused a faint trace of awe and reverence to appear in his heart. These were the most ancient memories of his bloodline resonating with this roar.

Although Dragon One had the perfect dragon race bloodline, this bloodline had been transplanted into his body after birth. And, the so-called ‘perfect dragon race bloodline’ only meant that half of his blood was dragon blood. Even then, the quality was actually relatively low.

In front of a true Divine Dragon, the blood within his body would give birth to fear and awe, as if his entire being were worshipping the ancestral gods.

“That is a dragon’s cry, there can be no mistake! How could this be!? Although the God Beast Mystic Realm is said to have once had God Beasts, that is a matter from countless hundreds of millions of years ago. The Laws of this universe have already collapsed, turning this place into a completely different space, and with the new Laws that followed after, it became impossible for any God Beast to be born in these lands ever again.”

“It shouldn’t be a God Beast, but…”

Just as Dragon One was alarmed, he suddenly saw a blue beam of light shoot up into the sky. The dragon’s roar became even more clarion!

At this time, a massive phantom appeared in the sky, tens of thousands of feet long. The incomparably pure energy of the mystic realm constantly transformed, gathering together! As it gathered, countless bolts of thunder formed in the sky, chopping straight down!

This was thunder tribulation. When a mystic realm demon was evolving into an Asura King, it needed to cross thunder tribulation!

Dragon One looked up. That massive phantom in the air had been manifested by the Asura King. And, what left Dragon One incomparably shocked was that this great phantom had clearly evolved into a dragon-like shape!

There was a dragon head, dragon horn, even a dragon body!

This mystic realm demon was actually manifesting into a dragon in the skies!?!?

Of course, it was not a True Dragon, but there was clearly the aura of a dragon coming from its body. That dragon roar was clearly emitted by this creature!

“How can this be?”

It wasn’t just Dragon One, but everyone from the Ancient Dragon Clan was stricken! They completely did not understand what was happening!

At this time, within the countless arcs of lightning in the far off distant sky, there was a group of shadows that were speaking to each other in some strange language. And, in the center of these shadows was someone that looked like a naked man with long hair hanging to his knees.

This man’s face constantly changed. Sometimes he was handsome and heroic, sometimes he was grim and fierce, sometimes he was ordinary and common, and sometimes he was ugly and grotesque. There were even times when he appeared to be like a beautiful woman or a wild beast.

This was the Asura King that was undergoing demonic tribulation. It already had an essential difference from ordinary mystic realm demons. It had condensed a body of flesh and blood, and this body seemed no different from that of a human. In fact, its stature and form were even more perfect and handsome. However, its arms and ankles were actually covered with blue scales. They seemed like… dragon scales!

A mystic realm demon was a life form of energy, a being with no physical body. However, if it had the chance to swallow up a massive amount of life force and blood energy then it could condense its own mortal body.

“Great King, those lowly and pathetic beings have already come. They are spying on you!” A vague and blurry voice sounded out from beside the man, in words that martial artists of the Divine Realm would not be able to understand.

“Of course I know, hehe… these beings from the outside world wish to take advantage of my weakest point as I undergo tribulation and kill me! But, what they don’t know is that I have already long discovered them and am still crossing tribulation to draw them near!

“These beings actually think as if they are the infallible masters of this mystic realm. Every period of time they will send people here to plunder our wealth and hunt down my Hallowed Demon race! In their eyes, we are nothing but prey! How ridiculous! But what they do not know is that my Hallowed Demon race is under the care and holy protection of the Heavenly Demon God! After constantly developing for hundreds of millions of years, our wisdom and strength have already improved beyond their reckoning. We are no longer unconsciously wandering around like before! Since they think of us as prey, we also treat them as tasty food. During my tribulation I just happen to lack some flesh and life force. I will make them come to me and help me complete my final step!

“Send out the orders. Hold the troops, do not have them move! They will take advantage of the last moment of my tribulation to begin their attack against me. Stay at the periphery and when that happens, block off the entire surrounding area of a hundred miles and completely kill all of them! All of them shall become my nutrition!”

As the Asura King spoke, it emitted a dreadful demonic energy that blotted out the heavens. And not only that, but there was even the aura of a dragon emitting from him!

“Yes, Great King.”

The several shadows respectfully said. They held incomparable admiration towards the Asura King, as if it were no different from their one and only god.

The Asura King’s aura became increasingly intense. Endless bolts of thunder fell down, setting the swamp underneath the Asura King into a blazing fire. Mud evaporated, burnt, and then even heated up into molten magma before evaporating once again!

This process happened extremely fast. In just the blink of an eye, a massive stretch of the black swamp had disappeared!

And in the distance, Dragon One, who had been lying unmoving, actually frowned. He felt signs that there was something wrong about this!

Before he came to the God Beast Mystic Realm he had only completely familiarized himself with the ‘God Beast Mystic Realm Compendium’. And, the Ancient Dragon Clan’s version of the ‘God Beast Mystic Realm Compendium’ was far more comprehensive than the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s. According to the records left behind, an Asura King of the mystic realm demons shouldn’t be so powerful.

This sort of thunder tribulation was too terrifying. And within this tribulation the Asura King was adamantly withstanding it, without seeming as if it were having any troubles.

Dragon One had a very bad feeling!

Although Dragon One knew that there was a massive lucky chance placed in front of him, he was still an extremely cautious person. For his talent and cultivation to reach such a degree, he understood his own destiny to an extent and was able to sense when impending catastrophes were around the corner.

He had an extremely tough life. Normally when he was exploring a mystic realm and he was close to death’s door at every moment, he would still be able to emerge alive, and moreover he would even be able to obtain great benefits.

And now, as Dragon One saw that the situation in front of him surpassed his every expectation, he had the idea of wholeheartedly retreating. To an extreme talent, if a lucky chance was placed in front of them, they had to go all out to obtain it even if the chances of survival were slimmer than a hair.

But, sometimes, just sometimes, in a situation where one couldn’t grasp the circumstances and variables involved, one would need to give up. And giving up also took enormous determination.

But just as Dragon One was thinking about whether to retreat, he saw another scene in front of him, one that caused his body to tremble and his eyes to shrink to dots before bursting out with a blinding light!

As the black swamp was evaporated by the bolts of thunder, a massive pit appeared in the ground. And, Dragon One also saw something that wasn’t visible before.

In this pit, there was actually a massive bone that was a thousand feet long. This bone was whiter than jade, and the top was narrow and seamless like a divine sword, piercing through the endless heavens!

This bone looked like a fragment of an unimaginably massive skeleton. Perhaps it was part of a rib, or perhaps it was part of a femur. But no matter what it was, this bone had an unbelievable number of complex runes scattered all over it. There were large runes like buckets and small runes like grains of rice. They were endless!

Every rune contained the Laws of this world!

From this fragment of bone, an indescribably great pressure surged outwards. This pressure was unfathomably profound and also mixed together with an overwhelmingly pure yang energy. Even though he was hundreds of miles away, he could still feel the incomparably pure baptism of energy and even feel the power of the boundless vibrant ancient Laws!

“This… this is…” Dragon One’s voice quivered. Although he had never seen one before, he knew that he wasn’t wrong. This fragment of bone in front of him was…

“A supreme dragon bone!”

Buried beneath the black swamp of the God Beast Mystic Realm there was actually a piece of dragon bone! A 1000 foot long dragon bone!

What sort of concept was a 1000 foot long dragon bone?

One just needed to think of the value of dragon marrow blood to understand this. Dragon blood and phoenix blood were of similar degrees of preciousness. Ordinary dragon blood was naturally the least valuable. Above that was dragon heart blood, dragon horn blood, dragon marrow blood, reverse scale blood, and so forth.

Dragon marrow blood was similar to phoenix marrow blood in terms of value. When Lin Ming had broken through to the seventh level of the Hells of Flame, besides the phoenix blood essence which he hadn’t yet managed to reach the full standards for, he only managed to obtain three drops of phoenix marrow blood. A single drop of phoenix marrow blood was enough to cause a Divine Lord powerhouse to struggle for it. As for 10 drops of phoenix marrow blood, that was enough for a Divine Lord powerhouse to go all out.

And this 1000 foot dragon bone was still complete, so there must be a massive amount of marrow inside. Just how much dragon marrow blood must there be within it?

And that was only the dragon marrow blood. The value of the dragon bone itself wasn’t even mentioned.

In fact, the dragon bone was even more valuable than the dragon marrow blood within it!

This was because no matter which one of the four God Beast Clans it was, the clansmen only transplanted the bloodline of the God Beasts. This method would only transform their bloodline. As for their skin, flesh, bones, and tendons, those actually couldn’t be transformed.

This was because they didn’t have the materials to do so!

If Dragon One could obtain this piece of dragon bone and fuse it into his body, the advantages couldn’t even be calculated!

Not only would the strength of his bloodline rise, but all of his bones would become near-indestructible because they would have fused together with the dragon bone. His physical strength and defensive ability would rise to a whole new level.

At this moment, Dragon One turned into a zealot. Desire flashed in his eyes, an intensity of emotion he had never felt in his life before!

If it was said that he had high hopes of becoming a Holy Lord in the future, then after obtaining this dragon bone he would be foreordained to reach the late Holy Lord realm or even the peak Holy Lord realm. Perhaps if he stumbled into more lucky chances in the future, he might even have a chance of becoming a World King!

At that time he would become another World King of the Ancient Dragon Clan. He would be one of the top three existences to ever appear in the last 100 million history of the Ancient Dragon Clan!

With such an impossibly great lucky chance in front of him, if he didn’t chase after it with everything he had just because of some worries, then he wouldn’t be Dragon One.

It wasn’t just Dragon One, but the other Ancient Dragon Clan disciples also felt their blood boiling over with longing. Dragon One would assuredly obtain most of the benefits, but they too could share in some of the soup. After all, this dragon bone was 1000 feet long. It was natural that some part of it would be divided to them. This was a heavenly treasure that even a World King powerhouse would go crazy over. Even if they were given a tiny imperceptible amount, it would be more than enough for them to soar in the future.

“Junior-apprentice brothers and sisters, form the formation, we’re going in together!”

Dragon One shook with excitement, but his eyes were still terrifying calm. This was the most important moment of his life!

In the skies, the phantom formed by the Asura King had reached 100,000 feet long. A terrifying aura showered down, enveloping the entire world. Without a doubt, this piece of dragon bone had been obtained by this Asura King that was currently crossing its demonic tribulation. It must have swallowed up the blood energy and pure yang energy of the dragon bone, thus developing some dragon-like characteristics.

Because of this Asura King, the dragon bone must have lost a great deal of its energy essence. However, this didn’t matter. If they could slay this Asura King and refine it, they could equally make up for the losses.

Chapter 1055 – Opportunity

In the sky, the longer the fight continued, the more vicious it became. At this time, it could only be described as absolutely frigid.

Whether it was the mystic realm demons or the disciples of the four God Beast Clans, all of them were betting their lives and desperately fighting!

Dragon One’s face was pale. As for the other Dragon Clan disciples, all of them had consumed a massive amount of energy. If this battle ended, even if they lived, if they didn’t obtain the supreme dragon bone then they would only live for another 10,000-20,000 years.

To a genius, this was undoubtedly fatal.

Thus, they had to win!

Bang!

Another crazy collision occurred. A dozen Ancient Dragon Clan disciples felt their bodies shake and a sweet coppery taste touch the back of their throats. They immediately vomited a mouthful of blood! And, the only seventh stage Life Destruction disciple paled, his lips shivering. He had finally reached his limits.

The Ancient Dragon Clan’s disciples were mostly at the eighth or ninth stage of Life Destruction; the seventh stage disciple was the lowest amongst them. This disciple also didn’t have heaven-defying talent like Lin Ming, thus his combat strength was limited. Within such a crazy battle, he found it extremely difficult to continue.

Let alone him, even Dragon One felt the blood tumbling within his body. Blue veins stuck out on his forehead – he too was nearing his limit. Out of everyone present, he had the highest talent and the highest cultivation. He was also the strongest one here; he could instantly slaughter any of the seventh or eighth stage Life Destruction geniuses present.

But because he was strong, the burden he had to bear was far greater. He was the eye of the 36 Astral Heaven Formation, and a quarter to a third of the array formation was shouldered by him alone!

However, at this time, the Asura King wasn’t much better off.

The demonic tribulation continued to fall down without end. If the Asura King hadn’t absorbed the supreme dragon bone’s essence energy and blood vitality, it would have died long ago.

“Damnit! This bunch of mousies has completely angered me!”

The Asura King’s entire right arm was wet with blood. After swallowing up a massive amount of human martial artists’ flesh and blood, and also the dragon marrow within the supreme dragon bone, the Asura King had already formed a physical body. It had organs, meridians, and even acupoints. If it was wounded then it would also bleed.

“Demon One, return to me and help me kill off these Dragon Clan disciples! Demon Two, Demon Three, burn away your cultivation and slaughter everyone else as soon as possible!”

As the Asura King saw that the other three clans had the idea of retreating but were struggling to do so, it issued this order.

Now, the greatest threat to it was the Ancient Dragon Clan’s disciples.

Woosh!

Demon One turned into a shadow that flew back towards the Asura King’s side. As for the other two demons, the blue light within them suddenly blazed out; they were clearly about to go all out.

Underneath the mind control of the Asura King, they obeyed his orders to the letter.

………….

At this time, underneath the supreme dragon bone, Lin Ming was completely buried in the black mud of the swamp. He steadily observed the brutal battle happening in the skies!

Because he was afraid that he would be found, he didn’t dare to reveal his sense. He only rose up high enough to expose his eyes, hidden beneath a cluster of dead mushrooms. His field of vision was limited and what he made out was also very vague. But, he could tell from the surges of origin energy how the power of space nearby trembled, and how the mystic realm demons constantly exploded into bursts of energy flows, and that the battle was reaching a calamitous state.

At this time, there was nothing he could do.

He thought of using an illusory magic array to recreate the image of the supreme dragon bone and then steal it away. But, this sort of array was difficult to lay down in such a situation and also easy to see through. Moreover, the Asura King had likely left behind a wisp of its sense on the supreme dragon bone. As long as the Asura King didn’t die, then let alone taking it away, the Asura King would likely know if Lin Ming even touched it!

Lin Ming could only wait for the best opportunity to arrive.

This was also a great test of Lin Ming’s mentality. He was in an extremely dangerous situation at the moment. As soon as he was discovered, the only thing waiting for him was death.

Like this, time slowly passed!

Lin Ming’s palms became wet with sweat. This sweat couldn’t even drip down before it was instantly decomposed by the power of the grandmist space, turning into an imperceptibly faint wisp that gathered into the elementary form of grandmist energy.

Lin Ming’s nerves were as taut as steel wire. Although he hadn’t done anything, this was still no easier than a life or death battle!

The only thing he could feel fortunate about was that there were no mystic realm demons around the supreme dragon bone. This allowed Lin Ming to concentrate his entire mind, waiting for that split second when he could grasp the opportunity.

“Ah!”

On the side of the three great clans, two Ancient Phoenix Clan disciples, because of Demon Two and Demon Three’s all-out attack, finally weren’t able to persist any longer. They emitted pitiful cries and exploded into fogs of blood that were then cleanly eaten up by the massive number of mystic realm demons. These mystic realm demons were like starving wolves. Wherever they went, nothing was left remaining.

As these disciples died, a massive gap appeared in the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s array formation. Before this, Xiao Ping was able to rely on his extraordinary strength to continue on, but he too had reached his limit now. He could no longer continue shouldering the array formation; three mystic realm demons rushed in from the array formation’s gap.

And their goal was the closest disciple, Huang Tidemark! Now, in the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s 100 Bird Burning Sun Formation, there were only five people left living. And the one with the weakest cultivation amongst them was Huang Tidemark! And now, he had become the main target of the mystic realm demons. These three mystic realm demons that charged towards him each had a cultivation above 8000 years!

“No!”

Huang Tidemark cried out in panic, his face as pale as paper. A cold fear shot up his back and into the heavens. Now that he truly faced death, a deep fear and despair appeared in the deepest depths of his soul. He didn’t want to die. He didn’t want to die!

“Senior-apprentice Brother Xiao, save me!”

Huang Tidemark miserably cried out. But, Xiao Ping seemed as if he didn’t hear Huang Tidemark’s cries. Xiao Ping’s eyes quickly glanced over at Huang Tidemark and instantly judged his situation. Three mystic realm demons, each with an 8000 year cultivation, were attacking him from a pincer angle; as Xiao Ping saw these, he immediately judged Huang Tidemark to death!

If Xiao Ping was in his top state then he could easily block the three mystic realm demons and save Huang Tidemark. But now, he had nearly spent all of his strength and he was resisting the attacks of a dozen mystic realm demons around him. At this time, he could barely manage himself, so how could he possibly help others?

“When Huang Tidemark blows up, I will use that opportunity to escape!”

Xiao Ping callously thought. Not only was he not planning on saving Huang Tidemark, but he was instead planning to take advantage of the moment when Huang Tidemark blew up and attracted a massive amount of mystic realm demons to escape. After all, once Huang Tidemark died, their Ancient Phoenix Clan would only have four people to form an array formation. With just four people, how could an array formation even be formed?

All that mattered was escape!

This was what the heart of man was like. Xiao Ping was the leader of the Ancient Phoenix Clan group that had come here and was also given the task of protecting the other disciples. He would easily help a fellow disciple out when it didn’t harm his own interests, but when something concerned his own life, he gave priority to himself first and foremost. All others could be sacrificed for his survival.

“No! No! No! Senior apprentice-Brother Xiao…!”

At this time, over 10 mystic realm demons dove into Huang Tidemark. His organs, his spiritual sea, all of it was filled with mystic realm demons!

His marrow was eaten, his organs were chewed up, his blood was swallowed, and even his spiritual sea was about to tear apart. This agonizing pain came from all directions, causing his face to twist. His cries became unbearably shrill.

He thrust out a hand towards Xiao Ping’s direction, his eyes full of hatred, as if he wanted to drag Xiao Ping into hell with him.

Why won’t you save me?

Huang Tidemark wanted to shout out. But, he could no longer voice words.

Peng!

Underneath the callous and indifferent vision of Xiao Ping, both of Huang Tidemark’s eyeballs bulged out from his head before bursting open! Blood gushed out of his head. His chest and stomach completely blew up with flesh and blood flying in all directions! Then, his last thoughts were of countless mystic realm demons feeding on him before his consciousness faded away…

And in the moment when Huang Tidemark died, when a massive number of mystic realm demons were attracted over to that direction, Xiao Ping launched his movement technique without any words and raced away!

He no longer cared about managing the group. The group’s combat strength had already become extremely feeble. Now, he could only count on his own strength and the little bit of combat efficiency he had left. Everyone else would simply be a burden on him.

The group had lost all use to him. Instead, the situation would cause far more mystic realm demons to attack them. In this case, Xiao Ping decided to run away by himself. As for the ones left behind, they could stay there and hold down the mystic realm demons for him.

“Xiao Ping!”

“Senior-apprentice Brother, you!!”

As the other Ancient Phoenix Clan disciples saw Xiao Ping run away by himself, they were all stunned for a moment before immediately frothing with resentment and despair. Without Xiao Ping here, it would be nearly impossible for them to resist this onslaught!

“Run! We all have to run away!”

Without their main pillar of support, the other disciples all panicked and began to disperse to escape. But, scattering also meant dying faster.

“Jejejeje! You will all die!” Demon Two screeched out in a coarse voice, also speaking in an extremely crude version of the Divine Realm language. Demon Two began to turn even crazier as it rushed over to the remaining disciples…

……………

“51… 50… 49…”

With his body buried in the swamp mud, Lin Ming began to silently count the dwindling number of disciples.

Of the disciples of the three clans that didn’t come from their respective headquarters, Lin Ming hadn’t noticed if they had died or successfully ran away. But, of the remaining disciples that could form array formations, only 49 were left over. Of these 49, the Ancient Dragon Clan occupied 36 of these spots. In other words, the other three clans only had 13 disciples left. Each clan now had less than five people on average!

And of these remaining people, many of them were probably on the brink of disaster. Chances were that at least half of them would die here. The savageness of this fight could be imagined!

“Really, birds die for food and men die for wealth. These people all had bright futures ahead of them. Although it was impossible for most of them to think of reaching the Holy Lord realm, they could still reach the Divine Lord realm and have 100,000 years of life. But now, they have nothing left, not even their bodies.”

Lin Ming sighed. He knew that this present situation occurred because the four God Beast Clans had underestimated the strength of the Asura King. After all, the only information recorded in the ‘God Beast Mystic Realm Compendium’ was that the Asura King would be at its weakest state after crossing tribulation, and thus one could kill it then. And, in the history of the God Beast Clans, there had indeed been disciples that had killed Asura Kings, much less that there was also the added temptation of the supreme dragon bone now.

But, this Asura King was not an ordinary Asura King. It was no different from a spider that had cast out a web, waiting for prey to wander into their own doom.

And then, because of everyone that had arrived and the dispute over the division of the supreme dragon bone, Dragon One had suddenly launched an attack, involving everyone in a massive life or death battle. This was why so many casualties had appeared.

As these thoughts flashed through Lin Ming’s mind, in the sky, some of the Celestial Dragon Runes beneath the feet of the Dragon Clan’s 36 disciples suddenly disintegrated. The entire array wheel started to collapse!

As the entire array wheel ruptured, a total of 10 disciples vomited a mouthful of blood, their bodies flying away!

“Mm?” Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. The Ancient Dragon Clan’s array formation had finally been broken!

Chapter 1057 – Crazy Dragon One

After Yan Littlemoon was received into Lin Ming’s Extreme Violet Ring, it felt as if every moment inside was as long as an eternity. This was because in the sealed space of the Extreme Violet Ring, she had no idea what was happening outside. All she knew was that in the moment when she was sucked into the Extreme Violet Ring, there had been 100,000 mystic realm demons surging towards her!

She could imagine just how intense and tragic such a battle would be!

Yan Littlemoon was well aware of her own abilities. If she was exposed to such a gruesome battlefield, there was only a single fate that awaited her.

That was to be eaten up without a skeleton, without even the slightest pieces left for a burial. And in that key moment, she had been taken in by Lin Ming and placed into his Extreme Violet Ring. But, this also meant that Lin Ming would have to shoulder the entire following battle himself!

Yan Littlemoon knew that Lin Ming was far stronger than she was, to a ridiculous degree. But in such a brutal battle, she didn’t have full confidence that Lin Ming would be able to safely escape.

All she could do was wait as time slowly passed in the minor dimension. Soon, an hour passed and there still wasn’t any news from outside of the Extreme Violet Ring. Yan Littlemoon began to feel a bit anxious.

She was afraid that Lin Ming would be severely wounded or even die in the chaos. She was afraid that at any moment, the Extreme Violet Ring would be destroyed and then countless mystic realm demons would rush in!

Although the scenery within the Extreme Violet Ring was beautiful to behold, Yan Littlemoon still felt like she was on pins and needles the entire time. There was nothing she could do now. It was also impossible for her to leave. Otherwise, she might add to the chaos if Lin Ming was in some critical moment.

She had been hoping that Lin Ming would quickly arrive, but she never expected that after some time, when there was finally a tiny spatial fluctuation above her, what appeared was not Lin Ming but rather a divine bone!

This 1000 foot divine bone was like a faintly blue tinted holy sword. It stood straight and tall within the Extreme Violet Ring, emitting an incomparably vast pressure.

There were countless complex and mystical runes on top of the dragon bone, each one symbolizing the Heavenly Dao itself. Every rune was 10 times more profound than the 100 Foot Royal Skyseal in Totem Tower, or even 100 times more profound! It was even no worse that the Huo Family’s ultimate treasure, the Sacred Flame Testament!

But, there were nine blocks of the Sacred Flame Testament and each one wasn’t too big. It was impossible to compare that to the 1000 foot dragon bone in front of her!

“Lin Ming, he… he…” Yan Littlemoon gulped over and over again. Her watery eyes filled with a fantastical light as if she couldn’t believe her own sense.

She certainly recognized this divine bone. It was the Asura King’s treasure and also what it relied on to evolve into an Asura King. It was the object that the Ancient Dragon Clan’s 36 disciples and the numerous disciples of the other three clans had fought for with their lives on the line.

But now, it was actually obtained by Lin Ming?

Moreover…

It was his alone!

How was this possible!? Just how had he obtained the dragon bone!?

Did he wrest it away by force?

No matter how talented Lin Ming was, he was still limited by his cultivation. With his seventh stage Life Destruction cultivation, he didn’t even have the ability to escape in front of someone like Dragon One. Moreover, there was also Jiang Bai, Argent Gale, and many other disciples that were able to gather into array formations together. So how could this have been possible!?

Was it with strategy?

No matter how smart Lin Ming was, the others weren’t idiots. On the other hand, all those chosen prides of heaven were cruel and ruthless individuals of their generation. Their mentality and calculations were all extremely cutthroat and broad. As for the Asura King, that was a monster that had lived for 100,000 years. This should have been impossible!

All sorts of thoughts flashed through Yan Littlemoon’s mind, but she still couldn’t figure out anything. She thought that it would have already been good if Lin Ming managed to escape with his life intact, but not only was he still alive, he had even managed to pick up the largest peach from the tree.

Yan Littlemoon fervently wished to know what was occurring outside. But, she also knew that even if Lin Ming had managed to obtain the dragon bone for now, there would still be a battle following this. If she rushed out randomly, she would only bring hurt to Lin Ming.

Yan Littlemoon bit her lips. She looked at the supreme dragon bone, unable to move.

She couldn’t help but walk over and trace her fingers across the surface of the divine bone. The rough texture was filled with a boundless and vigorous aura, making her feel an awe from deep within her soul.

This was the bone of a God Beast, one of the most precious treasures of the world!

Yan Littlemoon certainly didn’t dare to absorb the dragon bone. But, she also couldn’t bear to stand around and do nothing. She sat down and began to meditate on the Law runes carved onto the dragon bone. Every tiny bit of strength she could gain meant her chances of living through this were that much higher.

As Yan Littlemoon was meditating on the Laws, Lin Ming was facing a major life or death crisis!

He discovered that he had underestimated the Asura King. Even after such a savage and violent battle, it still had strength remaining to chase after him!

“Shatter!”

The Asura King thrust out its palm and the ground beneath the swamp collapsed. The Asura King chased straight down!

And behind the Asura King were the 16 remaining disciples of the Ancient Dragon Clan. In that savage battle just now, they had lost over half of their fellow disciples. Now, their strength was far from what it used to be.

At this time, Dragon One’s eyes were blood red. He never imagined that in their frigid battle with the Asura King that shook the heavens and earth, there would be someone sitting on the sidelines waiting to profit from their strife!

For this supreme dragon bone, he had burnt 20% of his blood essence and lost several tens of thousands of years of his life. He had consumed a massive amount of precious pills and now even had to bear the infamy of being a cruel demon that killed his own fellow clan disciples. Yet, all of his efforts had been made a gift to someone else!

How could he not loathe this!?

“Just who is it!? Who dared to plot against me!?” Dragon One was like a wild and injured animal. He knew that this mysterious person was not Xiao Ping, Jiang Bai, or Argent Gale!

For someone to quietly sneak in even through a swarm of 100,000 mystic realm demons, and also approach the supreme dragon bone and wait there for so much time, this person had to be a top master!

There was even a chance that this other party wasn’t human. After all, this was the God Beast Mystic Realm. There could be some unknown existence that had been eyeing the Asura King’s supreme dragon bone and had finally found their chance to take it.

One couldn’t blame Dragon One for thinking this. Lin Ming had used the grandmist space to conceal his aura, and in addition to the chaotic battle, even if Dragon One’s cultivation had been 10 times higher, he still wouldn’t have noticed Lin Ming’s aura. He wasn’t even able to ascertain if Lin Ming was human.

In addition, Dragon One didn’t know that Lin Ming’s combat strength was equal to that of a top extreme genius at the peak early Divine Sea realm. Moreover, in terms of lethality to the mystic realm demons, with his grandmist space and gold battle spirit combined together, Lin Ming surpassed even middle Divine Sea martial artists like Jiang Bai and Xiao Ping.

And, most importantly, he had used the grandmist space to conceal his aura as he moved underground. He hadn’t been detected by any mystic realm demons, thus he hadn’t encountered many of them at all.

In this situation where Dragon One had completely miscalculated Lin Ming’s combat efficiency, even if his imagination was 10 times richer, he still wouldn’t think that someone like Lin Ming would be able to snatch away the supreme dragon bone.

Now all he felt was a blazing fury in his heart, as well as the utter humiliation of being played for a fool!

No matter what, he still could not give up on this supreme dragon bone!

Although he knew the chances of defeating that unknown existence as well as the Asura King were incomparably slim, this was still a struggle between three parties after all. The situation was extremely complex and it was possible he could profit from the chaos. But, if he didn’t chase after them then there really would be no hope at all.

“There are 16 of us left, we can still form the 16 Celestial Dragon Formation. Although it is inferior to the 36 Astral Heaven Formation, we can still fight. Moreover, the disciples that have died were all at the ninth stage of Life Destruction and below. The greater portion of our fighting strength still remains. Swallow down your Nine Revolving Dragon Pills and let’s chase after them!”

Dragon One issued an order. But, among the 16 Dragon Clan disciples, there were many of them that had thoughts of retreating. They felt that Dragon One was a psychotic madman that had fallen over the edge.

After burning their blood essence, they weren’t even at 10-20% of their peak strength. They were in an extremely miserable state!

Even if they swallowed down the Nine Revolving Dragon Pills that were supposed to be left for saving their lives, they could only restore 40% of their combat strength or so. Moreover, they wouldn’t have enough time to absorb it and would waste most of the recovery efficacy.

But the key point of all this was even if they did all that, would they even still be able to obtain the supreme dragon bone?

With a captain like Dragon One, who was able to resort to any method to compete for the dragon bone, nobody felt safe. It had to be known that Dragon One had burnt all the blood essence of 10 disciples that were about to die, and he had done so without the least bit of hesitation.

What if they were the next ones to die?

A martial artist had to pursue lucky chances, even risking their life to do so. But, after weighing the pros and cons, and knowing that their chances of survival were slim and their chances of obtaining the dragon bone were even worse, it was understandable if they decided to give up.

As long as there was life there was hope. They would be able to struggle for more lucky chances in the future…

As long as they were alive.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Dragon One, I won’t go!”

“I won’t go either…”

Several Divine Sea martial artists declared, not fearing Dragon One. As for those ninth stage Life Destruction martial artists, although they feared Dragon One, their eyes were dodgy and evasive, obviously not intending to follow him.

“Mm!? You!!”

Dragon One’s eyes turned cold. At this time, he knew that his prestige had completely collapsed and these disciples that usually feared him and followed his orders had formed a united front against him. Like this, it was impossible for him to command these disciples around any longer. And most importantly, he no longer had time to establish his strength again.

“Fine! Then don’t regret your choices!”

Dragon One waved his hand and picked up the corpses of the dead Ancient Dragon Clan disciples. Then, he swallowed two Nine Revolving Dragon Pills and flew straight down into the black swamp! At this point he could no longer afford to waste time, otherwise he would lose track of the Asura King and that unknown existence!

As the Ancient Dragon Clan disciples saw Dragon One receive the corpses of their fellow comrades, all of them had extremely ugly expressions. Even so, none of them said anything.

It was clear that Dragon One took their corpses to make use of their blood essence. After burning their blood essence he would launch his attack. This method would make it so that those dead disciples wouldn’t even have skeletons left over. This was truly a tragic and wretched way to die!

In front of the temptation of such great benefits, Dragon One had completely exposed his cruel and ferocious nature.

Although all of them were disgusted, none of them could stop him. They could only allow Dragon One to do as he wished.

The truth was that Dragon One’s sole strength was definitely not enough. It was impossible for him to compete with the Asura King, whose strength compared favorably to a Divine Transformation martial artist.

But, he also had to take into account what that unknown existence might do. Dragon One could hide on the sidelines and launch an attack at a critical moment, finally obtaining everything for himself.

This couldn’t be called anything but a crazy plan, and the chances of success were also low. But in Dragon One’s opinion, if this unknown existence could do it, then why couldn’t he?

He was truly unwilling to give up on this lucky chance. If he could succeed all by himself and take sole possession of the dragon bone, then he truly would have a chance of stepping onto the path of a World King in the future!

Woosh!

Dragon One’s body sank into the swamp. He restrained his aura and dove down. But, he only understood the Water Laws and not the Earth Laws, thus drilling down was extremely difficult. Luckily, the Asura King had led the way and blown up the swamp ground ahead of him. Like this, it was still possible for Dragon One to catch up to those people ahead of him.

Chapter 1078 – His Skin Is Not of Ordinary Thickness

In the past when Lin Ming absorbed the dragon marrow and the Asura King’s source energy, his body had reached the limit. It was impossible to eat heavenly materials without end; he would be unable to absorb them at some point. For the left over dragon bone, Lin Ming had to slowly fuse with it.

“The resources that Miss Mo left behind are divided into the body transformation system and the essence gathering system. The essence gathering system resources were collected at Carefree Island, and they are also what I need to break through to the ninth stage of Life Destruction,” Lin Ming thought out loud.

Because he dual cultivated in body and energy, his body was incomparably solid and durable. It was far harder for him to make breakthroughs in Life Destruction than an ordinary martial artist. As for breaking through to the ninth stage of Life Destruction, that was at least a hundred times more difficult than it would be for others!

If he were to fuse the supreme dragon bone as well as open another one of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates before attempting to cross Ninefall, the difficulty would rise to an unbelievable degree!

Ultimately, the rules of the universe had changed some inestimable period of time ago, and now those that chose to dual cultivate in body and energy could be said to be defying the will of the heavens. How could this be empty talk? In the past, there were even top geniuses that were far too confident in their own talent and recklessly chose to embark on this dangerous path, only to be trapped in the Life Destruction realm. Finally, they had no choice but to cripple and break up their body transformation cultivation and continue cultivating the essence gathering system.

To be like Mo Eversnow and have a half-step World King cultivation as well as being close to opening the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, that was simply a miracle among miracles.

The further one went in the body transformation system, the harder it was to cross into Ninefall. With Lin Ming’s current situation, once he opened the Gate of View, he’d have opened six of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, only missing the Gate of Life and the Gate of Death. As for the Gate of Life and the Gate of Death, they were called the true life and death threshold. The difficulty to open them was on a completely different level, and these two gates were much more powerful. They were each equal to half a large boundary in the body transformation system. If Lin Ming completely opened the first six gates, that was the same as completing a certain goal of the body transformation system; his bodily physique would experience a qualitative leap upwards, but at the same time it would also become far more difficult to break into the ninth stage of Life Destruction.

However, the more difficult it was to step into the ninth stage of Life Destruction, the greater the advantages would be. The body would be tempered much more thoroughly. Especially after fusing with the dragon bone; whether it was Lin Ming’s body transformation system or essence gathering system, it would hold incalculable advantages to him.

For Ninefall, Lin Ming would need to have the support of a terrifying amount of resources. Otherwise, it would be impossible for him to succeed.

In the end, the current Lin Ming was going against the heavens!

Lin  Ming submerged himself into the spirit spring in the rear courtyard and entered into a contemplative state. What he didn’t know was that at this time, in Carefree Palace, there was actually a special meeting being assembled because of him. Those people participating in this meeting were either inner court Elders, peak direct disciples, the Highest Elders of Carefree Palace, the several Vice Island Masters, and even the Island Master himself, Xiao Skywhite.

“Island Master Skywhite? Are you playing a joke on us? You want to take Carefree Island’s destiny stabilizing treasure, the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree and give it away to an outsider? The Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree is an incomparably supreme divine medicine! In this world, such a divine medicine is unique, singular!”

As Xiao Skywhite slowly laid out the reason for this meeting, the Council of Elders’ Great Elder Xiao Haogan asked this question, his eyes wide as if he didn’t dare to believe his own ears.

The Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree was Carefree Island’s most precious divine object, without anything else even coming close. It was a treasure used to stabilize Carefree Palace’s destiny. Moreover, the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree would produce ten fruits every 1000 years. These fruits would be plucked and made into wine using a special technique. This wine would be rewarded to the sect’s most outstanding disciples. The Ten Severing Fruit Wine was extremely valuable. Without them, there might have been disciples that would never have broken into the Divine Lord realm.

Not just that, but Splintersoul Mountain and the Occult Bone Clan were already joining forces to suppress Carefree Island. If they actually handed out the divine treasure they used to stabilize the destiny of their sect, wasn’t that the same as being told to roll over and die?

Xiao Skywhite frowned, not answering. But then, the Elders of the Council of Elders began to whisper among each other, all of them were panicked and confused and everything was in chaos. None of them could believe Xiao Skywhite’s decision!

As for the core disciples, they were even more appalled. In the future, to make further progress, they would have to rely on the Ten Severing Fruit Wine!

“Everyone quiet!” Xiao Skywhite shouted. His voice contained true essence that spread through everyone like a strong breeze, immediately silencing all the Elders and core disciples.

Once the entire grand hall was calmed down and silent, Xiao Skywhite slowly spoke, “It seems that all of you have forgotten. When the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree was planted 50,000 years ago, my father told me that it did not belong to my Carefree Island. Rather, it was placed here by a benefactor. There would be a day when this benefactor would return for it. Did you all forget this? For these last tens of thousands of years since the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree was planted, we have been able to pluck the Ten Severing Dao Fruits. This has even faintly helped to improve the destiny of our sect. In all these years, geniuses have poured forth from our sect and now our sect is only a step away from becoming a Holy Land. The reason for this is that we have received the graciousness of that person. Did you all think the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree would always remain planted on Carefree Island?”

As Xiao Skywhite spoke, everyone froze for a moment before remembering this. Indeed, they knew of this. It was just that the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree was planted at Carefree Island such a long time ago that they nearly forgot that this divine tree never belonged to Carefree Island to begin with.

“So what’s the meaning of this? That person has come back to take away the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree?”

The Great Elder’s thoughts stirred. He suddenly recalled the report relayed to him by a disciple responsible for the entrance examinations. An extremely talented young man with an eighth stage Life Destruction cultivation had entered Carefree Island to request an audience with Xiao Skywhite. He also called himself a distant relative. This was most likely the person!

“Is it the youth with the eighth stage of Life Destruction? Is he the descendant of that mysterious person from the past?”

Xiao Skywhite remained silent, quietly acquiescing.

Realization stirred up the Great Elder. “It’s true that the Ten Severing Dao Fruit is not ours, but it has already been planted at my Carefree Island for the last 50,000 years. Does he think he can just take it away because he wants to?”

“That’s right! We have helped store it for them for 50,000 years and yet they want to just take it away. Where is the justice in that!?”

Another Elder echoed in agreement. However, more Elders stayed quiet. Although they definitely didn’t want the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree to be taken away, their skin wasn’t so thick that they could raise their voices. Although they had helped ‘store’ the tree for 50,000 years, the truth was that they obtained massive benefits from it. For those benefits to now be suddenly taken away, they definitely didn’t want that to happen. Of course, this was also a completely natural matter.

To give a cup of rice was grace and to fight for a cup of rice was enmity. Once one obtained a benefit from others and was used to it, if that benefit disappeared, that kindness would turn to anger.

At this time, a purple-clothed youth asked, “Elders, may this disciple speak?”

The one who spoke was the top direct disciple. In truth, this purple-clothed youth’s status was even higher than a normal inner court Elder. It was only that he was a junior so by customs he wasn’t allowed to interrupt a meeting.

“Speak.” The Great Elder said. This purple-clothed youth was named White Mirrorjade and he was an extremely favored disciple. He would likely become one of the top figures of Carefree Island, and he even had a chance of becoming the next Island Master.

White Mirrorjade politely bowed as a junior did, then began to slowly speak, “This disciple believes that if the descendant of the mysterious person that left behind the Sovereign Dao Fruit Tree comes to our Carefree Island after 50,000 years to take it away, there must have been some sort of accident. Otherwise, it’s impossible for such a long period to pass. As for that mysterious person, they have likely died by now. As for his descendant, they likely found some letter left behind by this mysterious person detailing the matter. It is likely that countless generations have already separated that mysterious person from his descendant. By depending on this alone, for this descendant to come to Carefree Island to demand the return of the Ten Severing Dao Fruit True, that is far too ridiculous.”

“Since ancient times, those with strength and those with the destiny were able to take and occupy heavenly materials. But that junior called Lin Ming is only at the eighth stage of Life Destruction. No matter how great his talent is, how high can his combat strength really be? This disciple also believes that this Lin Ming doesn’t have some supreme elder supporting him from behind. Otherwise, if he came here to do something so important as taking back the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree, he surely would have brought a master for a display of shocking strength. If such a top character were to come demand the return of the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree, the process would be much smoother. One could see from this that there is no one supporting Lin Ming; there is only him.”

“In this case, even if he obtains the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree, it will be impossible for him to keep it. A man’s wealth is also his ruin. He will surely bring upon himself a calamity because of the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree. He will be cursed to death by the divine tree. That is because his fate is too shallow, that is because he cannot withstand the destiny of the divine tree! If we do not return the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree to him, in truth, we are helping him. This can also be considered as returning the kindness of that mysterious person from the past.”

“As for my Carefree Island, we are thriving, and every single day we make more and more progress. Now we’re just half a step away from becoming a true Holy Land level sect. With the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree supporting us, we’ll become even more powerful, and our strength can also handle it. As for a lucky chance, for us to obtain the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree 50,000 years ago and for the mysterious person who left it with us to die, that is our lucky chance. The heavens themselves have granted the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree to my Carefree Island. If we do not accept the gift of the heavens, that will instead bring upon us misfortune. If we were to give away the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree to a junior whose strength is negligible, causing him to die, that would be the most stupid sort of behavior. That is the same as cutting off the hope for our Carefree Island to become a Holy Land.”

“Also, 50,000 years ago when the Ten Severing Dao Fruit was planted, we also had to use up a massive amount of celestial spirit water to nourish it. Only then did it begin to produce the Ten Severing Dao Fruits. How could we just give it away so easily after all that?”

White Mirrorjade’s words were clearly eloquent enough to turn black to white and switch good to evil, but his words were even plausible and backed up with undeniable logic, as if keeping the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree would actually be the greatest kindness to Lin Ming. As the Elders heard this, all of them were stunned. When the Great Elder spoke, he obviously shed all face and pretense of cordiality in not wanting to give up the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree, so no one spoke up. But now that White Mirrorjade spoke, there were some truths mixed into his words and he had even taken the side of justice and morality. He had come up with all sorts of reasons that the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree should stay here; really, it was enough to leave one gawking.

Ye Rosewater, the one who brought Lin Ming to Carefree Pavilion, was sitting beside White Mirrorjade. As she heard him speak, she was left stunned. She sighed and thought to herself, “This man, his skin is not of ordinary thickness.”

Chapter 1086 – The Eight Inner Hidden Gates, the Sixth Gate

The demon-masked man was silent for a moment. He finally said, “I’ve come here today to inform you about a top genius of Carefree Island. The degree of his talent far surpasses even that of Ye Rosewater, but his cultivation is only at the eighth stage of Life Destruction. Without accident, in just several hundred years he will grow to a degree that can give Splintersoul Mountain a headache of problems. If he is allowed to grow for a thousand years, he will even be able to shake the foundations of Splintersoul Mountain. Here is information on him. This time he should also be participating during this entry of the Red Desolate Mystic Realm. You should all know what to do next.”

He flung a jade slip into Soul Thousandmile’s hand.

“Keke.” Soul Thousandmile licked his lips as he swept his sense through the jade slip. The first thing that caught his attention was an energy projection image of Lin Ming. “Eighth stage Life Destruction? Is Carefree Island really so poor that they’re out of soldiers? They are even sending such a talented disciple with a low cultivation into the Red Desolate Mystic Realm and not waiting for him to grow up. Aren’t they afraid that he’ll die there?”

“Haha, it looks like Carefree Island is really desperate. They’re taking such drastic measures. It’s like they want to bring this fight to an end. It seems it’s do or die for them,” another Splintersoul Mountain disciple echoed.

At this time, the demon-masked man coldly humphed and said, “You think Carefree Island’s decision makers are fools? Although I’ve listed Lin Ming’s information, that is only the strength that he has shown. As for what the limits of his strength are, no one knows, not even me. I advise you all to not underestimate him, otherwise you will surely pay a steep price! The information is already written in the jade slip so you can pour through it yourself. I can only say that this person is my enemy, so you do not need to worry that this information is false!”

“Haha, don’t worry. We’re both clear about how ‘moral’ and ‘just’ Brother Mirrorjade’s character is!” Soul Thousandmile emphasized the words moral and just, clearly mocking White Mirrorjade. He wasn’t saying that White Mirrorjade was a righteous man that wouldn’t give wrong information, but that White Mirrorjade had too many ambitions and wouldn’t tolerate anyone to threaten his ambitions, so his information wouldn’t be wrong.

As he spoke up to here, Soul Thousandmile seemed to think of something else. A playful smile crossed his face. “You know Brother Mirrorjade, it seems as if you aren’t doing too well in Carefree Island. You seem to always be pushed aside and your status is constantly under threat. How about you join my Splintersoul Mountain instead? Our Splintersoul Mountain has extremely advanced studies into the soul. In fact, in that aspect alone we can be considered at the top of the True Martial Great World. If we pay a great enough price and help you increase the strength of your divine soul, your talent will absolutely rise.”

“You sure spout enough crap!” the demon-masked man icily said.

Soul Thousandmile stiffened, about to burst with anger, but at that moment the demon-masked man’s entire body combusted into flames. Before long, he turned into a giant conflagration. All of these flames came from the body of the masked man. Moreover, the temperature was extremely high; it easily burnt the demon-masked man to ashes.

As Soul Thousandmile looked at the remains of the demon-masked man, he shook his head, “He’s too careful. He never sends his main body here, and every time before leaving he will immolate himself and turn himself into ashes without clues left behind.”

The disciple beside Soul Thousandmile spoke up, “Of course he has to be careful. Not only does he have to guard against his identity being exposed to Carefree Island, but he even has to watch out for us ambushing him and capturing him. No one will believe this type of person.”

“Mm, even we aren’t exactly sure of his true identity. With the available information and his motives, I can approximate that he is White Mirrorjade. But as for evidence, we don’t have any.”

“Hehe, it should be more or less correct. Although he can hide his appearance, he can’t hide his motivations. Not just that, but the information he’s given us is so detailed; it’s not what the average disciple can provide. So who else could it be? This person really goes to extreme lengths to achieve his goals; he’s even willing to betray his own sect without an ounce of hesitation!”

“Humph, what does it matter if he betrays his sect? Even if Carefree Island is suffering setbacks in the Red Desolate Mystic Realm, they will only be weakened and slowly diminish to an upper eighth-grade sect. It’s impossible for the likes of them to truly be exterminated. This simply doesn’t have any effect on White Mirrorjade. In any case, his only goal is to become Island Master. As for whether Carefree Island is a ninth-grade Holy Land or an eighth-grade sect, that’s not as important as him becoming Island Master. If you had to choose, would you rather become a minion of a peak sect? Or the Sovereign of a lower grade sect?” Soul Thousandmile rhetorically asked.

The disciple nodded, “That sounds about right. Being a Sovereign would feel much better!”

As the two Splintersoul Mountain disciples were discussing, on Carefree Island within a secret seclusion chamber, White Mirrorjade opened his eyes.

“Humph, those two fellows keep trying to use words to probe my status, as if they are already completely sure about who I am. Humph, what a waste of time! They want to find my weak spot and use it to threaten me, but what a pity, they will never find any evidence. These puppets were made many years ago and also found by me in a secret depository deep underneath the seabed of the Red Desolate Sea. After I use them to pass on a message, I immediately destroy them. Even if these puppets are caught, there is no evidence on them to indicate they are related to me, because they simply don’t come from Carefree Island and the method of manufacturing them isn’t related to Carefree Island in any way.”

White Mirrorjade thought to himself as he stood up, “Lin Ming, to think that you would refuse the road to heaven and rush through the gates of hell instead. If you are on Carefree Island, I wouldn’t dare to move against you, but since you want to join in on the war between the three sects, you should also be aware that there no eyes in battle. Who can be blamed if you die in all the chaos?”

As White Mirrorjade thought of this, a sinister smile flashed across his face. He didn’t leave his seclusion chamber but instead closed his eyes and continued to meditate. This war was likely to be spread over a wide area with rivers of blood flowing. He had to maintain his peak state, otherwise even he might perish in the mystic realm!

As for White Mirrorjade’s information, in truth he hadn’t betrayed Carefree Island. He had only pointed out Lin Ming so that his chances of living in the chaotic battle would be much smaller. Of course, if Splintersoul Mountain was really useless, White Mirrorjade wouldn’t mind hiding in some secret place and helping them kill off Lin Ming.

Although he was one large boundary and another four small boundaries of cultivation above Lin Ming, he still wouldn’t lower his guard. For Lin Ming to grow to such a degree, his life must inevitably be extremely tough. Those that plotted against Lin Ming might find their plans bouncing back on them instead. Moreover, the high level figures of Carefree Island had an extremely ambiguous attitude toward Lin Ming; this also caused White Mirrorjade to have all sorts of doubts.

As White Mirrorjade was training, Lin Ming was also in training. As for the area where he was training, that was in Carefree Palace’s mystic realm space!

This entire space was like a boundless field of flowers, as if it were a sunny and breezy spring day. But high above him was actually a vast expanse of stars with distant celestial bodies. It was like he was in a field of green wilderness floating within the boundless universe.

In front of Lin Ming, a dragon bone floated, faintly glowing with an azure light. Although this dragon bone weighed more than a mountain range, this space had no gravity, so it easily floated where it was.

At this time, Lin Ming went into seclusion to open up the sixth of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates–the Gate of View!

The Gate of View was located in his back and was in charge of defense. After opening it, Lin Ming’s defense would rise to another level. But the truth was that in comparison to the defensive power gained from opening the Gate of View, the defensive power that he gained from absorbing the dragon bone would actually be much greater.

Once he fused the dragon bone essence into his own skeleton, his bones would become tougher than a top grade saint artifact!

By absorbing the dragon bone, Lin Ming’s ability to resist attacks would undergo a qualitative leap.

In addition to his terrifying endurance and regenerative ability, even if Lin Ming stood still and allowed martial artists at his boundary to attack him, in all likelihood, they wouldn’t even be able to harm him.

Mo Eversnow stood next to the dragon bone like an otherworldly fairy. And beside her was another woman. This woman had white temples and her face was etched with the passing of the years. One could see from her appearance that she had also once been an outstanding beauty. This woman was Mo Eversnow’s aunt, Mo Riverbliss.

Absorbing the dragon bone was an extremely long and vast project. In the God Beast Mystic Realm, the Asura King had obtained the dragon bone for a very long time already. Even so, it had only managed to absorb half of the dragon marrow. As for the dragon bone itself, it wasn’t able to do anything to it, because absorbing the dragon bone was simply too difficult.

The dragon bone was different from dragon marrow. For such a massive dragon bone, there was simply no way Lin Ming could swallow it. His only chance was to refine the dragon bone into its purest essence and fuse with it that way.

But the Ancient Azure Dragon was a God Beast of the primitive, archaic times. Even if its main body had died for countless hundreds of millions of years, its bones weren’t something that an ordinary person could refine.

Wasn’t wanting to refine its essence easier said than done?

This dragon bone also couldn’t be exposed to the world. Lin Ming hadn’t even dared to take it out in the Ancient Phoenix Clan. He wasn’t able to show it to his master Huo Violentstone, much less others.

If he didn’t have an expert like Huo Violentstone to help him, he could only rely on Mo Eversnow using the power of Laws to slowly refine the essence of the dragon bone. This was an extremely inefficient way of doing it. But now things were different; there was Mo Riverbliss. Her strength was at a half-step World King. She was stronger than Huo Violentstone, and even the current Patriarch of the Ancient Phoenix Clan!

Mo Riverbliss stood in front of the dragon bone and looked it over. She glanced at Lin Ming, a glorious light shining in her eyes once more. “I never imagined that such a great lucky chance would be found by you. In the past, if I had this dragon bone, my father’s soul injuries would have been healed and the Verdant Feather Holy Lands would not have ended up in such a state…”

Lin Ming bowed. “I’ll have to bother Senior Mo. I am very thankful for your help.”

Lin Ming knew that refining the dragon bone essence was not a simple matter. It would consume a great deal of origin energy and strength. This was not a minor favor.

Mo Riverbliss dismissively waved her hands. “There’s no need to thank me. If it weren’t for you, Little Snow would still be sleeping in the Magic Cube. Perhaps I would have passed away without ever being able to see her again. I will certainly keep this graciousness in my mind! Compared to that, what can refining this piece of dragon bone be considered? If you can help rebuild my Verdant Feather Holy Lands in the future, you will truly become the great benefactor of my Mo Family. I fear I won’t be able to ever repay such a benevolence in my lifetime. But at that time, I also fear that you won’t need my favors anymore.”

As Mo Riverbliss spoke, she waved her hand and a three-legged furnace flew out from her spatial ring, growing larger and larger. The furnace sent out a strong suction force that covered the supreme dragon bone. On the other hand, the supreme dragon bone began to shrink, until it was finally completely sucked into the furnace.

Lin Ming looked on from the side. This was actually a spirit artifact level treasure, and was even a first-class existence amongst all spirit artifacts.

Chapter 1094 – Counterattack

Rumble rumble rumble!

The purple mountain was smashed apart and countless pieces of shattered stone flew through the skies, scattering in all directions. A powerful shockwave rolled outwards, causing endless waves of red sand to shoot up into the sky, as though the apocalypse were unfolding. The disciples of Carefree Island never thought the Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain were lying in ambush just 6-7 miles away, and they attacked as soon as the sand storm stopped!

They looked at the terrifying attack that was launched at the purple mountain. If they were still there, the consequences would have been unbelievable!

Even if they instantly reacted and summoned their protective true essence, there would inevitably be calamitous casualties. None of the Revolving Core realm disciples would have been able to live and most of the direct disciples would have died. The ones remaining would have been seriously wounded. In this situation they would have to face an enemy that was several times their own size. They would be nothing but fish in a barrel, completely suppressed!

Ye Rosewater glanced at Lin Ming, shocked speechless. In this sand storm, a martial artist’s senses should have been limited to five miles at most, but Lin Ming was actually able to sense that the enemy was lying in ambush six or seven miles away, and even do so in an extremely accurate manner without the slightest mistake. What was even stranger was that he had accurately guessed their plans. The Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain were both waiting for the moment the sand storm ended to attack!

However, Lin Ming was also waiting for this moment!

“Attack! Give it everything you have!” Lin Ming coldly shouted out. In that moment, the many disciples of Carefree Island no longer hesitated. All of them overdrew their strength and combined their combat skills with an array formation to attack. Although they were far from being able to compare with their enemy, they had the initiative and also the mysterious Lin Ming on their side. Their confidence soared upwards, their momentum rising like a volcano!

In that moment, countless sword lights shot out. The disciples of Carefree Island studied the Wood Laws, so these sword lights were like a deluge of green beams that twisted through the air, lighting up the horizon!

As the disciples of Carefree Island attacked, Lin Ming’s aura also erupted. He opened the Heretical God Force to the limit, and at the same time a blazing gold light began to shine from between his eyebrows. He was burning all of the Ancient Phoenix blood within his body!

As he combusted the blood of the Ancient Phoenix, Lin Ming felt as if his bones were heating up like tempered metal. His blood and even his marrow began to boil over, and his joints issued endless crackling sounds that extended into a single loud explosive burst, as though a dragon was roaring into the vast skies.

The blood of the Azure Dragon was resonating with the blood of the Ancient Phoenix!

Dragon and phoenix, rejoicing together!

In that moment, a massive amount of origin energy gathered towards Lin Ming, as if a glorious blue lotus were slowly blooming around him!

This was an attack that combined three Concepts of Fire; Burning Heat, Annihilation, and Creation–the Blue Lotus Flame Dance!

This was Lin Ming’s self-created attack which he had comprehended during the smelting trial at Fire Spirit Star. It was a fusion of the first three level Concepts of the Fire Laws!

Lin Ming had first used this move when he rushed to complete the Illusionary God Combat Array’s Thousand Slaughter and fought Crimson Strifecloud. Now was the second time!

In Lin Ming’s peak state, even Crimson Strifecloud had difficulty directly contending with the Blue Lotus Flame Dance!

A spear thrust forwards and a flaming light lit up the entire sky. A heaven-shaking dragon roar echoed through the world. As the Phoenix Blood Spear flashed through the air, the massive blue lotus phantom fully bloomed!

At this time, Ye Rosewater was completely dumbfounded as she saw Lin Ming’s attack. Just what sort of attack was this!? The striking power was far too freakish! Just the sole power of this attack was far stronger than the combined attack of all the other disciples together!

……

“Haha, our attack was too brutal. Everyone inside should be dead.” A Splintersoul Mountain disciple recklessly laughed as he saw the purple mountain collapse.

“What a pity. Those women were extremely good vessels to help perceive the Life Laws. If –” The Divine Sea Occult Bone Clan martial artist’s words were caught in his throat. He suddenly twisted around to see terrifying beams of divine light tearing across the earth, shredding apart the wilderness as they hurtled towards them with an unstoppable momentum! Wherever this light went, endless red sand would turn into dust, forming a massive fissure!

“What!?”

“Enemy attack!”

The disciples of the Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain all paled. They never thought they would be the ones suffering a sneak attack at this time, and one so horrifying at that!

“Hurry and defend!” The late Divine Sea Occult Bone Clan captain shouted out. But as he quickly issued the command, all the other disciples were left panic-stricken. They wanted to defend, but they discovered they had exhausted all of their accumulated true essence in their own attack just now. They didn’t have enough time to gather more strength!

The point right after a martial artist attacked was when they were at their weakest. Even though this time was short, it could bring a fatal disaster! When masters fought, they would always reserve 30% of their strength in their attacks. Only at the end would they go all-out in desperate attack. But at this time, even if they weren’t able to kill their enemy, they could still cause enough trouble for them that they had enough time to gather their strength again.

If they completely used all of their strength to hit nothing and then had to face the enemy’s own all-out attack without having their guard raised, the result of this could be imagined!

Bang!

Unstoppable beams of light fell down like a rain of meteors. Terrifying explosions swallowed up everything. In this moment it was as though the entire divergent mystic realm had been lit up!

The disciples of the Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain all howled out in pain and misery. Many early Divine Sea disciples were blown to pieces, and many middle Divine Sea martial artists were grievously wounded! It had to be know that this barrage of attacks contained the strength of two great masters in Lin Ming and Ye Rosewater!

“This is…”

The disciples of Carefree island were surprised to see their attack have such a wondrous effect. They only had a dozen plus people, but they caused the nearly 40 some disciples of the Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain to suffer serious losses!

“Attack together! Kill them all!” Lin Ming frostily commanded. At the same time, he opened the Gate of Wonder and activated the Mystic Lightning Shade, shooting to the front!

A six or seven mile distance was far too short a distance to Lin Ming!

Ye Rosewater followed close behind. She had no idea what method Lin Ming had used to investigate the situation, but in addition to that terrifying striking power he displayed just now, she was utterly convinced by him.

The other disciples all rushed forwards. At that time, even if an archaic great beast were lying in front of them, they would still attack without hesitation!

“You bastards!”

“What’s going on here!?”

The two captains of the Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain had the lightest wounds. Even if they had all-out attacked, they were still able to rely on their solid foundation and multiple life-saving methods to block that attack. The attack just now barely affected their combat strength at all.

But their subordinates were off much worse. A third had immediately died. Of the nearly 40 people they brought here, only just over 20 were left remaining, and all of them were wounded.

The two captains simmered with a seething rage. As they saw a youth rush towards their front, their hatred and anger burst open like a roiling volcano!

“Only at the eighth stage of Life Destruction! You’re looking to die!”

“Mm? Eighth stage Life Destruction! It’s that damned Lin Ming!”

The two captains instantly recalled Lin Ming’s name. Lin Ming was also their top priority for coming here.

“So you are Lin Ming. You came at just the right time! I’ll carve you up first to boost morale!” The Occult Bone Clan’s late Divine Sea captain gave a loud shout. Layers upon layers of bone armor burst out from his body, covering his entire self. He grasped a giant bone sword and cut towards Lin Ming.

At the same time, the captain of Splintersoul Mountain also attacked. The weapon in his hand was very unique. It was a ghost banner. As this ghost banner shot forwards, cold winds appeared in the air and the pained screams of ghosts echoed outwards. These ghosts melded together, forming into a giant demon claw that grasped towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming had to face the simultaneous attacks of two late Divine Sea powerhouses!

“Junior-apprentice Brother, be careful!”

Although Ye Rosewater admired Lin Ming to the extreme, she also worried that Lin Ming would be severely wounded by these attacks.

As the attacks of the Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain’s two captains fell down, behind Lin Ming, a blood red lotus began to bloom!

Prime Emperor Lotus Flower – grandmist space!

With the concealing technique Mo Eversnow taught him, Lin Ming could fully utilize the grandmist space. He no longer needed to worry about it.

As the grandmist space activated, it was like a desolate ancient beast that devoured all. It met the attacks of the two captains!

The Occult Bone Clan captain’s bone sword energy was continuously weakened by the grandmist space. Although the Occult Bone Claw’s Laws of Life were mysterious, in the formation of the universe, life only appeared at the latter stages. How could the Laws of Life possibly resist the annihilating strength of the Grandmist Laws? As for the countless ghost phantoms that were sent out by Splintersoul Mountain, they were all reduced to ashes underneath the power of the grandmist space!

By the time the two masters’ attacks reached Lin Ming, they were already weakened by over half. Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and swept outwards!

Penetrating Rainbow!

Bang!

The power of thunder and fire furiously wove together in a deafening explosion, tearing apart the bone sword energy and the demon claw at the same time!

“What!?”

“How, how could this happen!?”

The two masters never expected their combined attack to be directly defeated by Lin Ming. Without time to think, Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear had already turned towards Splintersoul Mountain’s captain.

Lin Ming could see that the Splintersoul Mountain captain had weaker defenses. Moreover, his attacks were based on the Laws of Soul; they were completely suppressed by Lin Ming’s own abilities.

“Chasing Thunder!”

As the Splintersoul Mountain captain saw Lin Ming rushing towards him, a black energy surrounded his entire body as he waved his ghost banner. A black demon appeared from this black energy and plunged towards Lin Ming. While he used a physical attack, he also used a soul attack!

However, the power of ghosts were restrained by the power of thunder to begin with.

In front of Lin Ming, soul attacks were even more of a joke.

Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear thrust downwards without change.

A fierce explosion sounded out and waves of violent energy billowed outwards. The Splintersoul Mountain captain was directly smashed backwards by Lin Ming’s spear! His protective true essence crazily trembled and his bamboo hat flew away, revealing an incomparably pale face. Flows of red blood flowed down from the corners of his mouth, trailing into the wind.

Chapter 1100 – Sweep Away the Fallen leaves

The resources excavated from the Red Desolate Mystic Realm were truly wealth that could be spent. Although violet sun stones weren’t comparable to top heavenly treasures like a supreme dragon bone, they were still indispensable items for all martial artists. And, it was also impossible for Lin Ming to exchange the supreme dragon bone for money.

Before, Mo Eversnow had said that recorded within the Celestial Tyrant Manual, there were two pills that needed to be used in order to break through the last two gates of Life and Death of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. They were the Gate of Life’s Esoteric Immortality Pill and the Gate of Death’s Esoteric Mortality Pill. It would be impossible for Lin Ming to search for the ingredients to these pills himself. He would have to purchase them from a trading company or win them through an auction house. And to do all of this, he needed money.

As the many Carefree Island disciples hid among the rocks, they followed orders and restrained their divine sense and aura. At the same time, they were also gathering strength in their bodies, waiting to make a sudden strike like a bolt of thunder.

Hu – Hu –

The movement of Gongyang Bonesmash and Soul Thousandmile and their squads caused a sharp whistling sound as they passed through the air. They recklessly radiated energy from all over their bodies; the Carefree Island disciples that were hiding in the rocks were certainly able to feel this.

“People have come!”

“It’s… it’s the Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain! Why would they appear here? Moreover… they’re injured!”

The Carefree Island disciples saw with their own eyes, just seven or eight miles away, there were nearly 40 Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain disciples headed their way. All of them were wounded, exhausted, and on the verge of collapse. It was clear that they had suffered a tragic battle just now!

This was the best chance to ambush them!

“Lin Ming, he…”

Ye Rosewater, Xiao Raingem, and the others all glanced over at Lin Ming, not sure what sort of expression to use. It was clear that Lin Ming had accurately grasped their enemy’s every move, and thus he was able to arrive here ahead of time to ambush them.

To have someone like Lin Ming as an enemy was too terrifying!

“Now!”

Lin Ming indifferently spat out this word, suddenly rousing the Carefree Island disciples from their daze.

“Attack!”

Over a dozen Carefree Island disciples formed a battle array formation, erupting with the entirety of their strength. Sword light howled through the skies as beams of blue light pierced through the heavens!

Lin Ming burnt all of the Ancient Phoenix blood in his body as he simultaneously opened the Heretical God Force.

Blue Lotus Flame Dance!

Seven or eight miles was far too short a distance. Gongyang Bonesmash and the others would never imagine that they would be ambushed right here. After all, their previous battle had been far too harsh. White Mirrorjade wouldn’t divide a part of his forces to lie in ambush for them, and it was also impossible for him to know just what direction they would escape in.

“Be careful!”

“Shit!”

Gongyang Bonesmash and Soul Thousandmile both cried out at the same time. However, it was too late. Their disciples had exhausted far too much of their energy, so it was impossible for them to compare with Lin Ming and his group, who had gathered their complete strength. This strike was like a sudden bolt of lightning out of the blue!

Moreover, this strike contained the attacks of Lin Ming and Ye Rosewater, two great masters. In particular Lin Ming – his striking power was able to cut down a late Divine Sea master.

Bang bang bang!

A terrifying explosion lit up the sky. In an instant, around 10 disciples that were originally severely wounded were suddenly blown to pieces by the barrage!

“Attack!”

Lin Ming took the lead and rushed to the front! At this time, the opponents he faced were even weaker than the last bunch. He was like a ferocious tiger running into a pack of debilitated wolves; the result of this battle could be imagined.

With a sweep of the Phoenix Blood Spear, two martial artists were beheaded.

“Run!”

Gongyang Bonesmash decisively ordered. Right now his combat strength was less than 20% of his peak state and he had also lost an arm. Now, he had even fallen for the enemy’s ambush. His opponents were clearly prepared for him. Trying to struggle with them would only result in death. This meant that the only slim chance of survival he had was to escape as quickly as possible.

“Dream on!”

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a brutal light. The first six of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates opened together and the power of blood within his body flooded forth as if a dam had been released, waves upon waves of surging energy gushing outwards.

Ka ka ka!

Lin Ming’s entire body emitted explosive crackling sounds as his aura began to rapidly climb and his strength continuously increased. After his momentum reached the peak, Lin Ming stepped several miles forward in a single step, his Phoenix Blood Spear causing the space around it to tremble.

Celestial Tyrant Manual’s Hundred Layered Waves!

Bang!

With the sound of the world collapsing, Lin Ming used the Hundred Layered Waves technique to strike out with surging true essence in his body, pounding towards Gongyang Bonesmash like an unstoppable tsunami!

“Ahhhh!”

In this life or death moment, Gongyang Bonesmash roared and thrust out his lance. However, his efforts were useless. He was directly struck by the violent Hundred Layered Waves in his right chest. The horrifying impact force completely crushed the right half of his body into nothing!

Gongyang Bonesmash had died in a single attack!

Although he had been injured, he had still been a late Divine Sea master. Even so, Lin Ming had slain him in the blink of an eye.

Then, Ye Rosewater and the others finally caught up to Lin Ming.

What a frightening attack!

If even the disciples of Carefree Island thought Lin Ming’s attack was frightening, there was no need to mention what the disciples of Splintersoul Mountain and the Occult Bone Clan were thinking. Without the least bit of hesitation, all of them began escaping!

“Kill them all! Leave no one alive!”

Ye Rosewater didn’t go to finish off the last late Divine Sea master. Instead, she began to cut down the next strongest powerhouses. Her moves were fast and she was also strong, and most importantly, she was in her peak state. It was impossible for anyone from Splintersoul Mountain or the Occult Bone Clan to be a threat to her.

And at this time, Lin Ming approached the second late Divine Sea master – Soul Thousandmile.

Soul Thousandmile’s wounds were a bit better than Gongyang Bonesmash’s, but the result was the same. In a futile effort he sent out a soul attack towards Lin Ming, hoping to stop him. However, what goes around comes around. Soul Thousandmile was struck by a backlash as his soul attack failed, and as his face was pale and his eyes dazed, Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear had already pierced through his throat like a viper.

The second late Divine Sea powerhouse had been smoothly eliminated!

Lin Ming waved his hand and Gongyang Bonesmash and Soul Thousandmile’s spatial rings both flew into his waiting grasp.

As he investigated the inside with his divine sense, there was indeed a massive amount of resources. In addition, there were also the Revolving Core disciples of Splintersoul Mountain and the Occult Bone Clan.

Lin Ming planned to hand all of these people over to Carefree Island as prisoners. As for how Carefree Island dealt with them, it didn’t matter to him at all.

To the side, Ye Rosewater and the others were winning with overwhelming momentum. Ye Rosewater naturally saw Lin Ming take up the spatial rings of Soul Thousandmile and Gongyang Bonesmash. She also guessed that there was a massive amount of wealth hidden within them.

However, Ye Rosewater was smart enough that she didn’t say anything. She knew that without Lin Ming here, they would have already died without a burial ground, let alone obtaining any treasures.

The battle proceeded astonishingly smoothly. In less than an incense stick of time, all their enemies had been swept away like old autumn leaves.

All the disciples that had chased their enemies had already returned. 14-15 of them had died underneath Lin Ming’s hand alone. As for the disciples of Carefree Island, none of them had died and only several of them had been severely wounded due to a desperately suicidal counterattack by their opponents. But, these severely wounded disciples would be fine as long as they ate some pills and rested for some time.

However, they weren’t able to completely eliminate the wounded disciples of the Occult Bone Clan and Splintersoul Mountain. There had been too many of them to begin with and they had all scattered in different directions; it would be too troublesome to chase after all of them.

In just several hours, they had won victory after victory against opponents who had outnumbered them. This caused their confidence to soar up into the sky.

“Junior-apprentice Brother Lin, what should we do next?” Ye Rosewater asked Lin Ming. She had already decided to take Lin Ming as their de-facto captain, even if that meant blindly following. She admired him with her entire being.

“Nothing much. Let’s go and meet back up with the main force.” Lin Ming smiled as he spoke. If he delayed too long then White Mirrorjade would be able to recover from his wounds. Lin Ming naturally couldn’t allow that to happen.

Chapter 1109 – Crazy White Brook

“My apologies, Island Master.” Lin Ming sincerely said. He clearly knew that Xiao Skywhite reprimanded him in order to protect him in this situation.

However, White Brook refused to let go. “Xiao Skywhite, I have something to say today. This junior is not someone from my Carefree Island and he actually comes here to spout utter garbage, questioning me in front of everyone present and slandering the clean reputation of my White Family. If I were to let this go today, then what face would I have left!”

Someone like White Brook, who had occupied such a high and lofty position for all this time, was the same as someone who sat upon the imperial throne to mortals. He was like someone who had been an emperor for dozens of years already and was long used to all ministers and everyone else below him being utterly servile in his presence. But now, there was actually a boy who suddenly appeared out of nowhere and was daring to impugn his honor in front of everyone, and also question his words. From this alone, the results could be imagined.

“Elder White, may I ask why you would say that?” Lin Ming coldly asked, sneering inwardly.

“If you say that Mirrorjade betrayed you, then where is the evidence? Take out the evidence then! You blaspheme the dead and also destroy the innocent name of my White Family. Since you dare to do so, you had better take out the evidence, otherwise don’t blame me for being rude!” White Brook slowly fell down from the red mountain peak he stood on, coming to a floating position in front of Lin Ming as he looked down at him with thick condescension.

“I have evidence, but I’m afraid that you don’t dare to examine it.”

“What?” Blue veins began to pop up on White Brook’s forehead. His anger had finally reached the extreme. “If you have evidence then of course I must examine it! If you cannot take out evidence then I want you to die as reparation!”

“Die as reparation? Hahaha, hahaha!” Lin Ming laughed as if he didn’t have a care in the world. “If I cannot bring out evidence then you want me to die as reparation? Your White Family is far too arrogant. Then let me ask you, what if I can take out evidence? Will you die instead?”

Lin Ming didn’t fear White Brook, thus he repeatedly poked and challenged him with words. This caused the many Elders present to feel horrified, as if their hearts were being tightly gripped. If he enraged White Brook there truly wouldn’t any good outcomes for him.

“What… did you say?” White Brook’s face became as gloomy as dark water. His words were slow and pronounced.

“I already spoke; could you not understand my words? The one who said White Mirrorjade was a traitor was Gudao Ming. I only repeated what he said. And yet, if I cannot take out further evidence, you want me to die?

“And in turn, if I can take out evidence, you actually won’t need to pay any price, but you will still remember this grudge and take revenge against me in the future? Is there such a truth in this world? If this isn’t overbearing then what is?”

“Hahahahaha!” White Brook laughed out loud. “Just who do you think you are? You think you can speak reason with me? You think you can speak what is fair to me? Do you think you have these qualifications!? In the world of martial artists, strength is supreme! Fairness and reasoning only apply to those that are similar in strength! You are nothing but a little Life Destruction ant. Even if you are extremely talented, that only makes you a slightly larger ant! If I wanted to deal with you, that would be no different from a common mortal stepping on an ant, and who can stop me? Who can stop me!? And you still think that you can talk about fairness with me? Just how stupid can you be!?

“If I kill you, that is because you have harmed the reputation of my White Family! The reputation of my White Family is thousands of times more precious than your life will ever be! Your death is still far from enough! And yet you want to threaten me and have me take out my life to accompany you? Just weigh how much your life is worth and realize how laughable you are!”

……..

As White Brook was yelling at Lin Ming, an inner court Elder carelessly turned over the combat report jade slip passed out by Xiao Raingem. “Hm? This jade slip is actually divided into two parts. If one doesn’t pay attention, they wouldn’t realise there is further information on the back. Isn’t this just deliberately looking for trouble?”

Normally, a martial artist could look over a jade slip extremely quickly; it only took a single sweep. But, Xiao Raingem’s combat report jade slip was deliberately divided into two, and the middle section was blank. This created a gap in the reading, just like in a notebook where there were only words recorded on the first few pages and the last few pages, with the entire center blank. Most people who saw the blank portion would naturally assume that there was nothing left, thus they wouldn’t continue.

Of course, for the martial artists present, as long as they wanted to, they could instantly read over the entire jade slip.

As this inner court Elder read the last portion of the jade slip, he nearly choked on himself and rolled down the mountain. He looked at Lin Ming with an incredulous expression, “Am I dreaming? White Mirrorjade actually died to this Lin Ming. This boy… is he insane? If White Brook finds out about this then… that would simply…”

Because White Brook and Lin Ming’s dispute was too eye-catching, several Elders didn’t finish reading the jade slip. Ye Rosewater was also worried about Lin Ming. Lin Ming was simply playing with fire here. Why would he offend Highest Elder White Brook just because he wanted to sass back?

Facing White Brook’s horrifying pressure, Lin Ming seemed completely unaware of it all. He smiled and asked, “So, if my humble and lowly life can actually damage the reputation of the noble and glorious White Family, isn’t that a reason for me to feel honored? Hahaha! But Elder White, you said that it was impossible for White Mirrorjade to be the traitor. Since you’re so sure of yourself, why are you worried that I can produce evidence?”

“Lin Ming, if you can take out evidence then I will personally remove White Mirrorjade’s name from my family tree! Otherwise, hehe…”

“Remove a name? Remove the name of a dead person? Is that the price that your White Family will pay? How valuable.” Lin Ming mocked. But, he also knew that it was impossible to get White Brook to bet his life for any reason. With his status, he would never make such a bet with a junior.

“Elder White, you said that regardless of what the evidence is, you will investigate it yourself. Then, I will take out the evidence. If you don’t dare to examine it then don’t say that my evidence is wrong.”

“Then take it out!” White Brook coldly said, his eyes filled with a thick killing intent. “As long as you don’t try to play some tricks with this evidence then I can naturally verify it!”

“Good!” This was the effect that Lin Ming wanted. If he didn’t anger White Brook and took out the half-dead White Mirrorjade, then White Brook would probably storm off from the scene. As for agreeing to search White Mirrorjade’s soul, that was something he would never do.

“I apologize to all Elders here. Because of some reasons, there were some matters that I intentionally needed to hide from you all. In truth, White Mirrorjade wasn’t dead at the end of the Red Desolate Mystic Realm expedition. But, there’s not much of a difference now!”

Before Lin Ming left the Red Desolate Mystic Realm, he severed White Mirrorjade’s true essence, causing him to perch on the edge of death. A mystic art like the soul searching technique worked best when the party it was being done to was on the verge of death.

A martial artist had two kinds of death. There was the death of solely the human body, where the soul was still able to be preserved. If one suffered some sort of tremendous attack, it was likely they would die along with their soul. If that happened, their memories would also fade away and it would be impossible to use the soul searching technique.

As Lin Ming spoke, he threw out the nearly dead White Mirrorjade from his spatial ring. At this time, White Mirrorjade’s entire body was covered in pieces of flesh and blood, and he no longer seemed even human. His organs were all smashed apart and almost all of his blood had drained out. His chest cavity was open, filled with blood plasma. His exposed heart had nearly stopped beating; he would die soon.

White Brook didn’t even immediately recognize White Mirrorjade. It was only when he faintly felt a familiar aura coming from this ruined White Mirrorjade…

“Mirrorjade!”

White Brook’s eyes turned blood red. As he looked at Lin Ming, his killing intent had already reached infinite dimensions and his anger was erupting. “You turned him into this!?”

“Yes.” Lin Ming confidently acknowledged.

“Die then!”

White Brook suddenly attacked. As he lifted his hand, the power of his inner world came billowing outwards, forming a raging blue storm that rushed towards Lin Ming.

And at this time, Xiao Skywhite was already prepared. He gathered his hands together and countless grand runes appeared, aligning into mystical patterns behind him. These patterns forming a massive suction force that completely inhaled the surging blue storm that White Brook sent out.

The runes that Xiao Skywhite used were the supernatural power contained within Carefree Palace itself. It had to be known that the entire Carefree Palace was a titanic spirit artifact. It was a war fortress, and the only one with the authority and ability to control it was the Island Master!

Although Xiao Skywhite’s strength was inferior to White Brook’s, in Carefree Palace, White Brook was not Xiao Skywhite’s match.

“Xiao Skywhite, you dare to stop me!?” White Brook vehemently sputtered.

“Elder White, please proceed according to the rules!! If you want to deal with Lin Ming, then you must have the truth on your side!” Xiao Skywhite’s voice was cold. Because White Brook was his senior, Xiao Skywhite was respectful in the way he spoke to him. But, this did not mean that Xiao Skywhite feared White Brook. “It has already been stated that there is a chance that White Mirrorjade was the traitor. Lin Ming has already brought out the evidence to prove this point, and Elder White has also agreed to examine the evidence. If Lin Ming cannot take out true evidence then it won’t be too late to kill him. If you recklessly attack him now, then you will be accused of killing a witness to cover up your own crimes.”

As Xiao Skywhite spoke, more and more runes formed behind him, faintly forming an energy barrier that surrounded Lin Ming. This was clearly to protect Lin Ming.

“Xiao Skywhite! Good! Very good!” White Brook said the word ‘good’ twice, clearly angry to the extreme.

Then, he turned to Lin Ming, his eyes sharp as if he wanted to stab countless holes into Lin Ming, saying, “Where is the evidence!?”

Lin Ming shrugged. “Elder White, at this point, you should have already guessed it. The evidence is White Mirrorjade himself. Search his soul and investigate him. If you do not believe me then you can have the Disciplinary Elder, Island Master Xiao, or even yourself investigate him!”

“What did you say!?”

White Brook’s eyes turned blood red. The soul searching technique was originally an extremely dark and malicious demonic art. After searching someone’s soul, the subject would normally turn into an idiot. Although the soul searching technique was a cruel and sinister move, it was actually very easy to use. It was impossible to search out incomparably complex things like alchemy techniques, array formation techniques, or cultivation methods using this technique, but searching for just simple information was actually straightforward. Thus, even if one was an Elder of the righteous path, this was still doable.

“Elder White, you said that if I had evidence, you would investigate it yourself. Then, don’t blame me for this. Moreover, White Mirrorjade is already dead, so there is no meaning in you showing any sort of compassion to him.”

As Lin Ming spoke, White Mirrorjade seemed to confirm Lin Ming’s words. White Mirrorjade’s body twitched one last heart and then he lay completely motionless, with even the last puttering beats of his heart dying down.

Like this, the White Mirrorjade that had been considered by everyone as the best candidate to be the next Island Master had died.

Chapter 1119 – Where Lies the Limit?

High above the sea of clouds around Carefree Palace, the origin energy surged about. The winds became more and more turbulent, and the weather turned increasingly dark and stormy. Vaguely, one could make out an auspicious rainbow-hued divine halo of light surrounding all of Carefree Palace. This colorful light was created by all the different types of energy gathered around Carefree Palace.

Whoosh!

Two hazy lights shot out from Carefree Palace. One of them was Carefree Island’s Island Master, Xiao Skywhite. As for the other, they were completely wrapped in a bright white light, making one unable to discern their appearance at all. This person seemed like a profound woman that had descended from the highest heavens.

Great Elder Xiao Haogan instantly recognized this woman. It was Mo Riverbliss herself!

“Those two fellows also came out…”

Xiao Haogan whispered. If Mo Riverbliss and Xiao Skywhite emerged, then that proved that Lin Ming’s Ninefall was truly coming to an end. At this time, Mo Riverbliss had done everything she could do. The final stretch would all depend on Lin Ming himself.

Following that, a white-robed man slowly flew up from the skies above Carefree Pavilion. This person had a wizened appearance. He was the strongest master in Carefree Island outside of Mo Riverbliss, Highest Elder White Brook!

Behind White Brook were two other old men. They were also Highest Elders of Carefree Island. They had once been Vice Island Masters, but in terms of strength and status, they were worse than White Brook.

As the many disciples of Carefree Island saw these three people, all of them were shocked. It was naturally impossible for them to recognize Mo Riverbliss, who was shrouded in a bright white light, but there were enough disciples that were able to recognize White Brook and the other Highest Elders.

“Heavens! Isn’t that our Carefree Island’s three Highest Elders? Even Island Master Xiao is there!”

“Why would they all come out together? I thought that one of them was making a breakthrough, but now it seems that it’s someone else. Just who is in Carefree Palace?”

All of the disciples present were floored. As young disciples, they had never seen such a great scene as they had today. Naturally, they all thought that this sort of world phenomenon could only be produced by a late Divine Lord powerhouse.

At this point, a resonant cry resounded from the depths of Carefree Palace, shaking through the world, piercing into the heavens!

This sound was like the roar of a True Dragon awakening from a deep slumber, singing to the heavens!

After that, from the vault of Carefree Palace, a divine light lit up the world. A pure blood energy turned the clouds crimson. The red light penetrated through the skies, bathing everything in crimson, blinding everyone’s eyes.

Hu – hu – !

The condensed blood energy swirled about, manifesting into the shape of a red True Dragon. It rampaged through the skies, washing all of the clouds away. In the skies above Carefree Island for several hundred miles, there was only this blood energy dragon form dancing throughout, spurring the universe!

As this blood energy dragon rollicked in the air, a vast power of blood vitality surged outwards like an endless tsunami, crashing forwards without limit!

All of Carefree Island’s disciples changed complexions. This blood energy dragon that roared out from Carefree Palace had such a rich and vivid blood vitality that it wasn’t something a human could possess! This was no longer a question of cultivation. As an essence gathering system martial artist’s cultivation increased, it would only increase their life force and allow them to live longer. However, their blood vitality would still be limited. Whether it was a Divine Lord, Holy Lord, or World King, they still shouldn’t possess such a terrifyingly vast blood energy. This blood energy was so vast that it resembled a fathomless sea!

“Is it not a martial artist but an ancient great beast?”

All of the young disciples of Carefree Palace had this idea.

At this time, the heaven and earth origin energy finally began to condense. Countless Heavenly Dao Law Fragments gathered in the air, forming an origin energy cloud!

“The origin energy cloud has appeared!”

“It’s finally here!”

Mo Riverbliss, Xiao Skywhite, and all the other Elders of Carefree Island were waiting for this moment. This was the most critical period of Ninefall – the forming of the origin energy cloud!

“Mm… this origin energy cloud…” Mo Riverbliss frowned. She looked up at the skies. Normally, a martial artist would produce an origin energy cloud that was very colorful and auspicious. Its color would symbolize the type of cultivation method that they practiced. For instance, many of Carefree Island’s martial artists cultivated the Wood Laws, thus the clouds they formed were a deep emerald green. The Ancient Phoenix Clan cultivated the Fire Laws, thus their origin energy clouds were a vivid red. The Electric Violet Kirin Clan cultivated the Thunder Laws, thus their origin energy clouds were purple.

But, Lin Ming’s origin energy clouds weren’t red like fire or purple like thunder but a deep gray. This massive storm also contained a calamitous killing intent, as if it would swallow up the world!

As this origin energy cloud began to spread over Carefree Island, it was like the end of all times had come.

After it appeared it rapidly inflated. In just several breaths of time, it climbed to the inferior three levels, intermediate three levels, all the way to the superior three levels!

“A 24 mile origin energy cloud, that is an Eight Layered Heavens. If he continues upward then he will reach the extreme three levels!”

“From how this is developing, perhaps the extreme three levels might not be Lin Ming’s limit. He might even reach the absolute three levels!”

“Maybe… if that’s true, then Lin Ming will steadily reach large success Holy Lord and reach the peak of the Holy Lord realm in the future. But, for a half-step World King, an absolute three levels origin energy cloud might not be enough…” Xiao Haogan slowly said as the Elders began speaking to each other.

At this time, his complexion wasn’t too good. He didn’t know why, but as he faced this origin energy cloud that seethed with a terrible killing intent, he felt a great pressure pushing down on him.

He was a solemn and dignified late Divine Lord, and yet facing the origin energy cloud from a mere junior that was crossing Ninefall, he actually felt oppressed!

Of course, this sort of oppression didn’t come from Lin Ming, but came from the Heavenly Dao Laws. It was like he was facing the entirety of the vast universe.

As these Elders spoke amongst themselves, the range of the cloud had already reached 27 miles; this was a Nine Layered Heavens!

The first nine Layered Heavens were respectively called the Divine Heavens, Blue Heavens, Teal Heavens, Core Heavens, Reverence Heavens, Shaking Heavens, Purple Heavens, and Overwhelming Heavens.

Upon reaching the Nine Layered Heavens, that was to hold the chaos of the universe between one’s fingertips!

A Nine Layered Heavens Ninefall was an entirely new level!

One step back was mortality, one step forwards was sanctification.

Whether one could achieve a Nine Layered Heavens was the symbol of whether a genius could become a true Holy Lord in the future!

For the last 50,000 years of Carefree Island, a true Holy Lord had never appeared. Only the old Island Master and the current White Brook came infinitely close to becoming a true Holy Lord. Even so, they were always a single step off.

In the Divine Realm, a Holy Lord was an illustrious character even in a major world, so how could this boundary be so easy to reach? The only reason there were so many Divine Realm Holy Lords was simply because the Divine Realm was far too vast!

Of course, to Lin Ming, a Nine Layered Heavens was only a brief stop. Soon after, the origin energy cloud grew to 30 miles.

10 Layered Heavens!

Then…

11 Layered Heavens!

12 Layered Heavens!

The origin energy cloud was like a monster as it continued to expand. It broke through the 12 Layered Heavens without pause!

To reach 12 Layered Heavens was to reach perfection of the extreme three levels. Above the Nine Layered Heavens were the Primal Chaos Heavens, Zenith Heavens, and True Outer Heavens!

After 12 Layered Heavens were the absolute three levels of Ninefall!

“He actually reached the absolute three levels! Heavens! It’s said that those who reach the absolute three levels have hopes of becoming a peak Holy Lord!”

“I wonder if Lin Ming has a chance of breaking through the absolute three heavens. What could lie beyond that boundary?” Those Elders controlling the concealing array cried out. Some of them looked over to the ‘richly experienced’ Xiao Haogan for answers.

Xiao Haogan wryly smiled. He certainly had no idea what lay beyond the absolute three levels of Ninefall. This sort of matter had already surpassed his scope of knowledge.

“This brat’s luck is quite good. He managed to enter the absolute three levels. However, every level after that multiplies in difficulty…”

Xiao Haogan forcefully ‘explained’ as he attempted to maintain his face. But in truth, as for what lay beyond the absolute three levels, or how difficult it was to reach it, he didn’t have the slightest idea.

The origin energy cloud broke through 36 miles and reached 40 miles wide. At the same time, the origin energy cloud’s thick killing intent became increasingly heavy and dire!

In those clouds, all sorts of postcelestial dao diagrams began to form. These dao diagrams were both mysterious and profound. Some shined like suns, some were plain and simple, and some even exuded surging killing intent!

Those roiling origin energy clouds were like a fierce ancient monster, stretching out its body. It was gluttonous and insatiable, swallowing up all the heaven and earth origin energy around it without end!

The Divine Lord realm Elders were fine, but the junior disciples felt a tremendous pressure.

The mammoth blood energy, the dim and dire killing intent, the boundless breath of the Great Dao, all of this made this event difficult for them to withstand.

“What is happening? Is a True Dragon hatching within Carefree Palace?”

Although many of Carefree Island’s junior disciples had seen the direct disciples break through Ninefall and withstand the baptism of world Laws, they were unable to reconcile those scenes with this Ninefall occurring before their eyes.

Of course, Ye Rosewater was already aware of Lin Ming crossing Ninefall. At this time, as Ye Rosewater looked at the origin energy clouds in the sky reaching a 14 Layered Heavens, she sucked in a breath of cold air. Was it still going to grow? Just where did Lin Ming’s limits lie?

“Perhaps… when that mysterious senior said that Junior-apprentice Brother Lin would cultivate into a Great World King and then support Carefree Island in turn, all of that could truly become reality…”

As Ye Rosewater thought of this, all sorts of brilliant lights shined in her beautiful eyes.

16 Layered Heavens!

He had broken through the absolute three levels of Ninefall!

If this continued forwards, that was a domain none of them were knowledgeable about. Out of everyone present, besides Mo Riverbliss, none of them had ever experienced such a scene.

Only now did a faint trace of satisfaction appear on Mo Riverbliss’s face.

In her opinion, after Lin Ming broke through the absolute three levels he still maintained enough momentum to continue forwards. He would at least be able to break through another five or six Layered Heavens. Only then would he reach the most basic requirements that Mo Riverbliss desired from him. If he couldn’t even break through the absolute three levels of Ninefall, then all of her previous efforts would have been a joke.

“Little Snow, your judgement is quite good.” Mo Riverbliss said to Mo Eversnow with a true essence sound transmission,

Mo Eversnow gently smiled. “Aunty, what you’ve seen is only the opening act. Lin Ming’s talent is extremely good to begin with, and he has also used countless heavenly materials in the Life Destruction realm. There were some treasures that would even make a World King crazy with jealousy. All of those treasures were used to lay down his foundation and help train his dual body and energy cultivation. Now that he has broken through Ninefall, he is simply a dragon that has emerged from a pool and is ready to soar into the heavens. How could he possibly stop at 16 Layered Heavens? This is only the beginning. I’ve watched him grow up, so I know this clearly in my heart!”

“Oh? Little Snow, you think that Lin Ming could surpass the past you?”

“Yes!” Mo Eversnow decisively nodded, her eyes brimming with hope.

Chapter 1120 – Double Phenomenon

Tracing Lin Ming’s many lucky chances, when he was still in the Pulse Condensation realm he had entered Divine Phoenix Island and then the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm. There, he obtained a drop of Ancient Phoenix blood, top grade medicines, as well as solar origin spring water, finally reaching the Houtian realm during this trial. After that, he had entered the Demon God Imperial Palace during the Houtian Realm and had obtained the Nirvana Dragon Root that was highly beneficial to Life Destruction realm martial artists. Using that, he had reached the Xiantian realm and had also completed Tempering Marrow.

Then, Lin Ming had entered the Eternal Demon Abyss and accidentally stumbled into the grave of the ancient goddess. He obtained a heaven-step Demon God Bone and had broken into the Revolving Core realm. There was no need to even mention the Life Destruction realm. During this period, he had obtained the 12 dao fruits, the divine thunder of an Empyrean, the supreme dragon bone, Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree, and all other sorts of various treasures. All of the treasures used by Lin Ming were things that even a Divine Lord powerhouse would find incomparably luxurious.

The reason for needing so many treasures was undoubtedly because Lin Ming dual cultivated in body and energy. Because of this, he had to expend so many resources, but this had also formed an extremely solid foundation for him.

It had to be known that for most martial artists, even if they had many resources, they still might not be able to use them. This was because there was a limit that their bodies could take and their potential was limited. For instance, it was impossible for most of them to use something like the supreme dragon bone or Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree during the Life Destruction realm. Even the Asura King had to take an extremely long period of time to absorb half the dragon marrow from the supreme dragon bone.

As for the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree, after eating it, one’s mortal body would be severed ten times. It wasn’t something that the average human was able to withstand.

There were very few people that could be like Lin Ming, and essentially nearly become something similar to the fusion of a human and God Beast. The toughness of his body had reached an unbelievable degree, one that allowed him to shoulder the medicinal efficacy of any treasures!

Omm –

Howling gales tore through the skies. In the seas all around Carefree Island, raging currents appeared. The sea waves angrily splashed against the shores, splashing up hundreds of feet.

The tides surged more and more, finally forming waves upon endless waves of devastating tsunamis.

In the skies, the power of stars, the glory of the moon, the light of the sun, all of it gathered into that origin energy cloud, completely becoming a part of the Heavenly Dao Laws.

Lin Ming’s mortal body had streamed out from Carefree Palace and completely merged into one with the origin energy cloud, fully undergoing a baptism of the Heavenly Dao Laws.

At this time, his body was nothing but a river of blood; he hadn’t yet formed a physical body. But, if one were to wander about in this origin energy cloud, they would find that river of blood pulsating.

Bang! Bang!

Every pulsation was like a heartbeat. And, each heartbeat was similar to a divine drum that was formed from the skin of an ancient vicious beast, deafening and ringing!

Bang!

Bang!

The sound became increasingly thunderous!

“This isn’t the sound of a heartbeat. His heart hasn’t yet taken shape. This is the sound of his flesh and blood being tempered by the Heavenly Dao Laws. The advantages this gives him are unimaginable.”

Mo Riverbliss whispered as she looked at the surging river of blood. The origin energy cloud could contain all the Laws of the universe. Of course, the richness and degree of depth differed from person to person. The greater the origin energy cloud, the more Laws were contained within.

Ho – !

The origin energy cloud suddenly expanded once more. 54 miles wide, 18 Layered Heavens!

18 Layered Heavens Ninefall. Above the absolute three levels… was the colored three heavens.

The word ‘color’ held the meaning of matter. The so-called colored Layered Heavens in truth meant the 18 material Layered Heavens.

The 18 Layered Heavens were derived from the Nine Layered Heavens. Here Layered Heavens gave birth to different types of energy, each forming two Layered Heavens. Thus, with two lives from one, the 18 Layered Heavens were born.

The 18 Layered Heavens were the Blind Nihility Heavens, Absolute Shade Heavens, Crimson Clear Yang Heavens, Profound Moon Reverence Heavens, Glorious Wave Heavens, Falling Family Sovereign Heavens, Illusory Court Heavens, Extreme Arbitrator Heavens, Mystic Happiness Heavens, Transcendent Pearlshine Heavens, Essence Ascending Heavens, Consummate Imperial Protection Heavens, Manifest Extreme Wind Heavens, Origin Emperor Light Heavens, Infinite Ancestor Heavens, Thoughtless River Heavens, Superior Prophet Heavens, Limitless Dismal Vow Heavens.

These so-called ‘Heavens’ didn’t necessarily exist, but were rather a conceptual manifestation of humanity’s martial arts civilization inheritances, and condensation of Laws.

18 Layered Heavens was also an entirely new watershed!

An ocean-like amount of heaven and earth origin energy flushed into Lin Ming’s flesh and blood. That stream of blood became even more radiant and crystalline, sending out a dark golden brilliance!

This scene was like a god being born into the world!

At this time, Xiao Haogan’s complexion couldn’t get any uglier. The 18 Layered Heavens, colored three levels were already a domain that he was completely unable to think of.

“This brat, how could his achievements be so high… moreover, it’s continuing to grow… 18 Layered Heavens… is the 18 Layered Heavens not his limit?

“What is above the 18 Layered Heavens?

“How many Layered Heavens can possibly appear in Ninefall?”

As Xiao Haogan was lost in thought, he suddenly felt the array formation tremble. The light barrier of the array formation appeared and faint cracks began to reveal themselves.

This change shocked Xiao Haogan. There were problems developing in the concealing array formation!

Before this, Xiao Haogan had thought that Mo Riverbliss was making a fuss over nothing. He thought that he alone would be able to control the concealing array formation, but Mo Riverbliss actually ordered 12 of them to help activate it. Xiao Haogan had scoffed at this order, but now, it seemed that this array formation was truly having difficulties withstanding the impact of the Heavenly Dao Laws!

“Elder Xiao, what are you doing?”

“Hurry up and revolve your true essence and pour it into the array formation!”

Xiao Haogan was stirred up from his stupor as the true essence sound transmissions of the other Elders resounded in his ears. He turned to see that the other Elders were all pouring their true essence into the array formation in order to resist the energy shockwaves from the world Laws.

If Lin Ming’s origin energy cloud continued to grow, it was unknown whether or not the 12 of them could still handle this.

This caused Xiao Haogan to turn angry from shame. However, he had no choice but to pour his own true essence into the array formation. With Mo Riverbliss here, even if he was extremely dissatisfied, there was no way he could possibly publicly disobey her orders.

Rumble rumble rumble –

The 12 Elders poured forth their complete effort, fully driving the concealing array formation to its greatest heights, caging in the energy fluctuations from Lin Ming’s Ninefall.

Then, 19 Layered Heavens, 20 Layered Heavens, 21 Layered Heavens!

21 Layered Heavens, the Nirvanic three levels!

At this time, the origin energy cloud had already become incomparably heavy, as if it was chaos itself. This origin energy cloud contained limitless killing intent. It continued to expand as if it didn’t know what the meaning of limits was!

Not too far away from Xiao Haogan, Highest Elder White Brook’s lips turned blue. Fear and dread blossomed in his mind as his fingers began to tremble!

“21 Layered Heavens… can there even be 21 Layered Heavens in Ninefall?”

White Brook felt dizzy and his limbs turned cold. He had read over many ancient texts in the past that recorded instances of Ninefall. Within them, 18 Layered Heavens was already the derivation of the highest heavens. As for what lay above the 18 Layered Heavens, he had no idea. It was like a beggar imagining what secrets an imperial kitchen used to produce their delicacies. No matter what it was, the knowledge of those mysterious techniques and complex processing methods was completely useless to that beggar.

This was because he couldn’t understand it!

“Look! What is that!?”

A young martial artist suddenly raised his hand and pointed out to the distance. Everyone followed his finger as far as their eyes could see.

In that origin energy cloud that seethed with chaos, a brilliant red light began to shine out.

That blazing red light grew like a tenacious weed. It became bigger and bigger, brighter and brighter!

Then, people were able to clearly see that it was a red lotus!

In that chaotic origin energy cloud, an incandescent red lotus was fully blooming!

This was a red lotus born within chaos!

This belonged to the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower. Once it bloomed, an endless pressure would surge outwards. And this, this was pressure from the Heavenly Dao Laws themselves. This pressure blotted out the skies, overwhelming, unstoppable!

As everyone looked at this red lotus, crimson light completely flooded their vision. The power of blood in their bodies tumbled and surged, as if it wanted to break out from their mortal shells!

“It’s a phenomenon!”

“A Ninefall phenomenon!”

Someone cried out in fear and alarm. Within the ancient texts, it was written that when someone achieved an extremely high level Layered Heavens during Ninefall, world phenomena would occur. Every extreme genius would experience different world phenomena during their Ninefall. These phenomena corresponded to that martial artist’s cultivation methods, martial intents, battle spirit, and all sorts of other aspects.

As everyone was speaking, all around this red lotus, the heaven and earth origin energy naturally formed an Azure Dragon and a Fire Phoenix.

This dragon and phoenix danced in the air, swirling around the red lotus. The dragon roared and the phoenix cried, their dual sounds echoing through the world! Finally, the dragon and phoenix turned into countless runes that fell onto the petals of the red lotus.

Almost no one understood what this meant. But, Mo Eversnow was well aware what this was in her heart.

The red lotus phenomenon was naturally a manifestation from the Primordius martial intent that Lin Ming cultivated.

It was the inheritance of Empyrean Primordius!

As for that dragon and phoenix, they came from the rich dragon marrow and phoenix essence within his body!

Even two divine beings like a dragon and phoenix had to revolve around the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower, dancing around it gently. It was obvious from this alone that in front of Empyrean Primordius, even God Beasts had to bow and submit!

As Mo Eversnow was lost in thought, seemingly because Lin Ming’s origin energy cloud had produced the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower, it rapidly grew once again!

24 Layered Heavens!

At this step, the Elders of Carefree Palace seemed as if they would choke on themselves.

24 Layered Heavens – what concept was that?

It was difficult to imagine just how formidable the Heavenly Dao Laws contained within this origin energy cloud would be!

And at this time, above the origin energy cloud, another phenomenon was born!

Beside the dragon and phoenix red lotus, a deep azure divine light began to bloom. It was like a crystal and also like a seed.

After several breaths of time, a lush green sprout emitted from that dazzling azure light. Tender and verdant leaves slowly extended outwards.

This sprout had a total of six leaves, three representing fire and three representing thunder. All the leaves came in various shapes. The first leaf was like a crimson heart, the second leaf was like a thin and fierce sword, the third was a purple tripod, the fourth was a golden red heavy sword, the fifth was like a square imperial jade seal, and the sixth was like a blue lotus.

This was the Heretical God Sprout!

Like the Primordius martial intent, the Heretical God Force was similarly a transcendent divine might!

As for which was weaker between the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower and the Heretical God Sprout, Mo Eversnow was unable to say. But, the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower was incomplete; there was only a third of it. So in that sense, the Heretical God Sprout was superior!

Of course, all of the disciples and Elders of Carefree Island, including White Brook and Island Master Xiao Skywhite, were unable to recognize just what the phenomena of the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower and the Heretical God Sprout meant. Even Mo Riverbliss wouldn’t have understood if Mo Eversnow hadn’t explained this to her.

After the Heretical God Sprout appeared, surging waves of fire and sheets of raining thunder formed in that heaven and earth origin energy, both of them revolving around the Heretical God Sprout. A moment later, they condensed into two thunder and fire runes that fell onto the Heretical God Sprout.

Chapter 1123 – Five Element Grand Tribulation

In the skies, the origin energy cloud was still tumbling. But, no matter how much it condensed, it still wouldn’t surpass 99 miles. And within it, changes were constantly occurring, as if the clouds were evolving.

Lin Ming absorbed a massive amount of the power of Laws within the origin energy cloud. But, there was still a part of it that wasn’t absorbed by Lin Ming and had remained within the origin energy cloud.

Lin Ming’s body was still soaking within the origin energy cloud, floating within it.

“Lin Ming finished his Ninefall. Why hasn’t he come down yet?”

Carefree Island’s Elders were unsure of what was happening. As for Mo Eversnow, her delicate eyebrows were pressed together. She too had no idea what would happen after a perfect 33 Layered Heavens Life Destruction.

Five-colored lightning sparked in the skies. Then, a melodic sound like a grand morning bell burst out into the sky, echoing without end.

This sort of sound was vast and ghostly, like a massive bronze bell ringing to the ends of the earth. As the disciples of Carefree Island heard this sound, they felt all of the blood within their bodies swell up. Their heartbeats drummed in rhythm to this divine sound, and a trace of enlightenment even occurred between every heartbeat.

“Mm? This sound is…”

“It’s the sound of the Great Dao. There are far too many Heavenly Dao Laws gathered in the origin energy clouds, thus they naturally formed the sound of the Great Dao. What we’ve heard is just a tiny bit and yet we can feel a portion of that enlightenment. As for Lin Ming himself, he directly withstood the baptism of the Heavenly Dao Laws. The advantages he obtained from this could be imagined.”

Several Elders marveled out loud, their hearts filled with envy. Then, at this time, the sound of the Great Dao suddenly changed. It was like a god was sitting atop a cloud, playing a zither. Waves after waves of mysterious sounds surged outwards. Sometimes it was pitched and daring, like soldiers in the battlefield, trudging through war and mud. Sometimes it was light and sprightly, like rivers and mountains, beads dripping down from a jade plate. At times it was soft and mild, like the thick autumn rain, flowers falling and fading…

Nobody was able to understand the meaning behind this mysterious sound. But, as everyone was immersed in it, the origin energy cloud began to rise again and again, and the energy inherent within it became increasingly intense.

Not just that, but the killing intent within that origin energy cloud became increasingly thick and heavy!

Normally, when a martial artist crossed Ninefall, the origin energy cloud they formed would come in bright auspicious colors, reflecting the cultivation method or other aspects of that martial artist. This made it so that crossing Ninefall was a vibrantly colorful time!

But Lin Ming was just the opposite. The origin energy cloud he summoned was extremely gray and solemn, like chaos itself. Moreover, the origin energy cloud he formed was far heavier than one formed by a normal martial artist. This origin energy cloud seemed as if it were condensed from elementary grandmist energy, and it itself contained an eminent killing intent. And now, this killing intent became so thick that it was substantializing, making everyone under it feel a great pressure.

After Lin Ming crossed Ninefall, not only did his origin energy clouds not scatter, but the energy within them only grew stronger!

“That is…”

The Elders of Carefree Island widened their eyes. They were only able to stare helplessly on as a bolt of dazzling gold lightning lit up that origin energy cloud!

This blazing light looked like a sun that was hidden in dark clouds!

Mo Riverbliss’s complexion immediately changed. She cried out in alarm, “That isn’t an origin energy cloud any longer! That is a catastrophic tribulation cloud!”

“What do you mean tribulation cloud?” Xiao Skywhite asked from beside Mo Riverbliss. At this time, he was working together with her to conceal the energy fluctuations from the world Laws.

“The origin energy cloud has evolved into a tribulation cloud! 33 Layered Heavens, 99 mile origin energy cloud, nine through nine returns to one, Lin Ming’s Ninefall has reached the peak of perfection. The Heavenly Dao will not abide his continued existence, thus a tribulation cloud was formed!”

Before Mo Riverbliss finished speaking, the golden light hidden with the clouds turned into a sharp gold sword that suddenly shot towards Lin Ming!

“Thunder tribulation!?” Xiao Skywhite yelled out, his eyes widened like moons.

“No! Metal tribulation!”

From the five elements of metal, wood, water, fire, and earth, metal was placed first. It was the firmest element and also the most severe!

This sword appeared hundreds of thousands of feet long. It was like the divine weapon of an Empyrean, chopping straight down at Lin Ming!

Kacha!

The golden sword cut down onto Lin Ming’s body. his body suddenly shook, but the unforeseen sound of metal striking metal sounded out! Lin Ming’s body burst out with heated and dazzling sparks, and underneath him, a fissure thousands of feet long was cut into the earth, forming an unfathomable abyss!

As the Elders and direct disciples of Carefree Island saw the terrifying abyss that this gold sword had formed in the earth, and then saw Lin Ming still floating in the skies, completely fine, all of them gulped, their throats twitching.

In resisting the metal tribulation, a thousand foot fissure had appeared in the earth, but Lin Ming himself was alright!

Was he even human?

Even a block of divine metal wasn’t so hard!

After the first golden sword cut down from the skies, more and more blazing gold blades fell down from the tribulation cloud, completely enveloping Lin Ming in a rain of gold. Gold light shined everywhere, horrifying to the extreme!

Looking from afar, Lin Ming was extremely small compared to the infinite vastness of the world. He was swallowed up by that tide of golden energy.

“Crossing Ninefall and meeting a grand tribulation of the five elements, I’ve never heard of this before!”

Mo Riverbliss was panic-stricken. Whether it was thunder tribulation or five element tribulation, all of it was the power of heavenly tribulation. In this world, when something was born that surpassed the highest truths of the Heavenly Dao, that existence would draw heavenly tribulation upon itself. For instance, when a monster reached a point in its martial path where it would obtain enlightenment, or when a top divine weapon spirit artifact was forged, or when a transcendent divine pill was born, or even when a transcendent divine might was created, all of that could summon the wrath of heavenly tribulation to the world!

And now, Lin Ming had studied two transcendent divine mights!

In addition to that, he dual cultivated body and energy, a process that already violated the current Heavenly Dao Laws of the universe!

And there was the Magic Cube, an existence that defied the will of the heavens!

Moreover, Lin Ming’s Ninefall had crossed a 33 Layered Heavens and produced a 99 mile origin energy cloud. In this situation, it was normal for him to stir up heavenly tribulation!

“Five element tribulation… Lin Ming, he…” Xiao Skywhite paled. This would be fine if it were ordinary thunder tribulation, but five element tribulation represented the five source energies that formed all life in the universe. How could heavenly tribulation using this sort of power possibly be crossed easily?

“If Lin Ming can pass this, it will also be another great lucky chance for him. Lin Ming is too monstrous a genius. There are four or five aspects of him that are able to spur heavenly tribulation. All of that added up means that Lin Ming’s heavenly tribulation will be beyond terrifying!”

No one could help someone resist heavenly tribulation.

That person could only withstand the wrath of the Heavenly Dao themselves.

The powerful had the ability to resist a strong heavenly tribulation. But at the same time, their great strength would lead to an even more violent heavenly tribulation!

As Mo Riverbliss spoke, the blades of golden light that filled the world had already created a blindingly incandescent golden sea. Each blade of light had the strength to shear off a mountain top and sunder the earth!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s body had to bear thousands of metal tribulations at the same time. His protective true essence directly exploded and the metal tribulation cut into his flesh and blood.

Peng! Peng! Peng!

After absorbing the dragon bone relics, Lin Ming’s body had become as hard as divine iron. Even so, the gold tribulation of this heavenly tribulation was far too strong and there was far too much. The blades chopped through Lin Ming’s flesh, causing blood to spill out.

Soon after, Lin Ming was completely swallowed up by that golden light!

Looking at just that terrifying power and momentum, one could imagine that massive calamity Lin Ming had to resist.

The five element heavenly tribulation represented the will of the Heavenly Dao. The power of heavenly tribulation was specifically designed to kill geniuses, to kill those that dared defy the will of the heavens.

In this case, how could it be easy for anyone to contend with it?

Massive gashes thousands of feet long covered the ground. The earth was torn full of holes! Ye Rosewater watched with her own eyes as a palace of Carefree Island was struck by one of those golden blades and immediately fell apart!

Ye Rosewater acknowledged that she could resist at most two or three of those metal tribulations. But to resist hundreds or thousands of these golden swords, how could a mere Life Destruction martial artist still live amongst them?

Everyone held their breath. At this time, Lin Ming’s prestige in the hearts of Carefree Island’s Elders had completely turned around. Beside characters like Xiao Haogan and White Brook, who had dark intentions in their minds, all of the other Elders hoped that Lin Ming could truly complete his Ninefall, becoming a Great World King in the future and bringing glory back to their Carefree Island!

Before the appearance of the 33 Layered Heavens, a Great World King was a legend. But, for Lin Ming to reach 33 Layered Heavens in his Ninefall, that was a legend among legends. It was extremely likely he would become a Great World King!

Determining which was more valuable between such a genius and a heaven-step treasure like the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree, the Elders could clearly differentiate between them.

Just as Ye Rosewater was thinking, she actually saw that within that sea of golden light formed by countless golden blades, a deep red lotus began to sprout, recklessly blooming!

This red lotus was red to the point of being eye-catching, red to the point of being blindingly dazzling. The glorious aura that came out from this red lotus belonged to that of a great emperor, the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower!

Facing this terrifying metal tribulation, Lin Ming had decisively opened the grandmist space. In that instant, the world seemed to return to its most primordial time with a hazy grandmist energy floating about!

As the red lotus bloomed, the surging golden sea seemed to be split apart.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Lin Ming reappeared in everyone’s sight. His entire body was covered with blood!

Even with the grandmist space, the metal tribulation still rampantly cut down on his body, lacerating his skin and tearing his flesh. His protective true essence wasn’t able to block it at all!

And this was Lin Ming, someone who had fused with the supreme dragon bone. Any other martial artist would have long since been sliced to shreds and suffered a miserable death!

“My bones are alright, but too much of my skin and too many muscles have been torn…”

Lin Ming examined his body. Although an alarming amount of blood was flowing out, there weren’t any injuries to his bones or organs. Lin Ming’s strongest defense lay in his bones.

As long as his bones were safe, then Lin Ming could rely on the power of blood vitality he obtained after absorbing the Azure Dragon bone marrow to restore his wounds in several quarter hours.

However, the Heavenly Dao Laws would never give Lin Ming such a long time to recover. After the gold tribulation passed, a deep green light began to seethe within the tribulation clouds. The vast energy of the wilderness and nature surged outwards, condensing into light green rain that poured all over Carefree Island, like a summertime deluge!

Even the spirit plants in the medicinal fields began to rapidly grow as all plant life glowed with infinite vitality. Lingzhi, snow lotuses, ginseng, every precious herb began to grow like weeds as if thousands of years were passing with every single breath. If any of these common herbs were placed in the mortal world they would be priceless treasures, but here they grew like grass everywhere.

Lin Ming naturally wouldn’t relax because of such a beautiful and vibrant spring scene. He was very clear in his heart that this was wood tribulation!

Bang!

The ground below Lin Ming suddenly exploded. Dozens, hundreds of giant roots rose into the sky, wrapping around him.

Lin Ming stayed vigilant, unmoving like a mountain. Grandmist space crazily radiated out from his body. After these roots flew into the grandmist space, they were rapidly melted away by the Laws. Even so, a massive number of roots fell onto Lin Ming, tying him up in countless layers.

Wood tribulation – roots of the world!

Chapter 1124 – Brutal

In the five elements, wood origin energy had the attribute of growing endlessly. As Lin Ming was wrapped in these world roots, he suddenly drew out the Phoenix Blood Spear.

Although his entire body was bathed in blood at this time, his combat strength was still in its peak state. Not only did his blood vitality not show the slightest hint of diminishing, it actually billowed forth like a rocket, hurtling through the endless skies!

Ca!

With a wave of the Phoenix Blood Spear, a massive amount of sharp wood-attribute world roots were cut off. However, more and more world roots shot up from the ground, coiling around Lin Ming’s body like countless threads of twine.

Ka ka ka!

All of Lin Ming’s joints emitted explosive crackling sounds. These world roots held unimaginable power within them; even a saint artifact would have been instantly twisted to scrap!

“Phoenix blood essence, burn for me!”

Lin Ming roared. From inside his body, the phoenix blood essence lit up. A blazing golden light burst out from between his eyebrows and a dark gold phoenix phantom appeared behind Lin Ming, spreading out its wings wide.

The first three level Concepts of Fire had been fused together into one. After Lin Ming absorbed a massive amount of Heavenly Dao Law Fragments from his Ninefall, even though he hadn’t had time to thoroughly digest them, he had still unknowingly fused together the fourth level Concept of Fire.

The raging fire burnt through these world roots, scorching away their tenacity. At this time, Lin Ming opened all six gates, and with a sudden eruption of strength, all of these world roots were broken apart by Lin Ming.

“This… this is too terrifying! He is simply an ancient beast in human skin!”

“He’s lost so much blood and is wounded all over, yet he doesn’t seem affected at all. His blood vitality is still soaring to the heavens and his combat strength is still at its peak!”

“His endurance and recovery ability would leave anyone breathless with disbelief. There were hundreds of those metal tribulation swords, and now there are over a thousand of these world roots. Each metal tribulation blade and world root has the strength to massacre an early Divine Sea powerhouse, or even a middle Divine Sea genius. With 1000-2000 of these terrifying calamities headed his way, the strength of them added together is incredible. Yet, all of it was forcefully shouldered by Lin Ming! He must have consumed so much energy and yet his true essence doesn’t seem to have reduced at all!”

As everyone was speaking, the heavenly tribulation changed once again. It no longer came one at a time, but now two of them arrived together! This was dual water and fire tribulation!

If it was just fire tribulation then Lin Ming wouldn’t care. But now, water tribulation was added on! Water and fire dual tribulation!

Flames flew out from the clouds, forming a massive flame dragon that wildly soared through the air. It flowed from side to side, its body thicker than a water tank.

And on the other side was a blue water frost dragon. This water frost dragon had a terrifying impact force and corrosiveness, able to drown out all true essence.

The fire and water dragons issued deafening roars as they hurtled towards Lin Ming!

This was a completely overwhelming and bewildering attack!

By now, Lin Ming had experienced two great battles and he hadn’t even had a moment to catch his breath. Suddenly, he was engulfed by the flames, His entire body became a man-shaped pillar of fire that was surrounded by the blue water frost dragon!

Two cold and hot energies simultaneously invaded Lin Ming’s body. With Lin Ming’s body as a battlefield, they began a brutal battle!

The metal tribulation and wood tribulation had attacked the exterior of Lin Ming’s reformed body, but this fire tribulation and water tribulation had entered through his meridians, wanting to crush his dantian!

“Heretical God Sprout!”

Lin Ming’s mind moved. The Heretical God Sprout began to emit layers upon layers of brilliant divine light. Compressed true essence howled out, and those three flame leaves burst into radiance, magnifying each other and suppressing the raging flames within him.

The Heretical God Sprout was truly worthy of being called a transcendent divine might. It was even able to suppress the power of heavenly retribution to a certain degree!

But that water tribulation was somewhat difficult for Lin Ming to withstand. The intense corrosive strength flooded through him, causing Lin Ming’s flesh to wither. The pain from having his organs washed through with such acidic water could be imagined.

If it were a normal martial artist in his place then their bones would have long since melted from the acidic water and they would have turned into a puddle of bloody goo.

Even if it were Lin Ming, his entire body was still wracked with pain!

Not only did this water tribulation contain a deeply corrosive power, but it represented the most extreme polar cold, a cold that was colder than arctic ice. Lin Ming’s blood began to freeze over and his wounds were frozen solid with layers of ice. With slicing sounds, thorns of ice formed from within his body, piercing through his skin and organs, making blood spill out!

Lin Ming once again burnt the blood of the Ancient Phoenix. The blazing and roiling phoenix blood forcefully expelled the water tribulation.

However, before the water tribulation left, the ground below Lin Ming once again began to tremble. From the ground that was riddled with fissures, even larger cracks began to appear with alarming speed. Massive stone golems began to crawl out from these cracks!

These stone golems were each the size of a hill. Although they didn’t have any true essence, their physical strength had a force of tens of millions of jins. A single punch from them could collapse a mountain!

Before one wave ended, another wave had arrived.

This was earth tribulation!

As the Elders of Carefree Island saw this scene, all of them gasped. Who could still live through this?

Mo Riverbliss clenched her hands together. Seeing this scene, even she felt her palms turn wet with nervous sweat.

The existence of heavenly tribulation was not to temper and give lucky chances to those monstrous geniuses that had dared to violate the edicts of the Heavenly Dao.

Rather, it was the ultimate command to destroy them!

Heavenly tribulation was not easy to overcome!

Although it could be said to be an injustice to perish beneath heavenly tribulation, it wasn’t uncommon at all!

“Lin Ming, you must persist.” Mo Riverbliss said with bated breath. She was unable to calm her mood any longer. And beside her, although the usually tranquil Mo Eversnow had managed to maintain an appearance of calm, she was still wringing her hands together.

Now, Lin Ming could be said to be resisting three kinds of catastrophes!

He burnt the Ancient Phoenix blood, opened the Heretical God Force, and displayed the grandmist space. He had completely used all of his ultimate master moves!

Blood rained to the ground. His entire body was covered with horrifying wounds and vicious ice crystals pierced through his skin. Lin Ming’s body was like a broken bag of blood; it was difficult to look straight at him.

He forcefully used the Heretical God Sprout to suppress the power of fire, and then used the power of fire to dissolve the ice crystals in his body. Finally, he flourished the Phoenix Blood Spear, and with his formidable physical strength alone he shot towards the stone golems!

At this time, his inner true essence had become mixed up into a completely chaotic mess; he was unable to summon even the tiniest bit of it. All he could depend on was his own physical strength!

“Celestial Tyrant Manual – Hundred Layered Waves!”

Lin Ming shouted out loud and blue veins bulged up on his forehead. He opened all six gates and revolved their strength to the limit!

These stone golems each had tens of millions of jins of strength. They hurtled towards Lin Ming with crushing brute force!

This was a head-on matchup of savagery!

Bang!

The first stone golem was smashed apart by Lin Ming’s spear!

Although Lin Ming’s physical strength amounted to a dozen plus million jins, by using the Celestial Tyrant Manual’s Hundred Layered Waves, his strength could rise to an astonishing 30-50 million jins!

“This… this simply… this simply isn’t human at all!”

This was the second time that this Carefree Island Elder had said these words. As he saw Lin Ming smash apart a stone golem with brute strength, he was simply floored.

The flow of true essence within Lin Ming’s body had reversed, and his body simultaneously contained fire and water tribulations. He wasn’t even able to suppress his wounds. All of an ordinary martial artist’s meridians would have been torn and they would have died at this point, let alone continuing to fight. But as for Lin Ming, he forcefully resisted all this and shattered the earth tribulation stone golem.

As Lin Ming smashed apart the first stone golem, he could feel a great vibrating strength transmit up his arms, nearly causing the web of his palms to split open.

However, this agonizing pain actually caused Lin Ming to fall into an even greater fighting craze.

Smash! Smash! Smash!

The spear itself was a weapon meant for head-on battles. The only weapon that could sweep apart a battalion of a thousand soldiers was the spear!

A military general, no matter what circumstances in which they were fighting, would only use a spear, a lance, a great dragon crescent blade, or an overlord halberd!

This was because these weapons contained a great might and required immense strength. If one were to hold a spear and smash downwards, how could a mere single-handed sword block it?

In a situation of similar strength, one would only be able to avoid. This was because if a sword was used to resist such an attack, it wouldn’t be enough even if someone grasped the sword with both hands.

Kacha!

Kacha!

Stone golems were pulverized into pieces one at a time. Lin Ming’s blood vessels continued to tear apart even as the power of raging fire and freezing ice battled within his body. For him to still be able to display such a fierce combat strength in this situation was both thrilling and horrifying!

This savage and crazy fight lasted for almost half an incense stick of time. The 100 plus stone golems were completely demolished by Lin Ming, with nothing left behind but crushed stones. Underneath Lin Ming, a mountain of rocks was formed!

As for Lin Ming, he stood atop this rock mountain and supported himself with the Phoenix Blood Spear. The strong winds blew past him, sending strands of his hair fluttering in the wind. At this time, dyed crimson, he was like a war god of blood, causing those who saw him to shiver from their souls!

In this instant, everyone was astounded. It wasn’t solely Lin Ming’s strength, but his indomitable spirit, his tenacity for battle, and his will that seemed as if it could conquer the heavens!

The Elders of Carefree Island widened their eyes. Even someone like Xiao Haogan, who hated Lin Ming, couldn’t help but acknowledge that the magnitude of Lin Ming’s current achievements wasn’t just because he had many lucky chances, but because his will far surpassed all common sense!

“The heavenly tribulation… is… is it over?”

Ye Rosewater looked at Lin Ming, her heart racing. Currently, there was not a single part of Lin Ming’s body that was unharmed. He was dyed with blood and he looked like an Asura devil that had risen from hell.

If a mortal woman were to see Lin Ming now, they would blanch, possibly even fainting. But for Ye Rosewater, as Lin Ming’s appearance fell into her eyes, she actually felt as if Lin Ming was filled with infinite charm, leaving a heart-palpitating experience in her mind that would never be erased!

A martial artist’s looks could be altered using specific cultivation methods. One wouldn’t even be able to sense their original appearance with divine sense. They could even restore their youthful appearance by consuming a part of their cultivation. Moreover, because a martial artist’s body was tempered by energy again and again, there didn’t exist many martial artists that were too ugly. Thus, ugliness and beauty were not what martial artists searched for when seeking a lifelong companion.

What they looked at was a person’s will, their talent, experience, and all sorts of other intrinsic things.

Even though the current Lin Ming’s appearance was ferocious without the tiniest bit of handsomeness to be found, his hot-blooded aura of invincibility, his tenacious and unyielding outline, all of that deeply imprinted itself into Ye Rosewater’s heart.

And perhaps, it wasn’t just Ye Rosewater who felt this way too…

“The heavenly tribulation is over?”

“Lin Ming’s life force is already extremely weak. Bearing the dual water and fire tribulations and also fighting the stone golems isn’t something that a human should be able to accomplish. Lin Ming has overdrawn his vitality; I’m afraid he’s in a dangerous situation!”

Lin Ming’s blood vitality was indeed weak; nearly all of his blood had been drained out!

And at this time, Lin Ming suddenly turned around. A brilliant light flashed in his pupils.

Within Lin Ming’s body, the dragon marrow began to quietly stir, creating fresh blood. All of the blood vitality within Lin Ming’s body began to slowly burn.

“This… what kind of freakish life vitality is this!? Even at the point when he’s a lamp without oil, he’s still able to recover!”

“Heavens! His injuries are restoring themselves! This… this is simply a miracle!

Chapter 1130 – Refining Heavenly Tribulation

Originally, all of Lin Ming’s flesh had cracked apart, and the glistening white bones of his arms, legs, and chest were revealed. One could even count his ribs. There were also bones that were dislocated from the pressure. Even though Lin Ming’s bones were tough, they still couldn’t resist the continued grinding from the two primal chaos diagrams!

After his flesh reached such an appearance, his meridians and blood vessels also became tattered. His organs were almost squashed into mush, becoming a pile of messy goo.

The only complete body part he had was his brain. Within the protection of his skull, his spiritual sea hadn’t been damaged at all. Even so, for a person devolved to such a miserable state, there wasn’t any meaning left in having a complete brain.

This sort of condition could have been described as undoubtable death!

If a normal martial artist were to look like Lin Ming now then they would have already completely died! A Life Destruction martial artist had a stronger life force than a common mortal, but if their heart was pierced, their head was cut off, and their blood had all drained away, they would still die. This was the Heavenly Dao Laws.

Only during the crossing of Life Destruction when one’s body disintegrated could a martial artist preserve their life. That was also because this process was supported by the Heavenly Dao Laws, thus they wouldn’t die.

In this sort of situation, it was impossible for Lin Ming to live without some sort of transcendent divine pill, much less rely on his own regenerative ability to recover.

But now, a miracle was occurring in front of everyone present!

They watched on helplessly as Lin Ming’s flesh and blood began to grow back!

The dazzling white bones were covered again with a layer of fascia. Then, the blood vessels moved over them like glistening red vines, spreading everywhere. Afterwards, the meridians reformed, the organs repaired themselves, and the muscles were completely reborn, their lines even stronger and more perfect than before.

Then, his wounds began to stitch back together, with fresh flesh rapidly regenerating at a rate visible to the eye. His flesh glistened and shined, like translucent red crystal!

Even his withered hair fell off, and new hair grew out from the old, passing down over his ears. These hairs, after being tempered in energy, sparkled with a lustrous sheen. Their silk-like texture even contained the profound mysteries of the Laws. If Lin Ming’s hair grew long enough, it could even be plucked out and used as a material for a saint artifact divine bow’s bowstring! This was proof of just how tough it was!

At this time, Lin Ming seemed as if he had almost achieved the boundary of the legendary diamond Vajra body, an immaculate and immortal body!

“Impossible! This is impossible! He should have absolutely died, just how is such a heaven-defying turn of events possible!?”

“What happened!? This can’t be!”

White Brook and Xiao Haogan had expressions as if their fathers had died as they watched Lin Ming’s body be reborn anew.

Looking at the present situation, there was an extremely high chance Lin Ming would be able to cross the heavenly tribulation. At that time, with Lin Ming’s terrifying talent, it shouldn’t be a problem at all for him to become a Great World King. The two of them would be in an extremely miserable position!

“What do we do? What can we do?” Xiao Haogan asked, at a complete loss.

“How the hell would I know! At this time there is nothing we can do to change the past. If Lin Ming dies then that would be perfect, but even after being pushed to the brink of death and looking like he did, he still didn’t die. His life is far too tough! Chances are that he won’t die this time. We must not make enemies with him anymore, especially on the surface!”

White Brook wasn’t an idiot. Now that Lin Ming had crossed Ninefall, his status in Carefree Island would be like the sun in the sky. With Mo Riverbliss supporting him, even a Highest Elder like him would be a joke in front of Lin Ming. If he tried to make enemies with Lin Ming, wasn’t that just asking to die?

The yin yang dao diagrams still spun as before, pressing down on Lin Ming. In that instant, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open. His vision was like two divine lights piercing through the endless night, shining through the vast space.

His strength had returned!

Lin Ming suddenly clenched his fists together. With every movement, his joints seemed to explode with loud crackling sounds. He could feel a surge of energy rushing through his body. The power of thunder, fire, yin, and yang heavenly tribulations, as well as the tremendous power of the melted dragon bone relics rampaged within him. But, he forcefully suppressed them all!

This feeling as if his entire body was filled with energy caused Lin Ming’s blood to boil over. He concentrated his energy into his dantian, letting out a long and loud cry!

Hah – !

A terrifying sound wave burst out in all directions. With a deafening rumble, countless sheets of earth and stone were raised up by this sound wave. The clouds for several hundreds of miles were washed away, and even the tribulation clouds seemed to be affected as they faintly trembled.

Happy! Awesome!

Lin Ming laughed out loud, his bellows ringing through the skies!

He had never imagined he would feel such an explosive strength in his body as today. He was like a volcano on the brink of eruption, every step he took shattered the earth!

“Good young man! How did he do this!?” The Elders of Carefree Island looked on in utter shock. This sudden reversal was simply like a dream.

“Is this because of those beads he swallowed? Although I couldn’t see just what those beads were, they shouldn’t have been a transcendent divine medicine. Those beads contained a power that was far too tyrannical; they should have been some rare and fierce heavenly treasure. If Lin Ming swallowed such medicine at his peak state he might blow up from the energy, much less now.”

“I thought that Lin Ming’s body would burst apart after swallowed those beads, but such a change actually occurred. Just what secrets does he have on him?”

There was not a single Elder of Carefree Island that could understand what happened to Lin Ming’s body. Let alone them, even Mo Eversnow and Mo Riverbliss were looking on, dumbfounded. They too had no idea what was happening!

“This is absolutely not an effect of the dragon bone relics. The dragon bone relics are a violent and wild energy, and it is already extremely difficult for Lin Ming to withstand them with his body, much less for them to help regenerate his flesh. Could it… could it be… that black mystery bead?” Mo Eversnow suddenly thought. This was the only possible explanation. But just what was that black mystery bead? It actually had the strength to defy the power of heavenly tribulation! Even a top transcendent divine pill would pale in comparison!

At this time, the heavenly tribulation was continuing around Lin Ming!

Yin yang tribulation was truly worthy of being called the strongest level of the nine heavenly tribulations. It was a calamity of essence, energy, and the divine. Lin Ming had crossed the tribulation of the soul, of his flesh and blood, and now all that was left over was the tribulation of his dantian!

And at this time, Lin Ming’s body had been restored to almost its peak state. How hard could it be to survive one more tribulation?

In the sky, the dual yin and yang energies twisted together, forming dao runes and streams that constantly flushed into Lin Ming’s meridians, fusing together with the sealed thunder and fire tribulation within Lin Ming’s body!

The thunder tribulation became increasingly wild, the fire tribulation became that much more fierce!

These two energies had been suppressed by the Heretical God Sprout from the very start, but that was only a temporary suppression. As for refining them, that was not simple at all. Especially after Lin Ming had encountered catastrophe after catastrophe; just when did he have the chance to refine them?

But now was different!

“Thunder and fire tribulation, I hope you had your fill of hurting me. This time, I’ll be the one to refine you!”

Lin Ming shouted out loud and the Heretical God Force erupted. The energy of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation, together with the yin yang tribulation, was all completely suppressed by the Heretical God Sprout!

“Be refined by me!”

The Heretical God Force was a transcendent divine might!

Only a transcendent divine might could refine the power of heavenly tribulation. If an ordinary martial artist’s cultivation method was used to refine heavenly tribulation, all that would happen would be a tremendous counterattack!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Within Lin Ming’s dantian, energy boiled like magma, erupting like a volcano!

Such an impact placed a great pressure on Lin Ming’s dantian. But Lin Ming steeled his mind; he would thoroughly refine this yin yang tribulation and thunder and fire tribulation!

It had to be known that the power of heavenly tribulation contained immense benefits!

Lin Ming had crossed eight levels of heavenly tribulation and also over half of the ninth level of heavenly tribulation. The advantage this had to his flesh, blood, and bones was unfathomable.

His battle spirit had also broken through the elementary gold level, jumping straight over gold small success and reaching gold large success!

Even the Phoenix Blood Spear had transformed from a saint artifact to a spirit artifact after breeding its own source artifact spirit. This was something that a supreme elder might not be able to accomplish even in 100,000 years!

In this situation, Lin Ming still wasn’t satisfied with withstanding the baptism of heavenly tribulation. He wanted to refine the power of heavenly tribulation and use it for himself!

“Lin Ming, he… he is… heavens! He is refining heavenly tribulation!”

“This… refining heavenly tribulation!? He… he is far too crazy!!!”

Heavenly tribulation was not some trifling matter. When an extreme genius martial artist similar to Lin Ming crossed heavenly tribulation, they would be absolutely cautious lest they enrage the heavenly tribulation and cause a mutation to occur. Once heavenly tribulation arrived, all they could do was silently withstand it, allowing their body, dantian, revolving core or inner world, and soul to accept the baptism of heavenly tribulation. They had to use their own true essence to disperse the power of heavenly tribulation.

Who would dare to directly refine heavenly tribulation?

That was simply suicidal!

But now, Lin Ming was doing exactly this!

If the Heavenly Dao wishes to destroy me then I shall control the Heavenly Dao and make it my army of a million soldiers! I will have it ride through the endless space with me, battling through the rivers of stars!

The road of martial arts was originally defying the will of the heavens. And Lin Ming had the heart and soul to reverse the heavens themselves!

Chapter 1131 – Perfectly Crossing Tribulation

The power of four different kinds of heavenly tribulation raged through Lin Ming’s body. And, the power of the dragon bone relics also rampaged through him!

Lin Ming’s thoughts sank into his dantian. A torrential vortex appeared at the Heretical God Sprout inside. The power of the thunder and fire tribulation was completely sucked in by the Heretical God Sprout!

Compress! Compress again!

Blue veins bulged out on Lin Ming’s forehead. Even though his body had been reborn, he still felt as if his dantian would explode from withstanding this pressure!

“Lin Ming, divert all the power of the dragon bone relics and the other unnecessary energy into the threshold of life and death! Revolve the Celestial Tyrant Manual!”

Mo Eversnow’s voice suddenly sounded out in Lin Ming’s ear.

As Lin Ming heard her, a sharp light flashed in his eyes.

That was right! The threshold of life and death!

The method to cultivate the Eight Inner Hidden Gates that was recorded within the Celestial Tyrant Manual was slightly different to the method within the Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians.

The Eight Inner Hidden Gates was a large boundary, but in truth it could also be divided into two boundaries instead. The first boundary included the first six of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, and the second boundary included the last two of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. The last two gates were called the gates that stood upon the threshold of life and death, the Gate of Life and the Gate of Death!

The threshold of life and death was one of the most difficult barriers of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates to pass. In order to break through the threshold of life and death, one had to build a foundation and then pile up a massive amount of resources before making a breakthrough in a single go. In the Eight Inner Hidden Gates of body transformation, every step was more difficult than the last. As for the final Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, that was even more difficult than rising to the heavens!

“Open!”

Lin Ming shouted out. The power of yin yang tribulation along with the power of the dragon bone relics rushed into his meridians. They rushed through his eight pulse points, impacting the threshold of life and death!

With a loud banging sound, Lin Ming’s body shook as he spat out a mouthful of blood!

As Lin Ming vomited this blood, his complexion paled. He grit his teeth and revolved the energy within him once more.

At this time, behind Lin Ming, a deep red Prime Emperor Lotus Flower slowly bloomed. The grandmist space radiated outwards.

Heavenly Demon force field!

This was one of the Primordius martial intent’s three great force fields –

Heavenly Demon! Heavenly Mortal! Heavenly God!

Although it was only a third of a complete transcendent divine might, just what kind of existence was Empyrean Primordius? He was a peak character even amongst Empyreans. His Primordius martial intent was not some ordinary transcendent divine might. The chaos grandmist was the source of the universe.

Underneath the enveloping of this grandmist space, whether it was the energy from the dragon bone relics or the power of heavenly tribulation, everything was forced to submit, and the impact was even greater!

Bang!

The second impact!

The life and death threshold within Lin Ming’s body was like a divine drum made from the skin of an archaic vicious beast’s skin. With every impact of energy, it would release a terrifying sound.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

Every sound was like a bell from the heavens, pure and clear, echoing through the heavens and earth, deafening all who heard it!

The drumming grew increasingly loud and more vibrant. All of the blood within Lin Ming’s body boiled with excitement. The power of his blood vitality was so strong that it could be seen with the naked eye. It was like a monstrous pillar of flame that rocketed to the heavens, flying straight through the skies and piercing through the tribulation cloud!

This vast scene caused everyone to feel bewildered.

“Lin Ming is really controlling the power of heavenly tribulation! He has basically crossed heavenly tribulation!”

“Yes! If there isn’t an accident then he won’t be in any further danger. With such a deep blessing from the world itself, how could any accident happen to him?”

“Unbelievable, we witnessed the birth of a Great World King!”

Everyone held their breaths. Every scene passing in front of them meant that Lin Ming would soon cross heavenly tribulation, and complete the ninth stage of Life Destruction!

The yin yang tribulation and the power contained within the dragon bone relics constantly weakened. But, the barrier of the life and death threshold was also being worn away.

Without knowing just how many ringing impacts had occurred, there was finally an explosive sound like rolling thunder that caused everyone’s ears to tingle with numbness!

The life and death threshold had finally been broken through! All of Lin Ming’s meridians were cleared. Most of the yin yang tribulation’s power had been used up. As for the dragon bone relics’ essence, the remainder gradually precipitated into Lin Ming’s flesh and blood.

This strength was far from being able to open either the Gate of Life or Gate of Death. But to Lin Ming, breaking through the life and death threshold was more than enough.

Breaking through the threshold of life and death was the first step to opening the Gate of Life and Gate of Death. This was the equivalent to opening one of the many locks that bound the Gate of Life and Gate of Death.

At this point, Lin Ming had thoroughly crossed the yin yang tribulation!

All that remained within his body were the remnants of the thunder and fire tribulations. At this time, Lin Ming’s body was in its peak state. The surviving power of thunder and fire within him couldn’t threaten him anymore.

“Heretical God Sprout, compress again!”

The vortex formed by the Heretical God Sprout became increasingly violent. The massive amount of thunder and fire tribulation was forcefully sucked in. As the power of thunder and fire flowed into the Heretical God Sprout, it began to glow with an incandescent divine light!

For a time, the six leaves of the Heretical God Sprout seemed to turn to molten gold. Purple and red runes began to form atop the surface of the leaves. These dao patterns came in all sorts of different shapes. Some were like small tripods and some were like golden swords. The runes all fell onto the Heretical God Sprout, and finally, a bizarre change began to occur!

The Heretical God Sprout grew taller and taller, and finally it distorted and twigs began to bud out!

In just a few breaths of time, the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation was rapidly consumed. By the time the Heretical God Sprout stopped growing, over 90% of the power of thunder and fire tribulation had been used up.

The Heretical God Sprout had actually absorbed the power of heavenly tribulation as nourishment for its own growth. This ability was truly worthy of being called a transcendent divine might; it was even able to control the Heavenly Dao and use it!

The current Heretical God Sprout had doubled in height. In the past if it was a sprout, then now it was a seedling.

A pair of fresh new leaves emerged from the crown of the seedling, one red and one purple.

These two leaves were of the same shape: both resembled small primal chaos diagrams. There were numerous profound dao patterns crawling over the surface of these leaves. Without a doubt, these were leaves that evolved from the thunder and fire heavenly tribulation!

The power of heavenly tribulation had ended up becoming a part of the Heretical God Seedling!

“Mm? This is…”

Lin Ming’s thoughts sank within himself and he summoned the Heretical God Force of the Heretical God Seedling. Flames came from his left hand and thunder from his right. The two energies actually exuded an aura similar to the Heavenly Dao.

This was the power of heavenly tribulation!

Lin Ming deeply gasped. A transcendent divine might was indeed a transcendent divine might; it was even able to wield the power of the Heavenly Dao for itself. After the Heretical God Sprout absorbed the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation, that power was then integrated into the Heretical God Force. In the future, as long as Lin Ming used the Heretical God Force, he would be able to control the power of heavenly tribulation to a certain degree. Although it was weak, this was still strength that represented the Heavenly Dao! How could anyone dare to underestimate it?

“Hahaha! Great!”

Lin Ming faced the heavens and laughed, his voice echoing through the world. In that instant, he was like a butterfly that had broken out from its cocoon. His essence, energy, and divine had all risen beyond expectations!

The power of his blood vitality was like that of an ancient vicious beast. His mortal body nearly resembled an indestructible diamond Vajra body. His endurance had long since reached an unbelievable boundary. His true essence was as deep as a vast sea! Every time he moved, every time he raised his hand or stepped forwards, he would exude the aura of the Laws, forming faint lights around him. These were the Law runes that had been carved into his body. They thoroughly fused into his flesh and blood, engraving themselves into his marrow!

Now, Lin Ming had finally crossed heavenly tribulation! At this time, Lin Ming could be called an existence that surpassed the Heavenly Dao! Crossing heavenly tribulation and stepping beyond the Heavenly Dao meant that one’s strength could even resist the Heavenly Dao Laws in the future!

This sort of person’s fate was no longer controlled by the Heavenly Dao. This sort of person could truly say…

My life is controlled not by the heavens but by me!

“He’s done it! He’s reached the ninth stage of Life Destruction! This is the true ninth stage of Life Destruction, one that far surpasses all other ordinary geniuses!”

“After crossing these nine heavenly tribulations, his strength must be far from comparable to how it was in the past. The advantages he obtained from this are unimaginable!”

The Elders of Carefree Island began to cry out in horror and awe.

33 Layered Heavens, 99 mile origin energy cloud, nine heavenly tribulations of nine by nine Life Destruction!

This was likely the limit of the ninth stage of Life Destruction! It was simply incredible!

“This child’s achievements will know no limit in the future. If it were a normal genius, then even if they were like Lin Ming and had enough lucky chances accumulated to undergo that sort of heavenly tribulation just now, they would have absolutely died!” An Elder cried out, his voice thick with emotion. Such a heaven-shaking lucky chance was not something that just anyone could handle. This sort of massive lucky chance could also be considered a great calamity!

A peak genius was said to have a destiny like a ray of light and the life of an emperor. But, the truth was that sometimes, this was not because they were lucky, but because they could take all catastrophes that fell upon their head and turn them into lucky chances!

Destiny was not equal to luck.

The so-called luck meant that if one were lucky, they could casually walk outside and find a treasure. Someone lucky would often find the cave dwellings and inheritances of ancient supreme elders.

But, to have a great destiny was completely different. That was the ability to turn the tables. If one went into a mystic realm where there were nine chances of death and one chance of survival, someone with a great destiny would have the ability to return. Even in a brutal life or death competition with countless powerhouses embroiled within it, someone with a great destiny would be able to grasp that fleeting chance of hope and gain victory!

Their destiny came from their own self-confidence, strength, talent, and ability to remain calm even under the threat of death, never falling into despair and never giving up!

And Lin Ming was one of these people.

From the time he was at the Pulse Condensation realm when he went to the Divine Phoenix Realm, or the times afterwards when he went to the Demon God Imperial Palace, Eternal Demon Abyss, Road of Emperor, and other such places, he didn’t discover these places because of his good luck. Rather, these places were known by many people. Numerous individuals entered and yet only Lin Ming was able to obtain the greatest benefit from within.

This was a manifestation of his destiny!

These nine levels of heavenly tribulation were also the same. These nine levels of heavenly tribulation had been horrifying to an unbelievable degree; even Lin Ming had nearly died!

If Lin Ming wasn’t strong and his foundation deep, with a combat strength that far surpassed other martial artists’ at his level, as well as his dual body and energy cultivation and his extremely tough body, then he would have already been turned to ash by the second stage of heavenly tribulation that had come.

The reason that Lin Ming had been able to survive was completely because he never gave up, because his will had supported him throughout. If there was ever a moment when his heart had wavered then he would have been annihilated in a puff of smoke! But finally, in a despairing situation, Lin Ming had still searched for that final thread of hope. At the precipice of death, he thought to use the supreme dragon bone relics to resist the power of heavenly tribulation. He had risked everything on that final bet, never giving up, and finally he was able to create a miracle.

With all of these various factors combined together, it was simply impossible to recreate such an event.

“Lin Ming… he really did it. Although I placed great hopes on Lin Ming, I never did expect him to kill Tian Mingzi, because that was originally an impossible mission to begin with. But now, I can finally see, I can see that perhaps it really might be possible…” Mo Riverbliss murmured to Mo Eversnow. Although she had great confidence in Lin Ming from the start, Tian Mingzi had also been an extreme talent that was able to become a Great World King. As for Lin Ming, who didn’t have much support, it was simply too trying to have him contend with Tian Mingzi, who was tens of thousands of years older than he was and also had the support of a Holy Land behind him. It was far too difficult to do that. Even if Lin Ming became a Great World King, he might not necessarily be able to compete with Tian Mingzi.

Mo Eversnow took a deep breath. As she stared at Lin Ming, a strange and complex light was in her eyes. How could she not know how difficult it was to accomplish those things that she had asked from Lin Ming? Even so, Lin Ming had been able to blaze his own trail through the heavens and earth, defying all odds again and again!

“Lin Ming, your spear!” Mo Riverbliss flung out her hand. The Phoenix Blood Spear issued an excited cry, turning into a beam of light as it flew towards Lin Ming.

In that moment, the spear light was beautifully blinding.

Chapter 1134 – Clearing the Snakes

“Elder Liu, you are a veteran senior of Carefree Island. Of the three Highest Elders, you are the oldest. For these last tens of thousands of years, although I haven’t publicly appeared, I still stayed deep in Carefree Palace. I’ve been watching many things that you’ve done and I believe I have a deep understanding of your character. Before this, I spoke with Elder Zhou and he revealed some matters to me. As far as I know, in these last days, you, Elder Zhou, and Elder White have all been very close to each other, right?”

Mo Riverbliss’s light question caused Elder Liu’s heart to skip a beat as it fell onto his ear!

The Elder Zhou that Mo Riverbliss mentioned was the last of the three Highest Elders. When Mo Riverbliss wanted to give the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree to Lin Ming to help him break through his Ninefall, everyone in the sect had opposed this action. And White Brook, being the one that was so adamantly against it, had united many of the Elders together to resist Mo Riverbliss’s orders.

And in fact, the other two Highest Elders didn’t welcome Mo Riverbliss. No one wished that there would be another overlord hovering over their heads and stealing their authority.

In this sort of situation, they had tended to favor White Brook from the beginning.

But afterwards, Lin Ming had perfectly crossed his heavenly tribulation and achieved a complete nine by nine Life Destruction and then their thoughts had made a complete 180 change. Lin Ming’s performance had been far too magnificent and splendid. If Lin Ming could truly become a Great World King then Carefree Island would be able to ascend to a World King level Holy Land. And as their senior Elder, even sharing just a tiny bit of the soup would be an unbelievable advantage! This was absolutely not something that a single top heaven-step treasure like the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree could compare with.

Thus, they had begun to favor Mo Riverbliss instead. Now that they heard Mo Riverbliss suddenly mentioning old accounts and especially in a situation where she was dividing the Elders and talking to them one at a time, no one knew what anyone else would say, so all of their hearts were rife with fear and trepidation.

Once someone else confessed all of their matters, if they continued to be silly and help White Brook out then that would cause Mo Riverbliss to have an extremely bad impression of them. Then, even if Carefree Island rapidly ascended in the future they still wouldn’t be able to share in the profit and would only be regarded as an outsider who would be continually marginalized.

Ever since ancient times, there had been no right or wrong in struggles of power. Those self-proclaimed righteous and stubborn men of integrity would often die in the most miserable manner. Whether they were good or evil didn’t matter. All that existed in struggles of power were a few simple words – submit to me and prosper or oppose me and perish!

Elder Liu could already see that this woman, Mo Riverbliss, was not easy to deal with. Before now, she had quietly stayed in Carefree Palace because she didn’t want her status to be revealed. But now that she had, she would exert full and complete control so that when Carefree Island became a World King level Holy Land in the future, her authority would be smoother. What she wanted was for her voice to be the only one that mattered within the island.

As for White Brook and Xiao Haogan, they already stood opposite to Mo Riverbliss. Even if they sensed the winds and tried to switch sides, it was far too late. For those rulers with absolute control, what they had least was trust in others. And history had repeatedly proven that those rulers who easily trusted others and gave power to others would suffer tragic fates! In particular, trusting the enemy even once was the most stupid of behaviors!

It was obvious that Mo Riverbliss planned on being the only voice in the Council of Elders. Moreover, she wanted to establish her prestige. White Brook and Xiao Haogan would thus be punished as a warning to all others who dared to stand against her.

“Senior, I have something I must confess to you.”

After Elder Liu understood all of this, his choice became immediately clear. Mo Riverbliss did not lack ambitions, nor did she lack the means to accomplish them. Following her would be much better than following White Brook and his mixed band of supporters.

………

As time slowly passed, all of the Elders, besides White Brook and Xiao Haogan, had talked alone with Mo Riverbliss.

This caused Xiao Haogan to feel increasingly uneasy. Although he seemed relatively calm on the surface, the truth was that his heart was rapidly racing in nervousness, as if he were standing on pins and needles.

“What are you so panicked about? Mo Riverbliss hasn’t even done anything and yet you feel so pressured. Don’t be confused about your own position and stop shaking your legs. If she really did anything then you can’t just stretch out your neck and accept it.”

White Brook chided Xiao Haogan with a true essence sound transmission. Xiao Haogan forced a smile and nodded. He certainly knew what White Brook was trying to say, but could he feel that way in front of someone like Mo Riverbliss, where he didn’t even have the faintest bit of superiority? After Mo Riverbliss had borrowed the momentum of Lin Ming crossing his heavenly tribulation and split up the Elders, now, whether it was her own strength or her position in the hearts of the Elders, she surpassed White Brook in every aspect.

At this time, the minor dimension in front of Xiao Haogan trembled and then a white-clothed Mo Riverbliss appeared in front of everyone.

“Elder White, Elder Xiao, come with me…” Mo Riverbliss faintly said.

White Brook’s heart tightened. As he looked at the minor dimensional gate behind Mo Riverbliss, he felt as if he didn’t have the courage to step in at all.

This Carefree Palace was under the control of Mo Riverbliss to begin with. Not just that, but Mo Riverbliss’s strength surpassed theirs by several times. Who knew what would happen once they entered that minor dimension!

Xiao Haogan also thought of this. His complexion became increasingly ugly.

White Brook forced a smile and said, “Fairy Mo, if there is any matter then you can speak it right here!”

As White Brook spoke, all of the other Elders began to feel a bit of pity for him. In truth, everything that White Brook had done was a normal response for someone who was accustomed to holding great power. It was human nature for a person to not wish to cup their hands across their chest and hand over whatever authority they had. Moreover, because of White Mirrorjade’s situation, White Brook had wanted to kill Lin Ming. To a Highest Elder, killing a simple junior disciple to set an example wasn’t a problem at all. Unfortunately, he had messed with the wrong young man and had ended up kicking himself in the face.

Now, Mo Riverbliss was clearly looking to push White Brook over the cliff. At the very least he would lose his current high status. And most of the other Elders of Carefree Island had likely betrayed White Brook by now, especially those that had been close to him. They all rushed to privately contact Mo Riverbliss to display their utmost loyalty to her.

After all, they weren’t sure if anyone else had betrayed White Brook and revealed what all the other Elders had done. If those people had confessed all of their wrongdoings while they tried to hide what they knew, that would be the actions of an idiot.

On the other hand, if they clearly revealed all that they knew then that would be a sign of their loyalty; there would be no loss for them.

It could only be said that humans were inconsistent and fickle beings, quickly tempted towards extremes. Now that they faced White Brook, they all felt a bit guilty in their hearts. This sort of feeling didn’t feel too good. If one felt guilty for too long then this guilt would turn to hate. This was the subtlety of human psychology.

‘If you make me feel guilty and fearful, then I will no longer wish to see you or even talk to you!’

Thus, imperceptibly, White Brook and Xiao Haogan had already been isolated from the others.

“Oh? We can speak here too.” Mo Riverbliss spoke as if she were in a very jolly mood. She faintly smiled at the other Elders and said, “Then, may all the other Elders besides Elder Xiao and Elder White wait outside.”

Mo Riverbliss’s words left Xiao Haogan and White Brook startled. As they looked at everyone, they discovered that they were all evading their eyes.

Island Master Xiao Skywhite was the first to leave. Then, everyone began to scatter without a single one remaining. There were even some people that were much faster than the others in fear that they would leave a bad impression on Mo Riverbliss.

As the other Elders departed, the space where Mo Riverbliss, White Brook, and Xiao Haogan were was completely sealed up.

When White Brook saw this, he mirthlessly smiled, “Hahaha! I never thought this would be! The world of martial artists is truly a reflection of human nature! To think that I, White Brook, would one day suffer a fate like this and become no different from a plague. Everyone who sees me fears me and everyone wishes to cut apart all relations they had with me! Your methods are truly wonderful!”

White Brook grit his teeth as he looked at Mo Riverbliss. And behind him, Xiao Haogan was already shaking in his boots. Facing Mo Riverbliss, he felt an unbelievably strong pressure. This woman could take their lives whenever she wished.

“My methods aren’t much at all. It’s just that after Lin Ming crossed a nine by nine Life Destruction, whether it be in strength or prestige, I now occupy the absolute superiority. You are no longer my match. I could have let you go, it’s only that… I will no longer leave behind even the smallest chance for my current enemies or my potential enemies in the future. This is the lesson that my father paid a deep price to carve into my heart! I will no longer abide a snake that is looking at me from behind. Even if you do not have the strength to threaten me, it is possible that you will betray my information to my blood enemy in the future, or you may even sell out Lin Ming. Or in the future when I have troubles, you may even kick me when I’m down! You already have a festering hatred of me in your heart. Since we cannot resolve our issues, why should I allow you any chance to seek revenge?”

The annihilation of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands had left a lifelong lesson in Mo Riverbliss’s heart. It was because the old Holy Lord of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands didn’t act against Tian Mingzi ahead of time that they all suffered such a fate.

How could Mo Riverbliss allow the same mistake to occur again? Once White Brook realized that her hated enemy was Tian Mingzi, then even the spirit artifact scroll she had all the Elders sign might be useless. Tian Mingzi possibly had his own ways to remove such a curse. At that time, Tian Mingzi would find out about her as well as about the existence of Mo Eversnow and Lin Ming. The consequences of this could be imagined!

“Good! You are ruthless enough! I acknowledge that I deserve this punishment. So, let me see just how you’ll dispose of me!”

White Brook coldly said as he flung his sleeves open. In his opinion, Mo Riverbliss was merely relieving him of his duties. At most she would imprison him, not kill him. Otherwise, if a senior Elder died because of a power struggle then there would inevitably be fissures. Although no one would dare to do anything to her, she still had to be cautious of the effects her actions on public opinion!

If her killing sins were too great, it would be easy to lose the will of the people.

Mo Riverbliss seemed to see through White Brook’s thoughts. She cunningly smiled. “You seem to think you’re safe? As if you have nothing to fear? What a pity… your speculations are all wrong…”

“Mm!?” White Brook’s heart shook as he suddenly stepped backwards. He reached out to trace his own spatial ring, but at this time all he felt was a blinding haze before him; Mo Riverbliss had already arrived right in front of him!

Bang!

White Brook couldn’t see how Mo Riverbliss had acted. In only an instant, all he felt was a dizzying pain in his head. It was as if he had fallen into some unknown space with ice and snow falling all around him, enveloping the world.

White Brook wanted to shatter this world, but he felt his body become increasingly powerless. His consciousness and divine sense seemed to leave his body. This feeling was like a mortal being placed in front of the vastness of nature; there was no chance of resisting…

The difference was too great!

……..

Three days later, everyone saw Xiao Haogan and White Brook in Carefree Palace. They followed behind Mo Riverbliss. There didn’t seem to be anything different about them, except that they displayed absolute loyalty towards Mo Riverbliss. Moreover, there was also a deep sense of awe and fear shining from their eyes!

This sort of look was like someone who had their mind controlled and had a slave seal planted within them. Of course, no one dared to question Mo Riverbliss. They could only suppress their own suspicious and pretend to not notice anything. Everyone began to increasingly dread this woman known as Mo Riverbliss. Without a doubt, she was not some bleeding heart individual. For whoever disobeyed her, their fate would truly be tragic! Xiao Haogan and White Brook were the perfect examples of this!

No matter what Mo Riverbliss did to Xiao Haogan and White Brook, at least they hadn’t died. As for the ordinary disciples of Carefree Island, none of them knew about this situation to begin with, thus changes in public opinion never occurred. Like this, Mo Riverbliss calmly controlled all of Carefree Island while removing all of her enemies. Not only were there no negative effects, but her authority instead rose to an unprecedented level.

Chapter 1138 – The Little Girl Who Eats Violet Sun Crystals

The treasures that the early Divine Transformation man took out immediately attracted everyone’s eyes.

The specialty of this trade fair that attracted so many people was its strange and uncommon treasures.

“How interesting. Let me take a look.”

A tall, thin youth with a forked beard took that bone shard and investigated it.

Another youth took that white rubber object and also studied it.

“Miss Mo, what do you think those two objects are?” Lin Ming asked Mo Eversnow with a true essence sound transmission.

Mo Eversnow thought for a moment and then said, “That bone shard has a language written on it that stems from an extremely ancient era of the Divine Realm. It should be the language once used by the Saint race… that is already billions of years, even a matter of 10 billion years ago. At that time, the Laws of this world hadn’t yet changed and body transformation techniques were quite mainstream in the world of martial artists. That incomplete bone shard should be similar to a jade slip, or rather, it’s best to call it a bone slip. There should be some type of records located within it.”

As Mo Eversnow spoke, these objects were passed to Lin Ming. Lin Ming investigated them for a moment. As Mo Eversnow had said, the bone slip really did contain many types of records. The textures and lines were extremely mystical; Lin Ming wasn’t able to understand them at all.

“Miss Mo, can you understand the writing within this?”

Mo Eversnow replied, “Only a small part of it. In the past when I was studying the Celestial Tyrant Manual, I found that it deviated towards the language of the ancient Divine Realm eras. Thus, I referenced many ancient Divine Realm texts. Gradually, I was able to read a little bit of it. This bone slip should record some type of cultivation method, but if you really wish to unravel its meaning then that will require a period of time.”

Besides the bone slip there was also that rubber-like object. Lin Ming looked at it and found that it really did look like rubber. It was only when he tried to pinch it a bit did he discover that it was actually very hard and also very heavy. Even though it was a very small object, it weighed dozens of jins.

Mo Eversnow said, “I cannot tell what the origin of this is, but it’s probably some magic weapon fragment or array disc fragment. Although there are some mysteries in it, far too long of a time has passed and it is too incomplete to be of use or value. However, buying it as part of a collection would be quite nice.”

Mo Eversnow roughly guessed what the two objects were, more or less correctly.

Although the others didn’t have Mo Eversnow’s vision, they also investigated the objects and were able to approximate that they were ancient fragments of some sort. The chance of comprehending anything useful from such fragmented and incomplete ancient treasures like this wasn’t too likely, although they were interested in collecting them. However, these wealthy young masters weren’t idiots. If the price was too high then they wouldn’t buy them.

“Mister Luo, how much is that bone shard?”

The fork-bearded youth was the first to ask a question. He reclined in a comfortable position, vigorously rubbing the breasts of the young woman in his arms.

“3 million violet sun stones.” The Divine Transformation man referred to as Mister Luo smiled. This wasn’t a strange price.

“3 million violet sun stones isn’t too bad. I can buy this to play around with a bit. I’ll pay the price.” The fork-bearded youth gaily said, his eyes sweeping over the martial artists behind him.

It was impossible for anyone to contend with this fork-bearded youth for a bone shard that none of them could comprehend anything from. The youth himself was at the middle Divine Sea and he was extremely talented. His background was also good and he held a position of great status in this group.

The lack of reaction satisfied the fork-bearded youth. Just as he thought he had the deal, a voice of disagreement rang out, “I’ll pay 3.5 million violet sun stones. This fellow, how about passing over this bone shard to me? I’m quite interested in collecting artifacts like this.”

“Mm?” The youth frowned. In truth, he also discovered that there were some records contained within the bone slip and one of his Elders just happened to be a researcher on ancient languages. This youth had some hopes that this Elder would be able to discover some useful things from this bone shard.

The youth turned around and swept over Lin Ming’s cultivation, coldly saying, “Sorry, but I’m not in the habit of passing over things I like. 4.5 Million.”

“5 million.”

Lin Ming calmly raised the price. All of the youths present were from Holy Land level sects or families. Moreover, they were outstanding individuals of their generation. But even so, the wealth they brought with them was limited, likely to 100 million. This would be the wealth they specifically brought to partake in this trade fair.

Originating from a Holy Land didn’t mean that they were able to control the entirety of that Holy Land’s wealth.

Compared to Lin Ming, their wealth was simply trivial.

Lin Ming’s wealth came from the complete treasures that Splintersoul Mountain and the Occult Bone Clan had found in the Red Desolate Mystic Realm, and that was also a mission that they had paid a deep price to enter. In addition to the wealth that Mo Eversnow had left behind in the past, this was a giant sum of 500 billion violet sun stones!

When the quasi-Holy Land Carefree Island had put forth 10-20 billion violet sun stones, that was already nearly a complete gamble with most of their resources on the line. As for 500 billion violet sun stones, that was an amount that even an upper ranking Holy Land would have trouble collecting. And, a great deal of a Holy Land’s wealth came from fixed assets like its properties that couldn’t be easily converted into currency.

If Lin Ming wanted to roll over this fork-bearded youth with his wealth, that would be easy. But, that would make others curious about his motives for obtaining the bone slip.

In the blink of an eye, the price rose to 8.5 million. The youth’s complexion became increasingly ugly. 8.5 million was not a minor amount of the wealth he brought. Moreover, this price vastly surpassed what he was psychologically willing to pay.

He wasn’t even sure if he could learn anything from this bone shard.

He took a deep breath and suppressed his impulse to offer a higher price. Face was important, but it still couldn’t compare with his wealth.

“This brat… look up what background he has!” He said to one of his lackeys with a true essence sound transmission.

The lackey said, “That person was brought by Young Master River; his background shouldn’t be too bad.”

The fork-bearded youth simply didn’t place Lin Ming’s Ninefall cultivation in his eyes. What he worried about was Lin Ming’s background – this was what he had to be careful about. If this fellow could so casually toss out 8.5 million violet sun stones to buy an incomplete bone shard then that meant he came from a disgustingly wealthy and opulent background.

After Lin Ming’s purchase, those Whitejade spirit silkworm eggs were bought by someone for 4 million violet sun stones. As for the other things, no one cared about them.

In such a trade fair there was a limited number of guests and often many objects that no one would want to purchase. Thus, they would be put back.

Mister Luo laughed and put away the treasure no one wanted. It wasn’t a big deal if they didn’t sell it. And at this time, Madame Luo next to him deliberately raised her voice and said with a beguiling tone, “Those were only some little gadgets. Next up are some more… interesting things.”

Madame Luo clapped.

Two men in uniforms pushed in three carts. These carts were covered with red curtains. Madame Luo walked towards then and then tore off the curtains, revealing three iron cages that were as tall as a person. And, in these cages were three living people. One was a 20 year old young girl, one was a 11-12 year old little girl, and another was a seven or eight year old boy.

As these three people appeared, almost everyone’s eyes turned to that young girl’s body. She had elegant and soft features and a tender, watery expression. With her Revolving Core realm cultivation, her appearance easily aroused the pity of others.

“Chaotic yin body!”

The fork-bearded youth immediately recognized this young girl’s special physique.

Madame Luo chuckled, saying with great satisfaction, “Young Master Sun has good eyes. This is exactly the chaotic yin body! From birth, a woman with this type of body has extreme yin energy within their body. If they cannot find sufficient yang energy to bring their body into balance, it will be impossible for them to take even a tiny step forwards in their cultivation. If they try to force it, the yin energy within their body will turn to chaos, their meridians will reverse, and then they will fall into depravity!

“But what Young Master Sun trains in is a cultivation method that fills you with overflowing yang energy. What you just happen to need is yin energy to neutralize it. How about it, is Young Master Sun satisfied with this? This young woman is an extremely good cultivation furnace for you. As long as Young Master Sun is willing to spend some resources, you can easily bring this young woman to the Divine Sea realm in her thirties. At that time, she will be able to display an even better effect for you!”

Madame Luo’s words truly did tempt the fork-bearded youth. “Is there any problem with her background?”

This sort of special physique came with an extremely high level of talent for cultivation. It normally wouldn’t appear in the common people. There was a high chance that this young woman came from some large sect, thus he had to ask if there were any problems with her background.

“Rest assured. She is from a family that was annihilated in a war. She fled from that catastrophe and was rescued by us. Then, she also agreed with the conditions that we proposed to her. For her to follow Young Master Sun is a blessing to her.”

As Madame Luo spoke, the chaotic yin physique woman sighed, as if she were lamenting her own destiny. But, she also had no other choice. With the decline of her own family, she was desperate to find a turn in her fate. If she wanted to continue cultivating, her only choice was to attach herself to a powerhouse, otherwise there was no way she would be able to obtain resources. But, as she thought about herself being brought here for sale, she felt saddened.

“Good! Good!” This Young Master Sun was also very satisfied.

His eyes then moved over to that 11-12 year old little girl. He rubbed his chin and said, “Does this little girl also have some sort of special physique?”

If she did, then he could raise her for several years and use her all the same.

As the little girl was noticed by others, she immediately became nervous. She huddled in a corner of the cage, her tiny hands clinging to her shoulders as she trembled.

“Yes, and it is also a very special physique.” Mister Luo said with a smile.

“Oh? What kind of physique?” Many people leaned forward in interest. Even if they didn’t practice dual cultivation methods, they were still interested in what sort of special physique this little girl had. If her talent was good they could bring her back to the sect and raise her as a talented disciple.

“Well…” As Madame Luo and Mister Luo were asked this question, they looked at each other, not knowing what to say.

“We’ve referenced countless texts and sources to search for what exact type of physique she has, but we haven’t managed to determine it. All we know is that her physique is special. After she came here, she didn’t eat food but ate violet sun stones and violet sun crystals. If there are also energy stones available she will eat them. Every day she will eat five violet sun crystals…”

“What?”

As Mister Luo spoke, all of the heroic young elites present were shocked. There was also this type of physique? This was the first time they had heard of such a thing!

This great and wide world truly possessed every possible strange thing!

Chapter 1142 – Intimidating All Present

This Mister Luo was at the Divine Transformation realm!

Lin Ming was only at the ninth stage of Life Destruction!

From Divine Transformation to the ninth stage of Life Destruction, that was a disparity of over a large boundary! Even if Mister Luo wasn’t some earth-shaking genius, his strength still surpassed some of those lesser known Divine Transformation martial artists from small sects. It was already astonishing that Lin Ming’s fist had managed to severely wound Yue Ironrock, but compared to that, Lin Ming attacking Mister Luo was absolutely mind-boggling.

This was a Ninefall war god transformation!

“Brat, do you really think you are invincible!?” Mister Luo spat out as he clenched his jaws. Even so, he didn’t dare to look down on Lin Ming at all. Lin Ming had managed to severely wound Yue Ironrock. Although this was partly because Yue Ironrock had underestimated Lin Ming, Lin Ming was also attacking two of them at the same time and that counterattack had merely been a casual punch.

The difference in strength was clear!

Mister Luo drew backwards and took out a five foot long saber from his spatial ring. At the same time, his entire body began to blaze with black flames. These black flames condensed behind Mister Luo, forming the phantom of a hydra.

This hydra was thicker than a water barrel and every head was fierce and lifelike. The scales that covered the hydra heads were the size of bowls and its long poisonous teeth shined with a sharp and cold light, surging with reckless killing intent.

It was clear that this Mister Luo was part of the Hydra Clan. In using the power of his bloodline, he was already giving this his everything!

Hissss –

After this hydra appeared, all nine of its heads hurtled towards Lin Ming!

At this time, what Lin Ming faced didn’t seem like a phantom formed from energy, but a true and living ancient great hydra!

“Hydra bloodline? This bloodline is really too cheap!” Lin Ming sneered. When Lin Ming was at the Sky Spill Continent, before he had killed Yang Yun, his path had crossed with Whitedemon’s. Whitedemon had come from the Divine Realm and had been suppressed and locked within the Sea of Miracles. He too had the Hydra bloodline. It seemed that this Hydra bloodline was quite common in the Divine Realm.

“A mere nine-headed worm wants to contend with the glory of a True Dragon?”

Lin Ming cried out, his entire body emitting crackling noises. These popping sounds gathered together, echoing, resonating until they formed the keening cry of a dragon, directly impacting through the world. And behind Lin Ming, the phantom of an Azure Dragon formed!

The Azure Dragon was much smaller than the hydra behind Mister Luo, but the pressure it gave off was unbelievable, a completely different level!

Lin Ming had purposefully revealed the power of his dragon blood. After absorbing the dragon marrow, although Lin Ming didn’t possess a perfect Ancient Dragon bloodline, this was only because his bloodline was lacking in quantity. In terms of quality, the power of Lin Ming’s bloodline far surpassed the Ancient Dragon Clan’s Dragon One!

A true God Beast, an ancient Azure Dragon, was inherently suppressive to those of the Hydra bloodline. Moreover, as Lin Ming released the power of the Azure Dragon bloodline he also released the grandmist space. As the two strengths superimposed on each other, the hydra phantom that hurtled towards Lin Ming rapidly weakened!

Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force. True essence surged from his body, flowing into the Phoenix Blood Spear. At that moment, the Phoenix Blood Spear released an ear-piercing screech as the artifact spirit slumbering within it was awakened!

Although this was an incomplete elementary artifact spirit, it was still an incomparably rare and precious source artifact spirit. It wasn’t something that a normal false artifact spirit could compare with!

Even if the Phoenix Blood Spear had just grown into a spirit artifact, it was already an existence that surpassed a peak low-grade spirit artifact!

Lin Ming’s full force attack was combined with the spirit artifact level Phoenix Blood Spear! In that instant, Lin Ming’s striking power rose dramatically. Wherever the spear light went, space would tremble. The minor dimension that this trade fair was located in wasn’t able to withstand the sharp energy of the Phoenix Blood Spear. After all, an artificial minor dimension was less stable than the space of the Divine Realm.

Hiss – !

The gigantic hydra phantom was twisted apart by the Phoenix Blood Spear. The hydra wailed in pain and horror. Lin Ming’s spear light continued forth with unstoppable strength, completely annihilating that hydra phantom and continuing to stab towards Mister Luo!

Mister Luo’s complexion completely changed. He opened his mouth and spat out a foot long black snake, as thick as a thumb. After that, Mister Luo spat out black flames that enveloped him, even as black scales wrapped around his cheeks and body.

Mister Luo was still a Divine Transformation powerhouse and thus much stronger than Yue Ironrock. By using his bloodline power as a catalyst, the power of the black flames he emitted was no joke. In the legends, every head of a hydra could spit out a different substance, such as demonic flames, freezing ice, venom, and so forth. This caused the Hydra Clan to divide into nine branches and this Mister Luo just happened to be part of the Demonic Flame Branch.

These black demonic flames were able to scorch away even true essence. At that time when the Phoenix Blood Spear thrust into the black demonic flames, the black demonic flames seemed to pervasively penetrate the spear light as if it possessed a mind of its own, seeking every possible weakness.

Chi chi chi!

The spear light and black flames smashed into each other, emitting a harsh grating sound!

“That… is that… a spirit artifact!?”

It wasn’t known just who cried out in alarm in the crowd. The biggest difference between a spirit artifact and a saint artifact was that a spirit artifact had an intelligence of its own. Ordinarily a saint artifact would only be controlled by the martial artist; the weapon itself didn’t have the ability to control energy. But, a spirit artifact could fight in tandem with the martial artist to attack. This was just like the difference between a person and a puppet, and a person with a live partner. This was especially true if a martial artist was able to become one with their spirit artifact and achieve a heart-to-heart thread of communication. At that time they would be no different from allies in battle, fighting side-by-side.

“Spirit artifact!? That is a weapon that only a Divine Lord or at least a middle or late Divine Transformation genius can use. How could Lin Ming control one at the Life Destruction realm?”

To galvanize a spirit artifact, one needed the power of a world. In other words, one needed to be a Divine Lord realm powerhouse! But, there were also a small number of Divine Transformation realm masters that could use spirit artifacts, and all of them were bound to be top geniuses!

Just as that man cried out in alarm, his voice was immediately drowned out by the maddening explosion!

Bang!

A brilliant light flashed throughout the entire hall. The black flames were forcefully torn apart and the spear light also faded away. Mister Luo’s forehead was covered in sweat. He quickly tried to summon true essence for another attack, but Lin Ming’s second attack had already arrived!

“Phoenix Blood Spear – Blue Lotus Flame Dance!”

In that moment, a brilliant and captivating blue lotus bloomed behind Lin Ming – this was the Blue Lotus Domain. With every step Lin Ming took, a lotus flower would blossom beneath his foot. This was the fusion of the first three level Concepts of the Fire Laws, and with even the fourth level Concept fused in too.

With the Blue Lotus Flame Dance displayed through the spirit artifact level Phoenix Blood Spear, the power of this attack increased by yet another level!

“You bastard!”

In a rush, Mister Luo chopped down with his saber. But just as he did, he felt as if his hands were bound by something strange, like invisible ropes were tied around his wrists.

‘This is… a world of will! A battle spirit projection!’

Mister Luo suddenly released his divine sense and ‘saw’ that there were countless strands of gold light binding his hands together!

“Large success gold level battle spirit!?”

Mister Luo was shocked, nearly losing his composure. He tried to force open the will tentacles, but in that brief moment of delay, he no longer had time to evade Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear. He could only withstand it with his black flames.

Peng!

The black fire burst apart. Before the unstoppable spear light, the demonic flames only lasted for a few blinks of an eye before collapsing. Lin Ming’s spear pierced the right side of Mister Luo’s chest, running straight through!

“Ahhh!”

Mister Luo pitifully cried out as blood splashed into the air!

“This… this…”

All of the other martial artists were left bewildered with sweaty palms. What kind of ridiculously fierce combat strength was this? This was simply a monstrous talent!

In particular, River Feather, who had brought Lin Ming here, had his mouth hanging open. He was simply unable to gather himself. He had originally thought of winning Lin Ming over to his side to help him compete for the position of successor to the River Family’s house head, but now he felt as if all his ideas had simply been laughable.

Lin Ming’s combat strength was not something that an ordinary Holy Land level family could produce! Even a top Holy Land wouldn’t be able to accomplish this. Lin Ming was a genius that only a World King level Holy Land could produce!

Ninefall war god transformation – what sort of concept was that? It was simply unimaginable!

River Feather looked at Lin Ming’s weapon, the Phoenix Blood Spear, once more. That was an extremely high quality spirit artifact!

It had to be known that to these peak geniuses, a spirit artifact was precious but not impossible to obtain. As long as they cultivated to the late Divine Transformation realm, their families would be able to forge or hand down a low-grade spirit artifact for them. But, Lin Ming’s spirit artifact was clearly different!

In order to stimulate a spirit artifact to movement, one needed the world power that was bred within a martial artist’s inner world. By just depending on true essence alone, it was extremely difficult to do this. This was because world power was in simpler terms all the power that could exist in a world. There was true essence, the power of life, pure heaven and earth origin energy, and the faith energy of all living beings!

Only by combining all these various types of power was one able to activate a spirit weapon. But Lin Ming was just a Ninefall martial artist who had only formed a world seed, so how could he possibly produce world power?

If he could control the Phoenix Blood Spear, that only left one possibility, and that was that Lin Ming was interlinked with his Phoenix Blood Spear in their minds and hearts and it willingly allowed Lin Ming to use it.

The artifact spirit of this spirit artifact had an extremely high chance of being a source artifact spirit. That meant that it was an artifact spirit bred by the weapon itself!

The growth of the artifact spirit would also enhance the quality of the spirit artifact. In truth, for the physical body of a spirit artifact alone, as long as one fused in various types of rare and heavenly materials, it was possible to increase the physical quality. The only extremely difficult part was growing the artifact spirit itself!

A spirit artifact that could constantly grow and be enhanced was far different from other spirit artifacts that were set in rank once they were forged. There was no way of comparing them at all.

To match a junior disciple with a spirit artifact that had its own source artifact spirit, just what kind of extravagant luxury was that! Even an ordinary World King level Holy Land wouldn’t have the courage to do so!

When River Feather combined this with the scene of Lin Ming tossing out several hundred million violet sun stones to purchase that little girl, he was finally aware that he had far underestimated Lin Ming’s background!

If he was just rich, then it was possible that he might have stumbled across some great lucky chance and unearthed some treasure.

But, a true spirit artifact with its own source artifact spirit that could communicate as one was impossible to obtain through lucky chances alone. This was because a spirit artifact must be picked up from someone else, thus it was impossible to have a high fusion compatibility, so it should have been impossible for Lin Ming to use it. The only reasonable explanation was if the sect master of a large and grand sect helped Lin Ming personally forge such a weapon with countless heavenly materials!

And finally, there was also Lin Ming’s terrifying strength and horrifying talent. It was impossible for such a character to appear from a small family. The background behind him must be dreadful to the extreme!

Chapter 1144 – Yan Littlefish

Lin Ming ignored that Mister Luo and moved towards the iron cage that was pushed away to the corner of the hall. Although the fight just now had been a bit violent, Lin Ming had intentionally tried to avoid harming the little girl. Even so, the wild and crazy explosions had caused her to pale.

Lin Ming grasped two of the metal rails and pulled, easily pulling apart the finger-thick metal bars.

“Come with me.” Lin Ming stretched out his hand towards the little girl, a warm and inviting smile on his face.

The little girl bit her lips and grabbed onto Lin Ming’s hand.

Like this, Lin Ming brought the girl with him and left the hall. His steps were slow and steady, with a vague and deep pressure exuding from him that echoed in the hall, making anyone not dare to do anything.

Mister Luo gulped, not speaking. Madame Luo’s beautiful face also paled. She retreated to a corner of the hall lest she attract Lin Ming’s ire.

Lin Ming and the little girl left the trading fair hall with no one stopping them.

After Lin Ming left, Mister Luo finally relaxed. He grit his teeth, taking out several pills from his spatial ring and swallowing them down.

Today he acknowledged that he got what he deserved!

Although he had lost face, for better or worse the truth was that the tremendous pressure that came shrouding down was from a half-step World King powerhouse who was secretly observing everything happening here. If it was said that their gang was overwhelmed by a half-step World King supreme elder, then that wouldn’t be too shameful.

The other young elites glanced at each other in shocked dismay. This trade fair had completely broadened their horizons. Indeed, in the vast Divine Realm there truly was no limit to the universe; there would always be a higher peak and a stronger person. They were all outstanding juniors of their generation, but compared to Lin Ming they weren’t anything at all.

“This Lin Ming… is he really a genius that could be raised by a Holy Land? Would it be a Great World King level Holy Land?”

River Feather mumbled to himself. Although he knew that there were countless young elites in the Divine Realm that were far more formidable than him, this was the first time that he had felt so deeply powerless and frustrated. Against such a seemingly omnipotent strength, he wasn’t able to summon any courage to chase after him.

“Perhaps it might be a Great World King level Holy Land. Moreover, Lin Ming’s talent would be amazing even within a Great World King level Holy Land! And don’t forget, above a Great World King is an Empyrean. If it was a genius trained by an Empyrean, just how high would their talent be?”

“Empyrean…”

River Feather ruefully smiled upon hearing this word. If it were the descendant of an Empyrean, just how ridiculous would that be?

Without mentioning the resources or inheritances that an Empyrean could provide, just the level of talent that a descendant of an Empyrean would possess was far too dreadful to imagine. If the Empyrean’s spouse was also a super powerhouse and their child inherited both of their parents’ talents, that would simply be unbelievable!

Compared to that, they were nothing more than ants!

River Feather sighed. Then, a true essence sound transmission sounded out in his ears. It was Lin Ming’s voice, “I ask that Brother River continue to collect the materials that I requested. Without a doubt I will return within a year and pay you back the full price for them.”

As Lin Ming finished speaking he quickly dashed away, leaving River Feather in a daze. He could faintly feel that Lin Ming would shine with glory in the future Divine Realm. As for him, he would continue to strive to become the successor to his Holy Land Family, even if those hopes were slim.

The difference in status between the two could be imagined.

“If… if I can remain on good terms with Lin Ming in the future, then the benefits I obtain will be many. At the very least, I will be able to smoothly inherit the position of Patriarch in the future…”

River Feather whispered to himself. As he thought of this, he secretly solidified his determination. He had to seize this chance and help Lin Ming as splendidly and smoothly as he could.

……

At this time, Lin Ming had already left Immemorial Imperial City and had arrived at the distant outskirts. His speed wasn’t fast and he appeared extremely calm, but within the Magic Cube space, Mo Eversnow was releasing her divine sense, maintaining absolute vigilance.

Lin Ming’s breathing was even, as if he were taking a casual stroll. But, his nerves were taut; he was ready to deal with dangers that might erupt at any given moment.

He couldn’t help but be cautious. Although he had seemed to overawe everyone and smoothly walk out, the truth was that he had just escaped the jaws of death!

That underworld trade fair was no different from a danger zone to Lin Ming.

The reason that Lin Ming would brandish his weapon and start a fight at the trade fair was that he had no choice left.

If he was able to melt away disasters with some wealth then he wouldn’t have chosen to fight. But, that Mister Luo was insatiably greedy, and his attempt at extortion became increasingly ruthless. If Lin Ming pinched his nose and pretended he didn’t notice this, then that Mister Luo might even have the idea to inflate the price to unbelievable heights. At the end, he might have even developed thoughts of killing Lin Ming to steal his wealth!

After all, if Lin Ming wasn’t able to show that there was some great influence behind him and kept bearing all of the abuse, then others would think he was someone easy to bully. In this case where Lin Ming was carrying a large amount of wealth, they would think he was just some nobody that stumbled into a massive treasure trove.

Immemorial Imperial City was a place where both good and evil were mixed up. If others believed he was no different from a fat lamb that was free to be butchered, his fate could be imagined. He might even be eaten up by someone without any dregs remaining!

In order to combat these types of snakes, one could only be even more ruthless and thoroughly suppress them so that all they knew was fear.

“No one is chasing after us. There were several senses that were following you for a distance but they eventually returned.” Mo Eversnow said from within the Magic Cube space.

“Got it.” Lin Ming slowed down flying, a fearless look in his eyes. He didn’t hide his whereabouts nor did he purposefully change directions. It was only until he flew another thousand miles away and Mo Eversnow confirmed again that there was no one following him that he rapidly accelerated. He instantly blew past 10,000 miles in a single go, crossing through several mountains and valleys and switching directions several times. Finally, he stopped by a quiet forest where no one was living.

He was finally out of danger!

Lin Ming let out a long breath. This period just now had been an extreme test on his mentality. Although he appeared completely confident, the truth was that he was extremely anxious with nerves tighter than wires.

Mo Eversnow faintly smiled, “Your acting skills aren’t bad.”

Lin Ming chuckled, shaking his head. “Miss Mo was much calmer than me. When you put that pressure out, there wasn’t the faintest feeling that you lacked any energy at all. It was truly the aura of a top master who controlled the lives of all present, as if they could all be killed with a single wave of the hand. As for me, I was just putting on a child’s play.”

As Lin Ming spoke, his thoughts moved and his figure appeared within the Extreme Violet Ring. At this time, Mo Eversnow also turned into a stream of light that entered into the Extreme Violet Ring’s world.

Here, a little girl was sitting down near the medicine garden, holding both of her knees. She stared at the wondrous sight in front of her – 20 mountains of purple crystals!

Each crystal mountain was formed by a massive amount of piled up violet sun stones and violet sun crystals.

Lin Ming had exchanged the wealth he took from Splintersoul Mountain and the Occult Bone Clan at Carefree Island for violet sun stones and received over 100 billion. And, he had also inherited over 300 billion from the Verdant Feather Holy Lands. He had already exchanged the latter for crystal cards, around 3600-3700 of them. Each crystal card was worth 100 million. These crystal cards could be exchanged at any major bank of the great worlds for violet sun stones or different kinds of pills.

And now, these 20 purple crystal mountains had formed a tremendous visual impact on this little girl!

During her time at Immemorial Imperial City’s underworld influence, she had never had enough to eat. From the start, their only desire had been to study her special physique and ascertain just what it was. Thus, they had supplied her with many violet sun crystals. But in the end, this had come to nothing and they were only able to sell her for a price of 2 million. Afterwards, while she had been waiting to be sold, this little girl nearly never had anything to eat, and she had been in a starving state for a long time.

In fact, even when she had violet sun crystals to eat at the start, she only ate 20 some per day. That was equal to 200 thousand some violet sun stones, so when had she seen such a massive violet sun crystal mountain?

The little girl couldn’t help but lick her lips. She was unbearably hungry, but since she didn’t have Lin Ming’s permission she could only look on.

As she saw Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow arrive, she was startled and quickly stood up.

“Eat as much as you want.” Lin Ming casually said.

The little girl knew that Lin Ming had seen her hungry appearance and blushed, a bit embarrassed. She didn’t have the courage to directly start eating the violet sun crystals, but looked at Mo Eversnow with a confused look on her face instead, “You are… that big sister in the hall?”

The little girl suddenly asked, startling Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow.

The two of them glanced at each other and then turned to that little girl in disbelief.

“How did you know?”

“A feeling… I had a feeling that this big sister’s aura is the same as the big sister’s aura in the hall…” The little girl said, shrinking her neck back.

After Lin Ming listened to her, he looked at the little girl with a bit of surprise in his eyes. She clearly didn’t have the least bit of cultivation and Mo Eversnow had been purposefully avoiding placing any soul pressure on her. Even so, she was able to remember Mo Eversnow’s soul fluctuations, and even now when Mo Eversnow was restraining her soul aura, she had still been able to recognize her!

This was something that not even a martial artist skilled in the aspect of soul would be able to achieve!

“What’s your name?” Mo Eversnow asked.

“I… I am called Yan Littlefish, but you can just call me Fishy…” The little girl whispered in a clear voice.

“Yan Littlefish, that’s a very beautiful name. May I ask you a few questions?”

“You can ask me, Big Sister.” Fishy said, without the least bit of wariness towards Mo Eversnow.

“Mm… I want to know what your background is. Who are your parents? How could you only eat violet sun stones? And how do you know where the violet sun stone embryo is?”

Hearing Mo Eversnow’s questions, Yan Littlefish thought very hard for a time before shaking her head. She said, “I don’t remember where I came from… all I remember is that I have always been alone around Immemorial Imperial City, and I don’t have any parents…”

“You’re alone? Then how did you live when you were a little child? Where did you obtain violet sun stones from?” After hearing Fishy’s words, Lin Ming was surprised. It was simply impossible for a lonely and defenseless little girl to live near Immemorial Imperial City for all this time. Moreover, Fishy didn’t eat normal types of food; she only ate violet sun stones and violet sun crystals, so where would she have obtained them?

Yan Littlefish hesitated for a moment before finally saying, “The truth is that… I can see violet sun stones buried underground. I can even see them when they are super super far away. It’s just that I am very weak so I can’t dig them out, but… I can sometimes dig out some small pieces and eat them…”

Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow were dumbfounded. There was actually such a mystical ability??

Chapter 1145 – Marvelous Ability

“You can see the location of violet sun stones? Those people that captured you didn’t know this?” Lin Ming found this surprising. Violet sun stones and violet sun crystals were often buried deep underground, isolated by thick layers of soil. In addition, these layers of soil were often like the purple mountain in the Red Desolate Mystic Realm and had certain properties that could isolate divine sense. They were extremely difficult to discover. If Yan Littlefish had this ability, then just this point alone would cause countless underworld influences to compete for her.

Fishy shook her head. She clenched her small fists and said, “They were bad guys so I didn’t tell them. If I did, then it would have been really sad for me. I would have to rush every day to help them mine stuff, but the truth is if I look for things for too long then my head hurts and I will feel dizzy and sick.”

As Fishy spoke, Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow felt their hearts touched. Although Fishy was young and she didn’t have much courage, she was quite smart. A rhino would often die because of their horn and elephants were hunted for their pure white ivory tusks. It wasn’t easy for an 11-12 year old child to understand this and hide their own abilities.

It also seemed that Fishy revealing that she knew the whereabouts of the violet sun stone embryo was because she had no choice. Since she didn’t have any cultivation, she couldn’t use a true essence sound transmission to tell Lin Ming this; she could only speak it out loud. Luckily, Fish didn’t continue to hide her ability, otherwise Lin Ming wouldn’t have a clue to find the violet sun stone embryo and Fishy wouldn’t have been able to leap out of her sea of suffering.

“How did they treat you?” Mo Eversnow sighed as she remembered how Fishy had fear in her eyes when she saw that Mister Luo and Madame Luo.

Fishy said, “They let me eat at the start, but they also forced me to train a lot. They didn’t let me sleep or even rest, and afterwards that Madame Luo kept calling me useless trash and yelled at me, hit me, and finally locked me up. They didn’t let me eat anymore and only wanted to sell me away. They had wanted to sell me to a terrible witch for alchemy, but that witch thought I was too expensive and didn’t buy me. I was afraid of what would happen if I stayed there. I knew if I did, I would die sooner or later. That’s why I couldn’t help but call out for Big Brother…”

Yan Littlefish guiltily looked at Lin Ming. She hadn’t thought that her calling out to him would cause him so much trouble.

“These underworld gangs are truly heartless…” Lin Ming said, but, he understood that this was simply how it was in the world of martial artists. These underworld gang influences didn’t need to worry about what the public thought of them, thus they were able to seek profits at any cost, no matter how horrible it made them. The reason that they gave Fishy violet sun stones to eat at the start was only that they wanted to train her so when she matured they could sell her for a higher price. Thus, this was why they rigorously trained an 11-12 year old girl. Afterwards when they discovered that their training had no effect, they thought of simply selling her instead. As for what her fate would be and whether she would live or die, none of them cared.

“Big Brother and Big Sister are fierce! Those bad guys were all beaten up!” Fishy said, excited, as she thought of how Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow had shown off in such great glory.

Mo Eversnow smiled and shook her head, “We’re not as fierce as you think we are.” As she spoke, she couldn’t help but lift her hand and rub Fishy’s cheeks. She could rely on energy to simulate touch, a touch that felt like water.

“Big Sister, your hands are very cold.” Fishy said. She didn’t avoid Mo Eversnow but only looked at her strangely.

Mo Eversnow faintly smiled. Being called a big sister by such a little child was quite strange to her. She said, “You can call me aunty from now on. I’ve always had such a cold body.”

“Aunty…” Fishy tilted her head, thinking about it. She said, “But I like to call you big sister more! And Big Sister doesn’t seem to be much older than Fishy.”

“A bit.” Mo Eversnow chuckled, thinking it was funny. The time whilst she slept in the Magic Cube had been extremely strange. It hadn’t dimmed her fires of life at all, and they were still as vivid as they were 50,000 years ago. It was like time had stopped and only restarted when she had awakened with Lin Ming.

As she stood together with Lin Ming, they were like mortal youths in their prime, brimming with vitality. This was one of the most fascinating aspects of following the martial path, in that one could extend their youth.

Those that cultivated martial arts were not willing to resign themselves to the ebb of time. As years passed, their life force and strength would be slowly sucked away. Even though they had the ability to move mountains and sunder seas, they finally couldn’t escape the slow changes of destiny.

Often, a martial artist would constantly seek out lucky chances, passing through layers upon layers of dangers to climb to a higher peak of martial arts. What drove them was not just peeping at the wonders of the Heavenly Dao Laws, but also to obtain longer youth and longer life.

Even an Empyrean was unable to achieve that faint and illusory immortality that existed in legends. As for whether one could even achieve immortality through the martial path and surpass the scope of the Heavenly Dao, that had always been an enigma.

“Alright, eat something, you look hungry.” Lin Ming took out several high quality violet sun crystals from the purple crystal mountain and passed them to Fishy.

As Fishy saw this violet sun crystal and the incomparably rich energy within it, she bit her lips and said, “This is very expensive… Big Brother Lin Ming’s crystals are much better than ordinary ones.”

This large fragment of violet sun crystal that Lin Ming took out was worth several hundred thousand violet sun stones. That underground influence would definitely not be willing to give Fishy such a luxurious item to eat. But to him, who had 500 billion violet sun stones, several hundred thousand was just a drop of water in the ocean.

“Eat.” Mo Eversnow smiled, “There’s much more where that came from, you won’t be able to finish it all.”

Fishy took the big violet sun crystal, a bit embarrassedly, and bit down on it.

As Fishy ate the violet sun crystal, Lin Ming was paying particularly special attention to the changes in it. Violet sun crystals were extremely hard; not even an iron hammer would be able to break them and they could easily chip teeth. But as Yan Littlefish bit down on that violet sun crystal, part of the crystal’s energies mysteriously dissolved, just like she was biting a candied fruit instead. The violet sun crystal was simply eaten like that.

“This…” Lin Ming glanced at Mo Eversnow, finding this incredible. Just what sort of principle was this? Fishy clearly didn’t have any energy fluctuations coming from her body. She was a true and thorough mortal little girl.

“Yummy! I’ve never eaten something so delicious before.” Fishy seemed shy as she spoke but continued to eat. The more she ate, the quicker she ate and the more lively she ate, just like an ordinary little girl eating candy.

“I’ve never heard of this type of physique before.” Mo Eversnow sighed. In the vast Divine Realm, every strange and fantastical thing was possible. Mo Eversnow considered herself well-read and experienced but she had still never seen any type of record that pertained to such a physique. Violet sun stones were the condensation of heaven and earth origin energy. Martial artists could use them to cultivate, but because large sects of the Divine Realm often had training locations with extremely rich energy, there wasn’t too great a demand on violet sun crystals for cultivation. Normally, violet sun crystals would only be used to activate array formations and drive the movement of spirit ships, or even galvanize large-scale spirit artifacts. They were even used to open divergent mystic realms.

But to directly eat up a violet sun crystal… that was something she had never heard of.

In just half an incense stick of time, the large violet sun crystal chunk was directly eaten up by Fishy.

Fishy patted her full belly and accidentally let out a burp. Her face blushed red and she lowered her head in embarrassment, slowly saying, “I… I’m full. That was very delicious.”

Lin Ming looked at Fishy, a puzzled light in his eyes. In his opinion, energy in the Divine Realm was conserved. It wouldn’t come from nowhere, nor would it randomly disappear. A mortal could work labor because they ate food, and a martial artist could move seas because they absorbed heaven and earth origin energy.

Then, Fishy ate up so much pure violet sun crystal energy, so where did that energy go?

A little mortal girl had a limit to the amount of energy they could expend in their entire life. It probably wouldn’t even be equal to a thousandth of that violet sun crystal just now.

Lin Ming used his senses to investigate Fishy’s body. Following the movement of the violet sun crystal after Fishy ate it, he discovered that the energy simply vanished without a trace. It was like there was a bottomless pit in Fishy’s body and she swallowed it all without end.

Lin Ming glanced at Mo Eversnow, but Mo Eversnow only shook her head. She said, “I also cannot understand this. Fishy’s body is truly incomprehensible. She violates the conservation of energy contained within the Heavenly Dao Laws. Then again, perhaps this energy was hidden using some sort of special method, or maybe it was simply transferred somewhere else…”

Even though Mo Eversnow’s soul force was on the level of a half-step World King, she still couldn’t discover what was happening in Yan Littlefish’s body.

“Well, let’s consider it finished. We’ll slowly unravel whatever her physique is in the future.” Lin Ming didn’t think that it would be easy to understand Fishy’s physique. Otherwise, that underworld influence of Immemorial Imperial City would have already done so.

“Fishy, you said that you knew the location of the violet sun stone embryo. Did you find it when you were looking for something to eat?”

“I’m not too sure…” Fishy shook her head. “That place is very strange… when I saw that place, I felt very… uncomfortable, and I didn’t know why… I can lead Big Brother Lin Ming to go there now.”

“Alright. You point the way and we’ll go together. But, we’re not in a hurry so let’s rest a bit first.”

Lin Ming turned into a stream of light that shot out from the Extreme Violet Ring. Then, his thoughts stirred and his body began to emit great snapping and crackling noises. His body began to change. His figure became much larger, his muscles thicker, and his handsome looks more ordinary. In a short while, he became a completely different person. It was impossible to find even the faintest shadow of Lin Ming in his body.

Then, Lin Ming revolved the special martial skill Mo Eversnow taught him to conceal the energy fluctuations of grandmist space, using that to completely change his own aura. At this time, even an early Divine Lord realm powerhouse might not be able to recognize him.

And why would an ordinary Divine Lord powerhouse have the spare time to investigate everyone they came across to see if they had changed their appearance?

Like this, they stayed until nightfall. Under the cover of night, Lin Ming quietly moved towards Immemorial Imperial City. With Fishy’s guidance, he soon found the location where Fishy said the violet sun stone embryo was. But as he saw this place, he was actually shocked.

How… how could it be here?

Chapter 1161 – Auctioning the Boundless World Pill

“Fuck, who the hell does he think he is? He clearly lost so why is he pretending to be so amazing at losing!” River Feather cursed. “It’s as if he thinks that he’s donating to us or something. Everyone clearly knows he lost the bid and yet he thinks he won it!”

Lin Ming thought little of it. He said, “That type of person has an arrogant personality with a mouth that keeps running off on its own. Even if he lost he would tell others that it wasn’t because he was weak but because he couldn’t be bothered to put his full force into fighting. These geniuses from somewhat influential backgrounds are born with a sense of superiority, so being idiotically arrogant like this is also normal.”

As for Princess Honeylush, she looked at Zhong Wenshu without the least bit of embarrassment. As the auctioneer for this event, it was common knowledge that she would be able to keep a small percentage of the profits for herself. Even so, any normal person would have been humiliated after being publicly scolded by Zhong Wenshu.

But Princess Honeylush only smiled. She said, “What Sir Zhong said about me, I will surely remember. I hope that once the final several items of this auction come out, Sir Zhong will be able to put forth a splendid performance!

“If no one wishes to bid again, then I will begin the countdown!”

As Princess Honeylush spoke, Lin Ming was a bit surprised. This young woman wasn’t simple at all. She was actually able to remain so calm and composed in the face of Zhong Wenshu’s ridicule. It might really be true that she had a talent that approached the three prodigies of Sacred Martial Mansion.

“17 billion, going once…”

Princess Honeylush slowly spoke. As she finished the countdown, no one bid again.

“Congratulations to this guest for obtaining the nine aperture spirit crystal!”

Princess Honeylush smiled at Lin Ming. As for those young elites around Lin Ming, all of them were looking at him with strange expressions on their faces. They never imagined that this youth they were sitting with would actually be so special and wealthy.

“Does anyone know what his background is!?”

“Not sure. If he comes from a World King Holy Land then he should have revealed his status. If his status was certified, he should have been able to sit in the VIP seats as an honored guest. Since this youth didn’t, he might be the descendant of some expert. If that expert is amazing enough, then his status might not be too different from that of an upper level Holy Land. Otherwise, if he’s just some nobody that obtained a massive lucky chance by accident, then he will be in danger.”

All of the young elites began discussing Lin Ming’s status with true essence sound transmissions, curious as to just who he was and where he came from.

“Honored guest, would you like to switch seats?” Princess Honeylush kindly said to Lin Ming. She clearly wanted to swap Lin Ming’s seat for one in the upper levels.

Lin Ming shook his head, “No need.”

“Very well, please do as you please. Now, it is time for the next auction!” As Princess Honeylush spoke, she had already opened the second box.

This was a five foot long wooden chest. After opening it, a sword with a four foot long blade was revealed. The blade edge was sharp and chilling!

This was… a transcendent saint artifact!

A spirit artifact without an artifact spirit was a transcendent saint artifact. It was weaker than a true spirit artifact but far superior to a top grade saint artifact.

And most importantly, this sort of weapon could be used by an extreme Divine Sea genius. By relying on the weak world power within themselves, they could move this weapon. It wasn’t like a spirit artifact that required a Divine Transformation realm genius to use it.

“What a wonderful treasure, haha!”

“I just happen to use a sword! Although I can’t compare to those rich fellows that use spirit artifacts, a transcendent saint artifact isn’t too bad either. At least in terms of weapon hardness and durability, I won’t lose to others!”

At the ordinary lower level seats, many young elites were itching to put up a struggle for treasures. After the first auction, the quality of the items dramatically fell, otherwise they would never have been able to afford anything here.

The base price of this transcendent saint artifact sword was 80 million. The disciples of ordinary families bid on it until it was finally won at 160 million.

Following that, item after item was auctioned. However, the price normally wouldn’t exceed 200 million. The audience for these items was ordinary young elites. Of course, these so called ‘ordinary young elites’ were still top disciples of Holy Land level sects and distinguished martial families.

To Lin Ming and others, these things had little to no use.

Lin Ming didn’t call out another bid. As for those other World King Holy Land geniuses, they were all saving their strength for the true bidding.

As item after item was sold, the auction finally began to approach its end.

Princess Honeylush stepped on stage again. She said with a lively and spirited voice, “This auction has continued for three days. Several thousands of items have been auctioned, and now, it is finally time for the grand finale. The first of the final items is also the most precious of them all, as well as what so many of you have come here for. It is… the Boundless World Pill! Now, let us begin the auction!”

There were a total of 10 final items. The most precious, the Boundless World Pill, was the first and not the last. This was so that the young elites present would compete for it without holding back. Otherwise, if they all held their hands waiting for it, they would bid lower on the other items, thinking to save as much as possible for the Boundless World Pill.

Once the Boundless World Pill appeared, everyone would still be in the situation where they had the most funds available to them. They could wholeheartedly compete for it with everything they had! If they couldn’t win the bidding then they could at least forget about it.

At that time, they would be able to bid on other items. They would have already cut off all other paths so they would have no choice but to purchase something else, otherwise they would have to leave empty-handed without anything to show for their efforts.

This arrangement was to maximize the auction value of all items. It was also to ensure that the bidding competition between these young elites would be fair.

“Let’s begin, the true act is here!”

“Haha, I’ve waited three days for this. The Boundless World Pill is finally appearing. I must obtain it before I can go to sleep!”

In the higher reserved seats, every disciple of the World King level Holy Lands was gearing up to bid. Beside them were also many of their Elders that were here to back them up. Many of them were peak Holy Lord masters.

On Sacred Martial Mansion’s side, a tall and burly youth rubbed his spatial ring, caressing it like he would his most treasured lover. Without a doubt, there was a great deal of wealth contained within this spatial ring.

This tall and burly youth was Sacred Tianhao, one of the three prodigies of Sacred Martial Mansion. Beside him, the red-haired Sacred Yueping drawled, “Big Brother, there is no need for there to be a fight between us brothers. Let’s join together to purchase this Boundless World Pill and then we can discuss how to split it up later.”

As geniuses of Sacred Martial Mansion, although their relationship wasn’t usually harmonious, they naturally fell in sync with each other at this time.

“That’s a good idea. It’s not just us, but we also have to join together with Third Sister. We have to win this Boundless World Pill at all costs. This is going to be a tough battle for all of us.”

In truth, even if several of them joined together, the force standing behind the three prodigies was only a World King level Holy Land. Their advantage here wasn’t too great.

And in front of them were several geniuses of World King Holy Lands. For instance… Zhong Wenshu.

At this time, Zhong Wenshu had completely put away his previous cynical and contemptuous manner. He was staring at the jade box in front of Princess Honeylush, eyeing it like a viper eyeing its prey!

Zhong Wenshu had an early Divine Sea cultivation. If he could obtain the Boundless World Pill and close up in training for three months within a time altering array formation, then it would be guaranteed for him to step into the middle Divine Sea realm. Moreover, his inner world would become much more stable and he would be able to have a more amazing result in the First Martial Meeting. With a great result, the advantages he would obtain from the sect would be indispensable for his future achievements.

“This Boundless World Pill is mine no matter what!”

Zhong Wenshu cried out in his mind.

As for those disciples of ordinary sects and families, they could only watch the play unfolding in front of them. This would be a bloodbath of those with true wealth. Although they couldn’t participate, they were still filled with anticipation in being able to watch. They all wanted to see just how astronomically high the price would rise.

A Boundless World Pill used a Realmheart cornerstone as the main material in refining it. As for a Realmheart cornerstone, that could only be obtained after a boundless world reached its natural end-time and collapsed. The preciousness of such a treasure could be imagined.

Moreover, wanting to refine such a pill wasn’t easy either. Only a Great World King level alchemist would have the ability and power required to refine such a pill. Even then, in normal times this pill couldn’t be bought with mere wealth. And now that the First Martial Meeting was approaching, the value of the Boundless World Pill was impossible to calculate!

Many people had a similar mentality in that even if they couldn’t afford a high-priced treasure, and even if it was impossible for them to even dream of owning such an item, they would still want to see just how high of a price it could sell for. In the future, they could gossip about this and even boast about how they were present.

“I wonder just what it will sell for!”

“I have no idea. The price will surely be unimaginable!”

Before the auction for the Boundless World Pill began, Princess Honeylush waited for a full half incense stick of time. Finally, she slowly opened the jade box containing the Boundless World Pill. As the jade box opened, a perfectly spherical pill shot up into the air. The pill was surrounded by a clear jade green haze and the main body was translucent. Sealed within the centre of the pill seemed to be some kind of spirit. This spirit struggled within, as if it had a life of its own!

However, there was a special array formation on top of the jade box. As soon as the pill rushed out, it crashed into the array formation. There was a golden flash of light and the pill was bounced back, emitting hissing sounds all the while. As it floated in the air, brilliant beams of energy shot out like rays of the sun, beautiful and wonderful!

“It really is the Boundless World Pill!” Mo Eversnow exclaimed from within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea. She had clearly seen this pill before.

As for the others present, even if they were the young elites of World King Holy Lands, this was still the first time they had seen such a pill.

“So that’s the Boundless World Pill.”

“It seems alive, how incredible.”

“As expected of a top grade pill approaching the rank of a transcendent divine pill. If one could take this pill then the advantages could be imagined!”

Princess Honeylush lifted up the jade box and placed it within the array disc projection, expanding the image to tens of thousands of times its original size so that everyone could clearly see it. “Everyone, can you see that little life within the pill? That is a world spirit! In the legends it is said that there is a world soul, but… that is only a legend. Still, this Boundless World Pill was refined with a Realmheart cornerstone, so it wouldn’t be surprising if a world soul could truly be bred within. What does everyone think about this item? Hohoho… this pill, if taken by someone at the Divine Sea or Divine Transformation realm, will grant tremendous benefits to their inner world! Now, let us start the bidding!”

“The starting price…”

Princess Honeylush trailed off as she spoke to here, and then said, “The starting price… is zero!”

“Zero?”

Many of the young elites were stunned. They looked at each other, not thinking that the starting price would be zero.

But, no matter what the starting price was, it didn’t matter. In this bidding war, the final price for the Boundless World Pill would surely rise to unbelievable heights!

Chapter 1162 – The Rise

“With a starting price of zero there is no standard to measure the auction with. The first bid will be even more exaggerated!”

A World King Holy Land Elder said from the higher reserved seats. Because there were so few Boundless World Pills and they were rarely traded, their price was difficult to estimate. Moreover, there were vastly different prices in each transaction without any standard at all. Thus, no one could say just what the price of the Boundless World Pill should be.

In this sort of situation, if the auction house were to put forth a starting price then others would subconsciously think that this was the ordinary reserve price of the Boundless World Pill.

If this auction finally produced a price several times that of the starting price then there would be people who thought that they spent too much money and would think this was a great injustice!

This would cause some people to feel uncomfortable with their purchase and might even affect the final transaction price.

But on the other hand, if the starting price was too high then many people would develop fear at the start and wouldn’t dare to bid. This would lead to the auction being deserted and wouldn’t allow the bidding price of the item to reach its highest peak.

Thus, the starting price had simply been set as zero!

A starting price of zero even meant that some not-so-wealthy geniuses of peak Holy Lands felt eager to dip their hands into the game. Although they knew it was impossible for them to win in the end, they still felt fired up enough to bid a single time. Then, in the future, for better or worse, they could say that they had joined in on competing for the Boundless World Pill.

As several young elites opened their mouths to shout out a price, in the lower common seats, a red bamboo hat woman who had yet to speak a single word spoke up.

“100 billion!”

100 billion! That bid immediately broke past the limits of what most people were able to bid. Even if these young elites were to put forth their entire wealth, they still wouldn’t be able to match a tenth of that price! Moreover, this young woman was sitting in the lower common seats so chances were that she wasn’t a disciple of a World King Holy Land. Just where had she come from?

“Good heavens! The starting price is 100 billion!” River Feather wiped dripping sweat from his neck. He already knew that Lin Ming had raised an astronomical amount of funds in order to compete for the final items, but as for how much he had prepared, River Feather actually had no idea. And now the first bid was 100 billion. The final bidding price might even be 10-20 times higher than that! Could Lin Ming have possibly managed to scrounge up so much money?

Lin Ming glanced at the bamboo hat woman. Her voice wasn’t gentle or elegant at all. Rather, she sounded a bit hoarse. The bamboo hat was covered with a fine red gauze, but although it was just a little bit of fabric, there was actually a strange energy covering it that made others unable to see her appearance.

Where had this woman come from?

“200 billion!” On Sacred Martial Mansion’s side, Sacred Yueping suddenly stretched out the jade slip in his hand. His bright red hair was particularly radiant in the audience.

“250 billion!”

“300 billion!”

“360 billion!”

The bidding price continued to rise without end. Before a voice even faded, another person would place a bid!

This left the young elites present dazed. For them, it was already difficult to imagine just how much money this actually was.

At this time, a voice shouted, “One trillion!”

As this voice echoed forth, all of the heroic young geniuses of ordinary families were left completely panic-stricken. One trillion! This was one trillion! Just what kind of insane number was that? This was a number usually used to describe populations!

However, a bidding price of a trillion didn’t dampen the excitement of these Holy Land geniuses.

Zhong Wenshu stood up. He glanced at Princess Honeylush and then at Lin Ming, revealing a playful smile. He raised the jade slip in his hands and said, “2 trillion!”

By the heavens! This was double the last bid!

River Feather gulped. As he thought of the 150 billion violet sun stones that he had lent Lin Ming, that could barely be considered a rounding error! That amount had already been his complete wealth. He had thought that he had an incredible destiny after stumbling into a great lucky chance, but compared to these truly wealthy individuals, everything he had in his life was now a joke.

River Feather glanced over at Lin Ming and discovered that he was still sitting there with a placid expression, not hurried at all. This startled River Feather. How could Lin Ming remain so calm? This was 2 trillion! Did he still have the confidence to continue bidding later?

“2.3 trillion!” Sacred Martial Mansion’s Sacred Tianhao shouted out as he raised the jade slip in his hand, rising past Zhong Wenshu’s bid.

“Mm?” Zhong Wenshu frowned. He coldly looked over in the direction of this new bid and met the eyes of Sacred Tianhao. Both of them came from World King level Holy Lands so neither of them feared the other.

“Good, then let’s have a little battle! 2.5 trillion!” Zhong Wenshu shouted out another bid. Towards those like Sacred Tianhao and Sacred Yueping, who had a formidable power backing them from behind, he didn’t bother mocking. He could only contend with them in a battle of wealth.

“2.5 trillion! Is there a higher bid?” Princess Honeylush passionately said from the auction stage. She was extremely excited to be able to preside over such an auction!

And at this time, Lin Ming finally stood up. Besides the bamboo hat woman, he was the only one in the lower common seats that was able to compete with these World King Holy Land geniuses.

Because of the ruckus caused by Lin Ming competing for the nine aperture spirit crystal, many people were able to recognize him. As soon as Lin Ming stood up, he immediately attracted everyone’s eyes to him. As for Zhong Wenshu, he suddenly rose to a sitting position. He looked towards Lin Ming, a cold light flashing in his eyes.

“3 trillion!”

Lin Ming said, slowly and confidently. Then, he sat down. The new bidding price that he shouted out immediately shocked all of the young elites present, including River Feather!

It was already astonishing to them that Lin Ming had spent 17 billion to purchase the nine aperture spirit crystal. But now, something completely unbelievable had occurred. He had bid an entire 3 trillion!

If Lin Ming truly came from a World King level Holy Land then why wasn’t he sitting in the reserved VIP seats? If he was able to bring out a token that indicated he was from a World King level Holy Land then he would have been able to sit at the higher reserved levels. This would have helped him avoid a great number of troubles. Otherwise, it was simply too ostentatious for him to sit amongst the common young elites and call out such a high price. Once he left Immemorial Imperial City in the future, he would be targeted by countless people!

Just what was going on here?

Regardless of what happened, Lin Ming was now the center of all attention! A youth who others suspected of having an ordinary background actually put forth a bid of 3 trillion!

“This brat!” Zhong Wenshu’s lips twitched. He had thought that Lin Ming only had enough to win that single item at the start. He never imagined that this young man would actually have the ability to contend for the final treasures, and the most precious one at that. In addition, the first time he had entered a bidding war against Lin Ming he had lost. That had been the same as ruthlessly slapping his face.

“There must be some secret on that brat. We must investigate his identity in as much depth as we can!” Zhong Wenshu said to the old man behind him.

It wasn’t just Zhong Wenshu, but the three extraordinary geniuses of Sacred Martial Mansion also noticed Lin Ming. However, in the vast Divine Realm, it wasn’t easy to thoroughly vet someone’s background.

Just as Zhong Wenshu was about to shout out another bid, the bamboo hat woman that sat with Lin Ming in the lower common section actually stood up. She said in her coarse and deep voice, “3.3 trillion!”

“What!?”

This new bid left the audience bewildered. Lin Ming was already a surprise, but this bamboo hat woman also had trillions in wealth!

Just what was going on here!?

Everyone looked at that bamboo hat woman. Because of some special array formation in the red gauze that covered her face, it was impossible to clearly discern her appearance.

“Humph, covering up your face is nothing but a joke in front of me!”

Several Holy Lord level old monsters rudely released their senses. They wanted to directly pierce through the bamboo hat woman’s veil and see just what sort of person she was.

But at this time, a sharp light flashed in the eyes of an old woman sitting beside her. An unimaginable aura erupted from her, and the divine sense of these old men crashed into this aura, immediately repelled. This feeling was just like a mortal running at full speed into a brick wall. It was enough to cause them to almost vomit blood!

The several old men who tried to investigate the woman’s appearance paled as the blood drained from their faces. Their bodies shook and they nearly tumbled out of their chairs.

These old geezers were all stupefied. They knew now that they had kicked iron!

That person was…

Lin Ming’s mind chilled as he looked towards the old woman. The old woman was wizened and haggard, with a face that was dried up like a walnut. Her hair was sparse and stringy and her body was bent with rickets. Her entire body was swathed in gray robes and her breathing was deep. It was hard to imagine that she was someone capable of defeating a crowd of peak Holy Lord masters.

All this indicated that she was… a World King!

Everyone present glanced at each other in dismay and shock. The appearance of this old man caused them all to be even more acutely aware that this auction was truly a den of crouching tigers and hidden dragons!

There were some people that didn’t come from World King level Holy Lands, but standing behind them were still unfathomably deep existences. Because these existences were hidden, they were mostly unknown to anyone else. However, their strength far surpassed one’s imagination. And for this Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, they had personally sent out their disciples to temper themselves in the upcoming battles!

“That old woman is too terrifying!”

Many young elites spoke to each other with true essence sound transmissions. Looking at this old woman, their eyes filled with dread and awe. For this old woman to be able to reflect the divine sense of several Holy Lord level masters with just a thought, then even if her strength wasn’t that of a World King, she was infinitely close to one!

“Miss Mo, is that old woman a World King?”

Mo Eversnow shook her head. “She emits a very strange feeling. Her soul force is not inferior to that of an ordinary World King, but her true essence fluctuations are actually inferior to mine from 50,000 years ago! She should… not be a World King! But, she is someone approaching a World King, a peak half-step World King character! I am even more inclined to believe that she was once a World King. However, because of some injury she received in the past, she dropped out from the World King realm!”

Mo Eversnow inferred the likeliest situation from the little bits of clues and information she knew.

“I see… even someone that dropped from the World King realm is so frightening. She was able to casually defeat several Holy Lord level powerhouses and there were even peak Holy Lord level masters within that group. If what you said is true, then that bamboo hat young woman might be that old woman’s last disciple. In this auction, every opponent I face is stronger than the last. I only have 7 trillion… I wonder if that’s enough…”

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath. As he traced his spatial ring, his expression was solemn.

Chapter 1167 – Divine Spear Like Dragon

Mo Eversnow used her mind to control the small bone slip, bringing it floating out into the air.

This bone slip fragment didn’t appear to be special at all. If it had been placed in a street stall and not auctioned off at a trade fair then it would have been difficult for Lin Ming to discover anything strange about it.

Mo Eversnow said, “This bone slip has a cultivation method recorded within it. It includes the six early stages of body transformation, the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, and the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. The details about the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace are called the Nine Star Art. According to this bone slip, after one practices the Nine Star Art and truly opens of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, a martial artist can commune with the world around them, just like an essence gathering martial artist can. They can galvanize a type of energy using the world Laws. This energy is called astral essence!”

“Astral essence?” Lin Ming asked, startled. This was the first time he had ever heard of this sort of energy.

“Astral essence and true essence are two sides of energy, similar to how grandmist energy divided into yin and yang energies. I have a faint premonition that the secrets of astral essence are related to how to open the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.”

“The secrets to opening the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace…” Lin Ming thought for a moment. It was a pity that this bone slip was far too incomplete. If he wanted to understand all of these secrets then he would have to rely on his own efforts to do so.

The Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was an extremely distant matter. Currently, Lin Ming hadn’t even fully opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. And the final two of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates were extraordinary; they were equal to half a large boundary in body transformation.

The first six gates of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates could enhance various attributes of the human body. But in terms of increasing one’s comprehensive combat strength, they were inferior to the Gate of Life and the Gate of Death.

The Gate of Life was located at the heart and controlled the power of life.

After opening the Gate of Life, a martial artist’s fires of life would be incomparably vibrant and vivid. Their flesh, blood, organs, all of it would be able to regenerate at incredible rates. Even one’s blood vitality and fires of life, as long as they didn’t suffer some injury past 50%, could still be slowly restored.

This sounded like a gate that could increase a martial artist’s defensive and recovery abilities, but it wasn’t so. The most vital role of the Gate of Life lay in its attack potential!

To be able to regenerate one’s blood vitality and fires of life was an absolutely monstrous ability!

For a martial artist, their life source was extremely fragile. Once their fires of life weakened or they lost their blood essence, that often meant that their life force would diminish, their bodies would wither, and they would become increasingly feeble until they even dropped realms. To think of advancing further in the future in such a state was an absolute impossibility.

There were many wounds that could do this. For instance, the master of that red bamboo hat woman that Lin Ming had seen at the Imperial City Auction was one such case. She had likely reached the World King realm, but because of some grievous injury she suffered, she had dropped boundaries.

But after Lin Ming opened the Gate of Life, as long as he didn’t lose over half of his blood vitality or fires of life then he could slowly restore himself. This allowed him to use a singular move in future battles, an overwhelming one that others rarely used.

That was…

To combust one’s blood essence!

Once a martial artist combusted their blood essence, they could use their life force as a source of strength and instantly increase their combat strength to another level. In a time of crisis, if a martial artist burnt 30-40% of their blood essence, they could completely turn the tide of battle.

Lin Ming sat down on a nameless mountain peak. The pigeon egg-sized Esoteric Immortality Pill was grasped in his hands and the Phoenix Blood Spear was stabbed into a deep red rock in front of him. On top of the Phoenix Blood Spear there was a baby-shaped spirit crystal; this was the Nine Aperture Spirit Crystal.

After Mo Eversnow used the nine aperture spirit crystal, it had shrunk to an eighth of its original size. Now the rest would be used to nourish the Phoenix Blood Spear’s artifact spirit.

Woosh!

Lin Ming suddenly extracted the Phoenix Blood Spear and without flinching, violently thrust it at his chest!

The sharp Phoenix Blood Spear pierced through his body, cutting through his ribs and finally tearing into his heart. Blood splashed out into the air!

Without a moment’s hesitation, Lin Ming drew out the Phoenix Blood Spear. With his other hand, he thrust the Esoteric Immortality Pill into the gaping wound, directly into the opening he had cut in his heart. He submerged the pill into his heart and allowed it to fuse with him!

According to the records contained within the Celestial Tyrant Manual, the Esoteric Immortality Pill had to be sealed within the heart.

The Gate of Life was located in the heart. Once the Esoteric Immortality Pill was sealed into the heart, the medicinal potency within would be washed out using the flow of blood. The energy within it would be activated, allowing him to flush through the Gate of Life in a single go!

The pain of a pierced heart wasn’t much to Lin Ming in comparison to all he had experienced so far. But as the power of the Esoteric Immortality Pill erupted, Lin Ming felt his body shake. It was like a heavy hammer smashed into his heart, nearly causing his heart to stop beating.

A massive amount of energy had exploded in Lin Ming’s heart. This sort of impact force could be imagined.

However, up until now, Lin Ming had experienced the impact of many brutal and tyrannical pills. In addition, after swallowing the dragon marrow, absorbing the supreme dragon bone, and opening the sixth of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, his body had nearly reached an imperishable diamond state. If a normal essence gathering system martial artist were to allow the power within the Esoteric Immortality Pill to erupt in their heart, their heart would have exploded into pieces.

And at this time, in front of Lin Ming, Mo Eversnow used her battle spirit to activate the nine aperture spirit crystal. She drew out fire from the spirit artifact furnace to ignite the spirit crystal.

The nine aperture spirit crystal began to slowly soften.

Mo Eversnow flicked her fingers and three dragon bone relics flew into the nine aperture spirit crystal. Everything was being heated up together.

These dragon bone relics were the remainders left over after she had finished refining the Esoteric Immortality Pill. In order to refine the Esoteric Immortality Pill, 27 dragon bone relics was enough. Mo Eversnow didn’t waste any extra. With these three leftover dragon bone relics, she began to refine their essence within the flames to fuse them into the Phoenix Blood Spear!

The artifact spirit within the Phoenix Blood Spear had been personally formed by Lin Ming. Moreover, this artifact spirit had gone through the baptism of heavenly tribulation together with Lin Ming. The quality of it was extremely high. Once it grew in the future, it would definitely be capable of being Lin Ming’s life spirit treasure.

The three dragon bone relics had already been slowly melted for two months in the fires of the furnace. Now they were quickly fused into the Phoenix Blood Spear without the least bit of resistance.

Sword like jade, saber like tiger, spear like dragon.

Once a spear gained its own mind and wisdom it would be like an Azure Dragon soaring out of the ocean, roaming into the highest heavens, unstoppable!

The characteristics of the dragon bone relics just happened to perfectly suit a spear. To fuse them into a spear spirit was the best use of them.

In addition, the Phoenix Blood Spear also contained phoenix blood. This fused well with dragon bone. Dragon and phoenix soaring together, complementing each other’s strength!

Thus this fusion had gone smoothly, beyond any expectations.

Roar – !

A resounding dragon’s cry savagely impacted into the horizon. The Phoenix Blood Spear violently trembled and then the entire spear shot into the sky, diving into the dark clouds. For a time, countless purple arcs of thunder smashed into the Phoenix Blood Spear, dancing around it like a flurry of purple snakes.

Roar – !

The resonant dragon’s cry emerged once more, echoing between the heavens and the earth. Within the world, the faint image of an azure dragon phantom appeared. One could see flashing blue dragon scales, dragon horn, and dragon claws, all of it overflowing with a lifelike chill!

After fusing with the three dragon bone relics and the nine aperture spirit crystal, the Phoenix Blood Spear had undergone another evolution.

Woosh!

The Phoenix Blood Spear shot down from the highest heavens, crashing towards the earth like a raging meteor. The extreme speed caused friction with the air and a tail of blazing flames followed the descent of the spear. With a rumbling sound, the Phoenix Blood Spear broke through a mountain peak, thrusting deep underground and causing lava and flames to spew forth.

“What a wonderful spear!”

Even the hard-to-impress Mo Eversnow couldn’t help but cry out in praise.

The truth was that all in all, the rank of the Phoenix Blood Spear could only be considered a medium-grade spirit artifact. This was because the materials used to forge the body of the Phoenix Blood Spear weren’t too good and the spear spirit hadn’t fully grown.

But, with the Phoenix Blood Spear having undergone tempering through heavenly tribulation, a great deal of the power of heavenly tribulation had been retained within the spear shaft. Also, the source spear spirit was not what other spirit artifacts’ artifact spirits could compare with. As Lin Ming grew, the Phoenix Blood Spear would also grow. It was hard to estimate just how much it could continue growing.

Mo Eversnow no longer paid attention to the Phoenix Blood Spear. She turned to look at Lin Ming. At this time, Lin Ming’s entire body was covered in hazy golden light. He seemed like a golden Buddha, making it hard for one to look straight towards him.

Opening the Gate of Life wasn’t easy. There were enormous risks associated with taking the Esoteric Immortality Pill.

In the past, Mo Eversnow herself had taken this pill, so she was well aware of just what its effects were like. Or course, the foundation of Lin Ming’s mortal body was better than hers in the past. Thus, Mo Eversnow never worried that Lin Ming would experience some accident in opening the Gate of Life. And looking at him now, the situation was much better than she expected.

Mo Eversnow’s vision pierced through Lin Ming. She could see the inner workings of his body, his flesh and his blood. She could see the fires of life burning within him like a raging conflagration, a flaming mountain so great and high it seemed that it would scorch the skies.

As Mo Eversnow saw this, a rare smile crossed her face. Lin Ming’s talent was much better than she had estimated.

“Perhaps… he really might be able to open the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, achieving the peak in both the essence gathering and body transformation systems! I have no idea just what state he will be able to reach in the future…” Mo Eversnow whispered to herself. Her eyes grew increasingly bright. Her goal was to have Lin Ming become an Empyrean in the future!

This ambition was incredibly enormous, even impossible. If others were to learn of it, they would certainly scoff at her hubris.

Without mentioning anything else, even someone who became the champion of the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting would only have a suffocatingly slim hope of becoming an Empyrean in the future. And in Mo Eversnow’s opinion, it was hard to tell what result Lin Ming would obtain, whether that was top 10, top five, or even higher.

Of course, this was also because Lin Ming was far too young. Compared to the average age of the young elites entering the First Martial Meeting, he would be around 10 years younger.

Boom! Boom! Boom! Boom!

Lin Ming’s heartbeat reverberated through the world. The sound became increasingly loud and increasingly strong. At the start it was like a heavy drum, but then it slowly transformed into a rolling thunderclap. Finally, every beat of Lin Ming’s heart caused the earth to shake and lava to gush forth.

The mountain peak that Lin Ming sat on began to crack. Countless bits of rock tumbled down the mountain as a cloud of dust rose.

Every time blood passed through his heart, it would wash out a massive amount of energy. This energy nourished the entirety of Lin Ming’s body. This state continued for several hours. Slowly, the energy within Lin Ming reached the limit. The pigeon egg-sized Esoteric Immortality Pill had shrunk to the size of a fingernail.

At this time, the rest of the Esoteric Immortality Pill cracked apart. With an explosive ringing sound, energy erupted from all over. The mountain peak that Lin Ming sat on collapsed!

Lin Ming let out a loud and happy cry, his howls reaching through the skies and washing away all the clouds.

At this moment, he had opened the seventh of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, the Gate of Life!

Chapter 1169 – Finally Stepping Into the Divine Sea

Training passed without sense of time. Unknowingly, three months went by.

Because Lin Ming displayed Heavenly Dao Judgment, there was a deficit of blood energy within his body. However, he had restored this half a month ago. According to the Celestial Tyrant Manual, the less blood essence one consumed, the faster it would regenerate. If one consumed a great deal such as 50%, then it might even take over half a year to recover. If one consumed over 50%, then not even the Gate of Life’s powerful life force restoring abilities would be able to completely restore it.

After three months, Lin Ming’s essence, energy, and divine had reached the limit. The inner world seed within him had shrunk to the size of a grain of rice and was verging on the edge of eruption.

The more concentrated the world seed was, the greater the explosive force would be once it erupted.

Hu hu hu –

In the dimensional realm, strong winds stirred. Endless heaven and earth origin energy gathered, forming a massive whirlpool-shaped origin energy cloud in the sky. The central focal point of this origin energy cloud was a 100,000 foot high crimson mountain peak. Lin Ming sat at the very summit of this peak, deep in meditation.

100,000 feet was nearly 50 miles. If this were the Sky Spill Continent, this altitude would have long since pierced through the primal chaos heavens.

But in this sealed world, this height only just touched the infinite thunder clouds in the sky, bringing them in reach of one’s fingertips.

“It’s time.”

Lin Ming slowly opened his eyes from meditation. He stood up, the strong winds surging past him. Lin Ming’s white clothes violently fluttered in the air as his long hair whipped about him. Beside him, 12 thick iron chains were like 12 dragons, one end wrapped around the mountain peak with the other end extending into the vast and boundless skies.

Three months of accumulation… no, it should be 10 years of accumulation. Lin Ming had first crossed Life Destruction at 22 years of age. Now, nearly 10 years had passed. Everything so far had been for this final moment!

And the nine stages of Life Destruction had taken Lin Ming 10 years of time. He had nearly crossed a stage each year! Solid, step-by-step, steady and without a single shortcut taken.

This speed was considered relatively slow for a Divine Realm genius. However, such a patient and steady cultivation speed had brought tremendous benefits to Lin Ming. It had formed the foundation for him to hurtle into the future, overcoming all!

Today, Lin Ming would finally break into the Divine Sea.

Divine Sea, Divine Transformation, Divine Lord, these three large boundaries and nine small boundaries were collectively called the Nine Divine Shifts, similar to the nine stages of Life Destruction. Ninefall was to overcome mortality and the Divine Sea was to transform into the divine. After reaching the Divine Sea, Lin Ming would have completed his transformation from mortality and began stepping into the realm of god.

Hu –

Hu –

The strong winds became increasingly violent! The center of the origin energy cloud turned into a funnel that came extending downwards. In the skies, dark clouds extended for 10,000 miles, with countless flashing arcs of thunder shining from within as if an immortal god of thunder swelled in there. And beneath the mountain peak, an inexhaustible sea of lava and flames surged about. Volcanic explosions continued without end, sending molten lava tumbling into the skies!

Lin Ming took out the Boundless World Pill from his spatial ring. All of the energy within his body was gathered in his dantian, rushing into his world seed without a care for the consequences. The Heretical God Force opened, the blood of the Ancient Phoenix combusted. Together with the endless origin energy in the clouds above him, Lin Ming crazily absorbed it all!

As energy constantly entered him, the world seed within Lin Ming’s dantian began to radiate a blinding light. The world seed continued to shrink, going from the size of a grain of rice to the size of a needle’s eye, and still condensing even beyond that!

In the legends, when the universe first formed, it had begun from an infinitesimally small point. All of the grandmist energy in creation had been concentrated in that tiny dot, finally exploding outwards and creating the endless universe.

Now, the formation of Lin Ming’s inner world followed the same principles as the eruption of the universe.

“Boundless World Pill!”

Lin Ming already felt that his inner world had been compressed to the limit. Then, he crumbled the Boundless World Pill in his hands.

As the pill shattered, the world spirit sealed within the center of the pill turned into an incomparably pure world power that flew into Lin Ming’s body, all of it absorbed by him.

This pill that had been won with 7 trillion violet sun stones was the most valuable peak quality pill that a Divine Sea martial artist could use. Even the top genius of a Great World King Holy Land would find it difficult to use!

Now, this world spirit completely fused into Lin Ming’s world seed. At this time, his world seed finally exploded into pieces!

Countless tiny cracks appeared on this world seed that was smaller than a needle’s eye. An endless amount of energy erupted and Lin Ming’s dantian instantly collapsed!

Bang!

Energy transformed into an incomparably terrifying storm, rushing outwards with utter brutality. All of the clouds for thousands of miles around were completely washed away by the shockwaves!

And after the raging storm of energy dissipated, Lin Ming’s body had actually vanished.

On this 100,000 foot high mountain peak where one could touch the skies, a completely sealed space distortion appeared in the air. The power of time, the power of space, everything was completely twisted up in here. Even light was affected, unable to maintain a straight line.

Lin Ming’s body was sealed up within this space distortion.

This was a cocoon formed from a space distortion!

And Lin Ming was sealed within this cocoon, undergoing his transformation from Life Destruction to the Divine Sea.

The wind had already stopped. The surging thunder and the billowing lava had died down. The endless amount of heaven and earth origin energy no longer formed violent and dangerous fluctuations of energy. Rather, it turned into fist-sized balls of glowing light. These balls of glowing light were mostly red and purple, but there was also yellow, blue, black, green, white, and every other possible color imaginable.

More and more of these glowing balls of light appeared. From tens of thousands to hundreds of thousands to millions and even more, until it seemed like an infinite sea of lights. From a few dozen miles, it rapidly expanded to a thousand miles, filling the entire world with a beautiful glow. Looking from afar, it seemed like a single infinite rainbow had appeared, beautiful and charming, stretching to infinity.

Mo Eversnow slowly floated in the skies, looking at these endless beautiful balls of light as well as the giant cocoon floating within them. Strange and mysterious Law runes emerged from the cocoon and wrapped around it, as fantastical and amazing as a dream.

World seed shattered and dantian transformed into a minor dimension – this was the symbol of the Divine Sea.

And after reaching the Divine Sea, the Laws that a martial artist comprehended would become a part of their system and also become the Heavenly Dao Laws of this minor dimension.

The massive cocoon floating in the air was a projection of the Laws from Lin Ming’s inner world.

At this point, one could only wait. Lin Ming’s body, soul, his everything was being transformed within this cocoon. This process might take one to two months of time.

However, that didn’t mean there were no risks during this period. When Lin Ming truly began stepping into the realm of god, he would have to experience and overcome his heart demons. Because his consciousness had already entered a completely different space-time realization, Lin Ming’s dreams of his heart demons might continue for far longer than a month or two.

All martial artists would have to experience their heart demons when they crossed into the Divine Sea. There were very few people that would die because they couldn’t overcome their heart demons. But, if they were influenced by their heart demons, this would cause the evolution of their soul to be incomplete, making their divine foundation unsteady.

All of this would depend on Lin Ming himself. Mo Eversnow simply meditated in front of the giant cocoon, resting her soul form.

In the cocoon, Lin Ming was like a baby that hadn’t been born. His arms were wrapped around his knees and his body was rolled up. His entire body was naked, no different from a baby. While a baby would soak in amniotic fluid, what Lin Ming rested in was a sea of Laws.

Law runes appeared periodically on Lin Ming’s body before fading away. Lin Ming’s eyes were closed, unaware of all this.

Deep in sleep, Lin Ming’s face was sharp and clear. His long hair hung down, covering his strong back. His tough and long legs were filled with an explosive power. Every inch of his flesh, every fiber of his muscles, it was all a work of perfect art. In this cocoon, his body, his soul, everything he was began to subtly change.

In a dim haze, Lin Ming seemed to return to his childhood, and countless memories of it rushed back into his mind. All of them were strange, confusing, and unable to be discerned clearly.

Then, everything rapidly changed.

He was chased down by Tian Mingzi. Mo Eversnow was destroyed, her soul fading into ashes. He himself was severely wounded. His boundary dropped and he would never be able to advance again in his life.

Then, the secret of the Magic Cube was exposed. Every martial artist under the heavens began to hunt him down. Finally, Lin Ming died without a burial ground and even his homeland, the Sky Spill Continent, was exterminated by Tian Mingzi’s underlings.

All of these scenes were images that suited the weakness in Lin Ming’s heart.

This was a heart demon, all-pervasive and perpetual. As long as a human held desires or fear, they would inevitably have heart demons. The evolution of the soul was followed by the manifestation of these heart demons. If one wasn’t able to overcome them then their divine foundation would be damaged.

Fortunately, Lin Ming’s will was incomparably powerful. He soon discovered the shadows of these fears and completely crushed his heart demons!

He saw himself killing Tian Mingzi, becoming an Empyrean, helping Mo Eversnow reforge her body, rebuilding the Verdant Feather Holy Lands, and then climbing to the peak of martial arts. There, he surpassed the boundary of Empyrean, becoming immortal and everlasting, an existence that would last for eternity. Like this, tens of thousands and hundreds of thousands of years passed. He held the world in his hands, controlled the samsara of life and death, and dominated the Heavenly Dao Laws. This feeling was incomparably realistic and wonderful.

This sort of heart demon was a manifestation of Lin Ming’s desire to reach the peak of martial arts!

Even if Lin Ming’s will was strong, when facing such a heart demon, the effect of his willpower would be greatly diminished. This was because Lin Ming’s will and determination to chase after the peak of martial arts was very strong, and correspondingly this heart demon was also strong, much mightier than anything an ordinary martial artist could dream of.

Lin Ming wandered about this illusionary dream. He seemed to awaken and also fall asleep, again and again. He experienced lifetimes of great sadness and also lifetimes of great joy. Then, his mind suddenly shook. It was like he had seen the ends of the heavens.

There, a phantom of the Magic Cube, Demon Bead, and Purple Card appeared. An icy feeling rushed through his body and Lin Ming suddenly awoke!

As Lin Ming examined his body, he found that his dantian had already disappeared, replaced by a minor dimension!

The world power of the Boundless World Pill had already fused into this minor dimension. The evolution of his world had come to an end.

At this time, outside of the massive cocoon, the endless rainbow origin energy light that extended for thousands of miles suddenly gathered together, forming millions of phoenixes and fire birds that flew towards the center, all of them submerging into the giant cocoon. For a time, a blinding light filled the world, illuminating the heavens with shimmering multicolored lights.

Mo Eversnow’s eyes suddenly shot open. She knew that at this moment, Lin Ming had stepped into the Divine Sea!

Chapter 1180 – Ranking

“So they were merit points. That makes sense. But why do only a small number of people have numbers behind their names, and most martial artists do not?”

Although the golden scroll had many names with numbers behind them, this was because the scroll was simply too large. The names were densely packed together and seemingly endless. If one counted them, the number of people with merit point values behind their names were not even in the thousands.

“It should be that only those with at least a thousand merit points are displayed. Even for an Empyrean, wanting to constantly update the merit points of over 10 quadrillion geniuses wouldn’t be easy! Those with numbers but then vanished were likely people that crossed over 1000 before being killed by other participants or nightmare beasts. Finally, their merit points fell and they fell down the list.”

It was naturally impossible for Empyrean Divine Dream to constantly update the merit points of every single participant with her soul force. No matter how powerful her soul force was, wanting to simultaneously monitor and change the merit points of over 10 quadrillion geniuses was impossible.

What she relied on were the heaven and earth Laws of the Divine Dream World.

Everything within the dreamland was supported by the Divine Dream Laws as a foundation, and the Divine Dream World would complete the statistics of everyone there itself. Empyrean Divine Dream would only need to provide a little bit of energy to display everyone’s scores.

“So that’s what is happening. Those with their scores on the golden scroll are all outstanding cultivators! They are likely to pass the first round of eliminations and possibly even the second round!”

“Yes! Perhaps they will even be noticed by the various large influence, especially those whose merit points rise the quickest!”

In all corners of the Divine Realm, there were countless people holding such discussions.

However, they soon discovered that although they could see the merit points of all the participants in the Divine Realm, it was far too difficult to find specific people.

The golden scroll was simply far too large. It was hundreds of thousands of miles wide and several million miles long. Even a Holy Lord didn’t have the ability to cover the entire golden scroll with their divine sense. And if they did, with the near endless names on the golden scroll, they would overdraw their divine soul before they found who they were looking for.

“I wonder how Wenshu is doing.”

Several old men from Dual Polarity Palace frowned. They all had a half-step Holy Lord cultivation and were important characters of the Zhong Family bloodline. Even with their combined abilities, wanting to find Zhong Wenshu’s name on such a massive list was far too great an undertaking for them.

Of course, Dual Polarity Palace’s Palace Master had the ability to find Zhong Wenshu. However, a World King didn’t have such leisurely time to spend an extremely long time observing the preliminaries. What they cared about were only the finals.

As the several Elders were worrying, a golden carriage soared across the sky. The chariot stopped and a middle-aged man with a jade crown stepped out. He wore a long embroidered golden robe tied together with a purple gold belt. He had a bright smile on his face, and the aura he emitted was one of wealth and extravagance.

“Mm? It’s Imperial City Auction House’s Vice Director!”

The Elders of Dual Polarity Palace quickly recognized the middle-aged man.

“Everyone!” As the middle-aged man stood atop the golden divine carriage floating in the skies, dazzling arcs of golden light shot out into the world, capturing everyone’s attention. As for his voice, it easily spread over an area of 100,000 miles. His cultivation was at the half-step World king!

A half-step World King powerhouse. Within an area of 100,000 miles, that was a peak existence among hundreds of millions of watching people.

Everyone looked at the middle-aged man, not sure what he was about to say.

The middle-aged man faintly smiled and said, “My Imperial City Auction House has been granted authorization by Empyrean Divine Dream to come here and sell inquiry jade slips. You may use these jade slips to search for the ranking of specific participants. If you know the name and sect of a martial artist you may search them to find out how many merit points they have. The number of times you can use this jade slip is unlimited. The price of each jade slip is 10 million violet sun stones. The quantity is limited, so the price is quite high.” The middle-aged man took out a deep green jade slip as he spoke.

This small jade slip only had a simple array formation carved into it that could connect to the golden scroll dreamland projection of the Divine Dream World. Even so, the cost was 10 million violet sun stones!

For some time, all of the wandering martial artists and martial artists of small families and sects were left speechless. This price was simply a killing move. Moreover, it was just to look at the results. It was simply far too luxurious an item.

However, those from distinguished families didn’t care at all. An Elder from Dual Polarity Palace laughed and said, “Sage Shi, you have come at just the right time. I was worried that I wouldn’t be able to find the results of my family’s juniors. Allow me to buy an inquiry jade slip.”

“Alright!” Sage Shi tossed out a jade slip toward the Dual Polarity Palace Elder. At the same time, a spatial ring with violet sun stones contained within it was sent flying to Sage Shi.

Of the 10 million violet sun stones per jade slip, Imperial City Auction House was only able to take in 10% of the profits; the rest was to be given to Empyrean Divine Dream. In fact, these jade slips were created by the disciples of Divine Dream Palace. Although the process of creating them was simple, they contained a faint touch of the Divine Dream Laws, so anyone else could forget about thinking of duplicating them.

Empyrean Divine Dream was managing the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting. Just creating these massive Divine Dream Lights, continuing everything occurring within the Divine Dream Realm, and summoning those massive golden scrolls on all 3000 great worlds of the Divine Realm required an incomparably terrifying amount of energy.

Even if Empyrean Divine Dream was ridiculously rich, she still wasn’t able to use up resources like this, so she also needed a method to earn back some money.

A similar sale was occurring all throughout the golden scrolls of the Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds. The ones responsible for carrying out these sales were the several peak trade associations of each great world. As for those that were able to afford jade slips, they were also great influences.

“I found it! Dual Polarity Palace – Zhong Wenshu, 5300 merit points! Haha, Wenshu has not let us down! Amazing!”

After the Dual Polarity Palace Elder obtained the jade slip he immediately began searching for Zhong Wenshu’s name. Of course, just looking for the name of Zhong Wenshu alone wasn’t enough; there were many people with duplicate names. But with Dual Polarity Palace added on, it was much easier.

“However, Wenshu is not the highest. The True Martial Holy Lands have some people that are even higher. Their top participant already has 6000 merit points.

“That’s already quite good! Let’s go and report this happy news to the family head! But the current ranking is a bit inaccurate. Only later when the points stabilize will we be able to see the true results!”

Meanwhile, Sacred Martial Mansion also bought a divine dream jade slip. This jade slip was enough to display over a dozen names. The three prodigies of Sacred Martial Mansion were among them. Their merit points were around 5000 each.

This was a result that satisfied the many Elders of Sacred Martial Mansion.

At this time, at Good Fortune World, a massive scroll similarly floated in the skies. Underneath this massive scroll, a beautiful woman was also selling divine dream jade slips.

“10 million violet sun stones is far too expensive!”

An Unbroken Cult Elder frowned. They were only an eighth-grade sect. Although they could afford a price of 10 million violet sun stones, it was hard for them to pay such a price only to find out the results a few months ahead of time. But their sect had spent a great deal of wealth and effort to cultivate Yu Youming. They were anxious in discovering just what his results would be like.

“Let’s join together with some other eighth-grade sects to buy one. Buying one alone is a bit too luxurious for us. Our Unbroken Cult’s wealth comes from the hard work of our disciples. We don’t have so much to spare.”

“Right, let’s buy it with others.”

The Elders of the Unbroken Cult devised this new plan and contacted some other eighth-grade sects they were on good terms with. Together, they bought a divine dream jade slip.

They quickly searched for Yu Youming’s results.

“3150 points. This result ranking is between the top one and two million of Good Fortune World!”

Currently, only those in the top 10,000 ranks would show their specific results. The rest only showed a general range.

“A rank between one and two million…” The disciples of the Unbroken Cult discussed amongst each other, not knowing just what concept this rank was.

“It seems that passing through the preliminaries will be impossible,” an Elder said. This was only the ranking of Good Fortune World. If this rank spread through to the entire Divine Realm it had to be multiplied by a factor of 3000. But through the preliminary qualifiers, only 10 million or so people would pass. If one wanted to pass in a great world, one needed to rank in the top 300,000. This would be extremely difficult for Yu Youming.

Even so, these Elders were quite satisfied with this result. They were only an eighth-grade sect, but there were also many geniuses of countless Holy Lands that were unable to pass the qualifiers. Those that were able to advance were at least the geniuses of peak Holy Lands that approached a World King Holy Land in strength.

The other sects that bought the divine dream jade slip with the Unbroken Cult took their turns to look up the disciples they sent. The result was that all of their disciples were ranked below 3 million. One could see the disparity as soon as they compared disciples. It was clear that Yu Youming led them all.

This caused the Elders of the Unbroken Cult to be in a much happier mood. The Vice Sect Master stroked his beard in satisfaction and said, “That Youming child is quite good. It seems we haven’t trained him in vain!”

“Yes! In the future he might even be able to become a half-step Holy Lord!”

The Elders of the Unbroken Cult were all overjoyed with their successes. Moreover, the Elders of the other eighth-grade sects also sourly sent their congratulations. The disciples of the Unbroken Cult that accompanied them here were soon celebrating.

Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan were also amongst these accompanying disciples.

“Big sister, that jade slip is…” Qin Xingxuan whispered.

“I know.”

Mu Qianyu’s heart was also tangled with conflicting feelings. If she was able to search that jade slip she could look for Lin Ming. She didn’t care about Lin Ming’s results; she only wanted to know whether or not Lin Ming joined the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting. If she knew he was participating, she could find out which great world he lived in. She could also confirm which branch palace he was accepted into. At that time, looking for Lin Ming would be far easier.

Her status as an outer court disciple was simply far too low. She and Qin Xingxuan had put in their greatest effort in their tasks and helped to perfectly refine the heaven-step pill. Finally, they managed to obtain two spots that were reserved for janitorial disciples so they could come watch the First Martial Meeting.

To directly speak to an Elder, she didn’t have these qualifications at all.

Mu Qianyu clenched her teeth. She took a brave step forwards and said, “Elder, this disciple has a request to ask of you.”

“Mm?” The Unbroken Cult Elder turned to Mu Qianyu. It was very sudden and surprising for Mu Qianyu to stand out from among the outer court disciples.

Yu Feng, who was responsible for managing the outer court disciples was angered. Her thin eyebrows shot up and she fiercely said, “Mu Qianyu, hurry up and step back if you don’t know customs!”

The rules of the Unbroken Cult were severe and strict. If Mu Qianyu aroused the annoyance of an Elder, as the one in charge of handling these disciples, she would leave a bad impression on the Elders.

However, due to Yu Youming’s results, the Unbroken Cult Elder was in a very good mood. He didn’t bother with Mu Qianyu’s rudeness but instead waved his hand. “What does she want? Let her speak.”

Chapter 1191 – Strength Surpassing A 100 Million

Sacred Martial Mansion’s three prodigies cornered Lin Ming from multiple angles. Sacred Yueping was flushed with anger, wishing that he could tear apart Lin Ming on the spot. As for Sacred Tianhao who was standing beside Sacred Yueping, he had a gloomy complexion as if he were dreading something.

“Lin Ming, right? That’s what those people from the True Martial Holy Lands called you,” Sacred Tianhao said, his words calm and even. He hadn’t exchanged words with Lin Ming before.

Lin Ming remained silent, tacitly agreeing.

“I heard you come from a Holy Land level influence and that your guardians are all on the Crimson Light World. You should understand the situation you’re in and what it means to your future in the True Martial Great World if you continue to oppose my Sacred Martial Mansion,” Sacred Tianhao threatened.

But as his words fell onto the ears of those present, this proved to them that Sacred Tianhao was afraid. Otherwise, why would he use his background to threaten Lin Ming instead of just killing him?

The three prodigies of Sacred Martial Mansion were gathered here, yet they were afraid of Lin Ming. Although that previous collision had a surprising result, everyone was still surprised to hear these words tumble out from between Sacred Tianhao’s lips. This Lin Ming should be extremely abnormal!

“What are you trying to say?” Lin Ming chuckled.

“As people, we should allow a lifeline for each other. If we really fought, I would not fear you. But I do not want to suffer any losses here. Since our merit points have already grown to such a degree, regardless if you die or if I die, both of us will have to pay a deep price for just a single kill. With your strength, you can easily pass the preliminaries. As for us, all we want is to obtain a higher ranking,” Sacred Tianhao honestly said.

Although the three prodigies of Sacred Martial Mansion were labelled the most fantastic three geniuses of the younger generation, Sacred Martial Mansion itself was by no means a monolithic mass of viewpoints. If they wanted to enjoy resources, they also had to constantly bear tests and trials. They needed a dazzling result in the First Martial Meeting to silence all of their opponents at Sacred Martial Mansion, otherwise it would create a great burden on their families.

If killing Lin Ming had been easy, they would have just killed him and gotten it over with. But now, in Sacred Tianhao’s mind, Lin Ming had an unfathomable flavor to him that he just couldn’t place his finger on. Even Zhong Wenshu was killed by his hand. If the three of them fought Lin Ming, there would inevitably be deaths, and they might even lose. In this sort of situation, coming into conflict with Lin Ming simply wasn’t a wise move.

Lin Ming smiled. “Your plan is quite well thought out. You wanted to step on me like an ant, but now you’ve realized that isn’t possible, you’re asking for a truce? Do you think there is such a good matter in this world?” As Lin Ming spoke, he raised the Phoenix Blood Spear and pointed it at Sacred Tianhao’s head.

Sacred Yueping exploded with rage. “Big brother, why are you bothering with his crap! If the three of us join together, there is no way we can lose to him!”

Sacred Tianhao’s complexion became thoroughly grim. “It seems you would rather do things the hard way. After this First Martial Meeting, prepare yourself for the anger of Sacred Martial Mansion! Fight!” Sacred Tianhao shouted out and the three of them began to attack.

Sacred Tianhao stood still, but as for Sacred Yueping and Sacred Yanran, they charged Lin Ming from two different directions!

“Deep Earth Force Field!”

A brown energy rushed out from Sacred Tianhao’s body as the Deep Earth Force Field came falling down with overwhelming force. The three prodigies of Sacred Martial Mansion each had their own domain force fields. Since Sacred Yueping’s time enchantment didn’t work on Lin Ming, so Sacred Tianhao instead sent out his Deep Earth Force Field.

This force field used the Earth Laws as its foundation. As long as one was placed within this force field, they would have to bear the crushing pressure of the mountains and earth. If one’s cultivation was insufficient, they would directly be pulverized into mush. If one’s cultivation was sufficient, they would still be restrained. The domain would even damage their organs.

As the Deep Earth Force Field came down, all of the surrounding martial artists felt a stuffiness in their chest. They all rapidly began to move away. At this time, they were already very far from Sacred Tianhao, and they weren’t bearing the brunt of his attack. Even so, they felt as if someone had dropped a mountain on their backs, making it difficult to even breathe. The power of this force field could be imagined.

At this time, Sacred Yanran cried out and turned into a red afterimage as she hurtled toward Lin Ming. One of her twin wheels was aimed at Lin Ming’s throat and the other was aimed between his legs; this was a violent and sinister attack!

The instant that Sacred Yanran attacked, Sacred Yueping also fused the Concept of Haste from his Time Laws into her body. Because of the grandmist space, he couldn’t slow down Lin Ming’s speed with the Time Laws, but speeding up Sacred Yanran was actually simple and easy, and the effect was nearly the same.

The three joined forces to attack together. This tacit understanding and battle coordination originated from years of training and fighting together. Now that they displayed it, it was extremely fierce and swift!

These attacks left the surrounding martial artists breathless with wonder. Even the red bamboo hat woman was a bit startled. She didn’t fear any one of Sacred Martial Mansion’s three prodigies; she would be able to defeat any of them in a one versus one. But when the three of them attacked together, their combat strength actually increased by several times. This was something even she felt a bit of dread toward.

Facing the Deep Earth Force Field that overwhelmed the world, facing the ruthless attack of Sacred Yanran combined with Sacred Yueping’s enhancements, Lin Ming suddenly bellowed out, all of the joints in his body releasing explosive crackling sounds.

Eight Inner Hidden Gates – seven gates all open!

Ang -!

A dragon’s roar directly impacted through the heavens, washing away the clouds. This dragon roar came from the explosive sounds of Lin Ming’s bones.

After opening seven gates, Lin Ming’s strength instantly rose to 40 million jins, and a titanic Azure Dragon phantom appeared behind him.

40 million jins of strength supported by his dragon bone fused skeleton that was harder than divine iron, just what sort of strength would erupt!?

Bang!

Sacred Tianhao who was renowned for his strength was actually shaken and sent stumbling backwards by Lin Ming’s terrifying explosion of pure strength. His true essence became chaotic and his organs were injured. At the same time, Lin Ming thrust out his spear, meeting Sacred Yanran with his extreme speed.

Sacred Yanran’s complexion instantly paled!

“Die!”

Lin Ming showed neither pity nor compassion. The Phoenix Blood Spear came pounding down mercilessly with a terrifying strength behind it. Sacred Yanran’s hand shook and the green ring spirit artifact in her hand was sent flying away with even her wrist bones fracturing.

Sacred Yanran screamed as the Phoenix Blood Spear smashed into her. Her true protective true essence exploded as she was sent crashing away! The speed at which she was sent back was even faster than her speed rushing forwards, leaving all the surrounding martial artists unable to even muster a response.

“Third sister!”

Sacred Yueping wanted to save Sacred Yanran with the Time Laws’ Concept of Stagnation, but at this time, he felt a boundless and potent strength covering him; this was the grandmist space.

He turned his head and was met with the blazing radiance of thunder and fire sparkling in front of him. The violent energy had reached him and was about to explode.

He had no time to bother with Sacred Yanran!

Peng!

Sacred Yanran smashed into a rock wall like a falling meteor. This rock wall was a hundred times harder than steel and yet she was struck 700-800 feet into this rock wall, forming a human-shaped hole. Sacred Yanran vomited out a mouthful of blood as her bones shattered.

At the same time, the power of thunder and fire from the Heretical God Seedling exploded around Sacred Yueping and Sacred Tianhao!

Bang!

A terrifying explosion erupted as true essence shockwaves manically surged outwards. Massive block rocks were blown into fragments and all the surrounding martial artists were forced back again and again.

At this time, Lin Ming rushed into the rampaging shockwaves, the Phoenix Blood Spear in his hands crashing down at Sacred Tianhao!

Sacred Tianhao’s complexion completely changed. As he saw the Phoenix Blood Spear falling down on him, he didn’t dare to use his heavy sword to meet it. The disparity in strength was too great!

“Lin Ming, Sacred Martial Mansion will make you pay a deep price for this!”

Sacred Tianhao was well aware it was impossible for him to avoid Lin Ming with his speed. He grasped his heavy sword and swung it toward Lin Ming’s head, hoping that they would both perish here together.

But Lin Ming only sneered.

Gold battle spirit – will projection!

The gold large success grandmist battle spirit howled out from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows. The space 10 feet around Lin Ming came under the control of his will. Countless will tentacles wrapped around Sacred Tianhao, binding his every movement!

Sacred Tianhao felt as slow as an insect trapped in a spiderweb. Although he himself had a silver large success battle spirit, the difference was simply too great against Lin Ming. His battle spirit couldn’t play a role.

With a burst of strength, he forcefully broke free from the battle spirits. Although Sacred Tianhao near instantly freed himself from the shackles of the will tentacles, it was already far too late!

The Phoenix Blood Spear’s edge approached Sacred Tianhao’s heart; it wasn’t even possible for him to bring Lin Ming down with him anymore.

“Earth Shield!”

Sacred Tianhao wildly cried out. A thick brown barrier formed all around his body s a sandy brown layer of earth crawled up his body, forming an armor of earth. The Earth Laws represented the pinnacle of defense amongst the five elements. Sacred Tianhao wanted to use the power of absolute defense to defend against the Phoenix Blood Spear.

But Lin Ming ignored it all and continued to thrust his spear forwards.

Peng!

The Phoenix Blood Spear stabbed into Sacred Tianhao’s earth essence armor. The spiritual energy seemed to have a mind of its own, pervasively digging into every crack and weak point of Sacred Tianhao’s defense. This was one of the abilities of a spirit artifact.

However, Sacred Tianhao’s earth armor kept it all at bay.

Lin Ming wasn’t perturbed at all. He thrust out his spear once more!

Spear after spear, Lin Ming’s striking speed had reached a nearly unimaginable degree. Every spear was faster and stronger than the last. The power of these spear strikes began to add together, multiplying, like a surging tide with wave upon wave behind it.

Ka ka ka!

With a light sound, a crack appeared in Sacred Tianhao’s earth armor. A cold sweat began to pour down his head.

He finally realized that the reason Lin Ming struck out so many times with his spear was because he was superimposing their strength together!

But it was already too late!

After Lin Ming stabbed his spear out 99 times, with the 100th spear, all of that strength erupted at once!

“Celestial Tyrant Manual – Hundred Layered Waves!”

Only by thrusting out his spear 99 times before and saving all of that strength would the final eruption display its true strength. This was far stronger than a hastily sent out version of the Hundred Layered Waves!

40 million jins of strength was displayed again and again with the Hundred Layered Waves, adding up again and again. In that final moment, Lin Ming’s strength broke through 100 million jins!

This was the complete Hundred Layered Waves spear strike!

Bang!

With this strike, Sacred Tianhao’s earth essence barrier shattered, fully disintegrating, and even his earth essence armor completely broke apart. Sacred Tianhao’s chest was torn open by the Phoenix Blood Spear. His ribs were crushed and his heart and lungs blew apart. He vomited a mouthful of blood and was sent flying backwards like a broken ragdoll, all sensation and strength rapidly fleeing from his body.

The strongest Sacred Tianhao of Sacred Martial Mansion’s three prodigies had been defeated by Lin Ming’s spear strike. In addition with the grievously wounded and dying Sacred Yanran, this meant that Lin Ming had thoroughly won this battle!

Chapter 1195 – Lin Ming’s Ranking

Everyone realized what was happening. That’s right, according to how the competition was being held so far in the preliminaries, everyone had their own corresponding merit points. If so, this merit point ranking system could be expanded to the entire Divine Realm!

The previous ranking had been held within each great world, but now there was a ranking that encompassed the entire Divine Realm!

Of the 3000 great worlds, there were only several hundred thousand participants that were chosen to be on this ranking list.

To put it more accurately, there were only 300,000 people on this list!

On average, that meant that every great world had 100 people represented on this ranking list!

As the martial artists searching the Divine Seal Decree rankings realized this, they were all startled. A deep feeling of awe swelled up from within their hearts.

This ranking list was born from the 10 quadrillion geniuses of the entire Divine Realm!

What sort of overwhelming momentum was this!

No wonder it was called the Divine Seal Decree!

In truth, these people had already passed the preliminaries ahead of time. This was because 10 million people would make it through at the end of the preliminaries and yet there were only 300,000 geniuses ranked on the Divine Seal Decree.

Moreover, these 300,000 were only chosen for the primaries. But even in the primaries, as long as one was listed on this ranking list, they would be considered a chosen pride of heaven amongst all chosen prides of heaven. In the future, they could become late Holy Lords, peak Holy Lands, and for those ranked near the top, they could even become half-step World Kings!

It had to be known that these were all top 100 ranked existences of a great world!

“Amazing! Amazing!”

“What amazing grandeur. The Divine Realm First Martial Meeting held by Empyrean Divine Dream may be the most glorious occasion for the last several million years. There is even a total ranking list that includes all the participating geniuses of the Divine Realm. This is truly an unprecedented magnificence.”

“There’s nothing that can be done about it. Besides Empyrean Divine Dream, there is no other Empyrean that has such ability. In the last Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, 100 trillion geniuses were gathered together in a grand tournament, which cost an incalculable amount of resources. Wanting to create a total ranking list for 10 quadrillion people should be an impossible matter. Even 100 trillion people would be extremely difficult to fairly judge.”

The Elders of the Unbroken Cult and other sects sighed with emotion. As it stood, it was impossible for Yu Youming to be ranked on such a list of participants. He was ranked between 250,000 and 400,000 of the Good Fortune Great World. But if this were spread to the entire Divine Realm, he would likely be ranked from 800 million to a billion.

At a ranking of a billion, how could he possibly be included in a ranking list of the top 300,000?

“Ah, what a pity…”

The Unbroken Cult Great Elder shook his head, secretly wondering why there wasn’t a ranking list that included just the Good Fortune Great World.

As he sighed again, he suddenly heard a cry of alarm.

“Ah!”

“Mm?”

The Great Elder frowned. In front of so many Elders from other sects, shouting out and making a fuss was extremely improper behavior.

He turned around to see that the disciple who cried out in alarm was the inner court disciple Yu Feng.

The Great Elder had some impressions toward this disciple. Although her cultivation talent wasn’t too good, she was skilled in handling interpersonal relationships and other miscellaneous matters. She was skilled in management and disciplined her subordinates severely. If she was given a chore or a mission, she would accomplish it in time without making a mistake. The Great Elder had originally had some thoughts about promoting her to an internal affairs manager, but how could she be so disrespectful today?

“Yu Feng, what are you doing?”

The Great Elder grunted out, his complexion cold.

Yu Feng was so scared she jumped and forgot to immediately apologize. With one hand covering her mouth and another hand waving at the empty air, she haltingly said, “Great Elder, I… over there! I-I…”

She couldn’t believe her eyes. She really couldn’t believe her eyes!

She didn’t want to speak because it was something even she didn’t dare to believe. However, at this time, the Great Elder’s complexion became increasingly gloomy. What was she trying to hide? She was actually acting like this in front of so many honored guests. Acting like this would naturally leave a bad impression, and if she continued to hide whatever it was, she would only make things worse.

“What is it, stop hesitating and being impolite! Hurry up and say what it is!”

This was already an extremely severe criticism. If it weren’t for the guests present, Yu Feng would have been directly punished by the Great Elder.

Yu Feng’s face paled. She could only truthfully say, “Over there. The name on the Divine Seal Decree is…”

Yu Feng pointed her finger in a direction of the Divine Seal Decree. Everyone looked over, and even the Great Elder frowned and turned.

The general direction that Yu Feng pointed toward was very far away. Because of this distance, every character seemed to cover the heavens and earth, exuding a daring and indomitable spirit. There were many names grouped together, but a martial artist could easily identify them with their sharpened eyesight.

An unbelievable name popped out in front of the Great Elder and the many disciples.

Ancient Phoenix Clan – Lin Ming!

Merit points: 9,918,670!

Divine Seal Decree – ranked 29,876!

“Ancient Phoenix Clan, Lin Ming!?”

How could it be this name!?

The Great Elder was stunned. Next to him, a disciple who had heard Mu Qianyu make her request in the past and also many other Elders stared with wide eyes, their mouths falling open and not closing for a long time.

For them, although they hadn’t placed Lin Ming’s name in their hearts from the start, a martial artist still had extraordinary memory. It was naturally impossible to forget a name they heard just a little while ago.

What was going on here?

If it were just the name by itself, there could be said to be duplicates. But when the Ancient Phoenix Clan background was added on, it was nearly impossible for it to be a duplicate. Moreover, the most important factor was that the Great Elder had already searched for the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Lin Ming and obtained only one result. This was undoubtedly Lin Ming!

Lin Ming, Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan’s husband!

Mu Qianyu? Qin Xingxuan?

The Unbroken Cult Great Elder looked at the two women and nearly bit on his tongue.

As for Yu Feng who was in charge of Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan, her legs softened, wobbling. As she thought of her actions to them in the past, she trembled.

This was the Divine Seal Decree! Moreover, this ranking wasn’t in the hundreds of thousands, but in the top 30,000!

What sort of concept was that? That meant that Lin Ming should be someone ranked in the top 10 of a great world. This meant there were countless geniuses of World King Holy Lands that were trampled underneath his feet!

If such a person grew up in the future, it was highly likely they would become a half-step World King, an existence that could cause an ordinary Holy Land to feel immense fear. They would become someone that a World King Holy Land would try everything for to win over.

As for the Unbroken Cult, they were only an eighth-grade sect. In their sect, the most powerful person was a Divine Lord powerhouse. They didn’t even have a half-step Holy Lord. For such a top character, the entire Unbroken Cult was nothing more than a speck of dirt.

The Great Elder blankly looked toward Qin Xingxuan and Mu Qianyu. The other Elders of the Unbroken Cult, the Elders of the other sects, Yu Feng, the Unbroken Cult core disciples, inner court disciples, outer court disciples, everyone looked at Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan.

These two women had such a husband?

At this time, Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan also recovered from their shocked states. Lin Ming’s name had appeared on the top 30,000 ranks of the Divine Seal Decree. This meant that he already passed the preliminaries ahead of time. It was more accurate to say that to Lin Ming, these preliminaries no longer mattered. All he had to focus on was just how high his final result would be in the First Martial Meeting.

“Our husband is actually ranked in the top 10 of a great world?” Mu Qianyu murmured in disbelief. The Yu Youming that she thought was very strong was only ranked between 250,000 and 400,000 of a great world. The difference between him and Lin Ming could be seen from this!

Although Mu Qianyu had always said she believed in Lin Ming and believed that he would establish his own fame in the Divine Realm, she never imagined his fame would be so great!

“Big Sister Qianyu, we… we…” Qin Xingxuan couldn’t find the words to speak. Her mood was incomparably complex and also incomparably excited. Although she said she didn’t care about Lin Ming’s result and only cared about his safety, with his true results being so extraordinary, she was actually extremely proud of him. This was her husband! The man most intimate to her and also the most important man in her life. In particular for Qin Xingxuan; she could be said to have grown up with Lin Ming.

For the Unbroken Cult, their Elders were already smiling from ear to ear if one of their disciples reached the top several hundred thousand rankings of a great world. But her husband actually ranked in the top 10! How could she not be proud of him?

“Little Sister Xingxuan, we can see him, we can definitely see him!” Mu Qianyu couldn’t help but weep. She was excited and thrilled, but her mind was still clear.

A mother’s honor rose with her son, and a wife’s honor rose with her husband. With Lin Ming’s status being so high now, it was likely the Unbroken Cult would send someone to escort them directly to see Lin Ming.

Moreover, with Lin Ming’s results being so prominent, even in the vast sea of people that was the First Martial Meeting, wanting to find him would be extremely easy. If so, all troubles they thought they would have in searching for him were no more!

To see Lin Ming once more, how could Mu Qianyu not be sobbing with happiness?

As Mu Qianyu realized this, she turned back to look at the Unbroken Cult Great Elder. At this time, as the Great Elder saw Mu Qianyu look at him, his expression was extremely wonderful.

Chapter 1197 – Empyrean Descendant

The Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds each had a corresponding great world in the Divine Dream World. Within these great worlds, endless slaughter was occurring every second.

During the second round of eliminations, the rankings were pulled even further apart!

And, within that grand Divine Seal Decree, the ranked 30,000 or so Lin Ming naturally wasn’t the most noticeable. Rather, it was the 10 kings of the ranking list!

The many spectators of the Divine Realm 3000 great worlds were all staring at these magnificent names. To them, these names all represented legends.

Especially the first name. That was the most radiant of all. The writing style of this name was written exactly the same as the Divine Sea Decree title, and the names of these characters were also of the same size. They were over twice the size of the other names!

Demondawn Heavenly Palace – Xiao Moxian!

Merit points: 116,507,820!

Divine Seal Decree ranking: one!

This was the only person whose merit points had surpassed a hundred million. Moreover, it was a great deal more than the second place!

The name of Xiao Moxian was very strange. It was a name that meant little demon fairy. In truth, this name seemed more like a nickname, and also the name of a woman.

The prefix of Demondawn Heavenly Palace meant that this woman didn’t originate from Divine Dream Palace. In fact, no one from Divine Dream Palace participated in the preliminaries. They directly passed through the preliminaries.

At this time, within Lightmend World, four martial artists were violently battling a massive snake, weapons held in each of their arms.

This snake had a body as thick as a tree as well as three giant heads. Each head spat out a different colored cloud of gas. When any plant life was touched by these gas clouds, it would immediately decay and wither into nothing. Even the swamp would melt away when touched by these gas clouds.

If Lin Ming was here, he would estimate that after killing this python he would be able to receive several thousand merit points. This was absolutely a vicious beast that would cause geniuses of ordinary Holy Lands to flee as far as they could.

However, these four martial artists were able to battle this giant snake. It was clear that their strength was quite formidable.

The snake and the four men had been in a brutal melee for some time already. A scholarly-looking man found an opening and chopped his blade deep into a weak point. The snake stiffened for a moment and then the other martial artists closed in and finished it off.

“Haha! After the second round of eliminations began, the merit points of these nightmare beasts have increased so much!”

“Yes, this big snake actually gave us 5000 merit points, that means that each of us can receive over a thousand merit points. Before this, the highest value nightmare beast only gave us 1800 merit points. This also means that martial artists will accumulate an increasing amount of merit points! It’s possible that the top 50 rankings can be completely changed too! This is our chance to rise.”

“That’s right, us brothers must try harder and crash into the top 50 rankings to give our father some face!”

As the four martial artists were speaking, they were suddenly stunned. With a surprised expression, they all looked to the side and saw that in this swamp, a young woman wearing all black had appeared. She had the appearance of a 15-16 year old girl, and her hair hung down past her shoulders like a waterfall of black ink. Her eyes were dark yet bright, and her forehead was crowned with neatly-trimmed bangs. As she appeared here, she was like a fantastical night spirit.

The young girl carefully patted down her skirt as if she were afraid she would dirty herself with the mud of the swamp, and then began to slowly walk towards the four martial artists.

The four men glanced at each other, a bit dumbfounded. Just who was this girl? If a martial artist was afraid of dirtying themselves in the swamp, they could fly in the air. A martial artist could fly at the Xiantian realm. Was this girl not even a Xiantian realm martial artist?

The scholarly-looking youth of the four men was extremely suspicious. Then, he discovered that this girl was stepping on small leaves that had fallen on the ground. She would rely on just these fallen leaves to support her body, briskly hopping over them.

If she could accomplish this then she could certainly fly. But, why would she be using such a bothersome and tedious method to walk? She was like an innocent girl that was stirring up trouble and thought it amusing to step on these fallen leaves to move forwards.

“Who is this girl? I’ve never seen her before.”

The location that the four men killed nightmare beasts at was the highest quality hunting grounds near their city. In order to hunt here, one needed a certain amount of skill. If this black-clothed girl had been able to come here before, they should have had some impression of her, especially since she had such a unique appearance.

At this time, the black-clothed girl suddenly looked up at the four men. She brightly smiled, but that smile also seemed to have a faint taste of malicious playfulness.

She had a beautiful and charmingly lovable face, but that smile of hers actually revealed a sharp pair of incisors just like a little devil.

“Little girl, what are you smiling at! Who are you, did you come from some nearby city?”

A big fellow from the four martial artists suddenly asked, anger in his voice. If someone appeared here and they didn’t recognize them, this likely meant that they came from some nearby city to harvest merit points.

The black-clothed young girl seemed to not hear a word he said. She only chuckled, her voice like soft tinkling silver bells.

“You bitch, what are you smiling for!? Once I’m done with you, let’s see how you’ll still smile!” The big fellow boorishly said. The scholarly youth frowned, “Third Brother, it might be a bad idea to provoke this girl.”

“So what? She’s just someone from a nearby city that I haven’t seen before. What can a girl like her do to me?”

The big fellow indifferently said.

But at this time, the black-clothed girl giggled and said, “You stupid fool. I don’t come from a nearby city but a nearby great world. I come from Demon God World and all the powerful people there have already been killed by me. I thought it was a bit boring so I came here to play. How many merit points can the lot of you give me?”

“Points? Merit points?” The big fellow’s eyes widened. He immediately responded, “What did you say? You’re from the nearby great world, Demon God World?”

But soon he reacted once more. Why would he believe someone just because they said something? He sneered and said, “What a boastful idiot, it’s like you’re not scared of having your lies seen through. And to think you said you came from a nearby great world, as if you’re so amazing! In this Divine Dream World, how could you possibly travel the vast distance between great worlds? Looking at your soft and fair skin, you’re nothing but a little baby. For a great man like me, you’re not even enough for an appetizer!”

The big fellow laughed, his voice travelling for half a mile. But then, he stopped.

His entire body was paralyzed. With great effort, he bent his head down and saw that there was blood leaking out from his throat and chest. It was like something had pierced through his body and wormed its way in. With his wounds as the center, he could feel the meridians within his body suddenly go cold, freezing over. His consciousness gradually blurred, dimming down as his strength rapidly left his body. This was the feeling of death, and this wasn’t the first time that this big fellow had experienced this.

“I… how did I die?”

This was the big fellow’s last thought before he toppled over.

The other three were all shocked senseless.

“Third Brother!”

The scholarly youth cried out in alarm. But at this time, any sort of reasoning told him that wanting to take revenge for his third brother was impossible. This girl was simply terrifying to the point that those present couldn’t even believe their eyes. She had to be a top ranked martial artist of a great world. As for them, they were only martial artists ranked between 60 and 70.

Just now they hadn’t even seen how their third brother had died!

“Scatter and escape!”

The scholarly youth decisively shouted this command. The other two also sensed the direness of the situation. They used their fastest movement techniques and escaped in different directions.

The little girl was faintly startled. Then, she chuckled and said, “Smart move. I’ll give you all five breaths of time as a reward.”

The little girl shut her eyes and began to count, without any nervousness at all. She was just like someone playing hide and seek.

After counting to five, the young girl suddenly opened her eyes. She smiled and said, “I’m going to chase you now.”

As she spoke, she vanished, her body disappearing into motes of light. In a moment she seemed to have teleported 10 miles away. Then with another flash, she flash-stepped another 20 miles.

It had to be known that the Divine Dream World and the Divine Realm were nearly the same. The space here was extremely stable, and if one wished to pass through space by flash-stepping a short distance, that was extremely difficult to accomplish. This required one to have an extremely high understanding into the Space Laws.

Finally, no one was able to escape from the hands of this young girl.

Their throats all gushed out with blood. As their corpses vanished, a small and thin golden leaf fluttered to the ground. This was clearly what killed them.

“Their merit points are too few; my total score doesn’t seem to have moved at all. I have to look for a top three ranking martial artist in this Lightmend World. I’ll only be able to increase my score by killing them.”

The black-clothed young girl whispered to herself. Her body vanished in motes of light and soon completely disappeared.

……………..

At this time, within an exquisitely carved jade tower, a blue-clothed youth had a cyan sword hanging over his shoulders as he looked at the distant Divine Seal Decree in the horizon.

This youth had a slender and handsome appearance, as if his looks were molded from the purest jade. A pill hung between his eyebrows, looking like a third eye.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Frost Dream, Junior-apprentice Sister Xiao Moxian has indeed managed to obtain first rank. It seems she’ll become extremely famous now. She has surpassed the second ranked martial artist by nearly 30 million merit points. I think that those Great World King Holy Land geniuses of Demon God World are really too pitiful. They don’t even have anyone that is ranked in the top 5000 of the Divine Seal Decree. I estimate that all of them were killed by Junior-apprentice Sister Xiao Moxian. Even the neighboring great worlds might be in for a stroke of bad luck this time. Junior-apprentice Sister’s personality has been well known ever since she was young. She simply loves playing around far too much. She could have directly attended the finals, but in the end she decided to join in the preliminaries to bully everyone instead! This is simply giving no face at all. I think that the Great World King of Demon God World is probably feeling extremely ill!”

Beside this blue-clothed youth was a young girl wearing an icy blue dress. She was obviously the Junior-apprentice Frost Dream that the blue-clothed youth spoke to.

This young girl appeared to be 16-17 years old. Her stature was slender and fluid like an ice sculpture, her fingers were thin and long, and a faint haze covered her entire body. Every single movement of hers caused a bit of ephemeral starlight to sprinkle down, seeming holy and inviolable.

Her looks were also covered in this strange mist so it was impossible to see her face. But, one could vaguely feel that she had perfectly contoured features and eyes like deep spring pools.

The young girl lightly nodded, not responding. She continued to look at the Divine Seal Decree in the far off distance.

The feeling she exuded was like an immortal fairy of frost and rime that lived in the highest heavens: beautiful, charming, and untainted by the sins of the world.

The blue-clothed youth didn’t seem unhappy at all at the young girl’s cold response. Instead, he continued to enthusiastically speak, “And then there’s Junior-apprentice Brother White Yao who is much more collected and reasonable. Although he is also an Empyrean disciple, he is only ranked tenth. He’s not as devilish as Junior-apprentice Sister Xiao Moxian, killing all those Great World King Holy Land geniuses until they are rolling around in their own misery.”

The blue-clothed youth casually said. But, the truth was that in his opinion, this Divine Realm First Martial Meeting was basically a competition between Empyrean descendants. For anyone else to break into their circle was impossible.

Chapter 1198 – The Mysterious Monster

True Martial Great World – dreamland space –

3000 miles southwest of True Martial City, there was a long and winding mountain range called the Demon Sealing Ridge. On Demon Sealing Ridge, the trees towered high into the skies and vicious beasts roamed everywhere. In the real world, the Demon Sealing Ridge was a training ground of normal Divine Sea powerhouses. But in the dreamland space, Demon Sealing Ridge became dozens of times more dangerous. If a normal Divine Sea powerhouse was here then they would die instantly. Even a weak Divine Transformation powerhouse would find their life threatened.

Thus, in this dreamland space, those that came to adventure here were the top 200 ranked masters of the entire True Martial Great World.

Even so, there were still deaths.

Rumble rumble rumble rumble!

A terrifying explosion sounded through the mountains with countless shock waves surging outwards. A group of 10 people were sent soaring backwards, tossed into the air like a handful of straw.

In such an intense explosion, a hideous-looking nightmare beast with its entire body covered with spikes slowly fell to the ground, utterly dead.

This sort of violent hunting scene was a common occurrence on Demon Sealing Ridge. Those people that were capable of killing these vicious nightmare beasts were usually top 100 ranked masters of their great world.

“Huh? What’s this?”

After the martial artists slayed the vicious beast, they discovered that there was a palm-sized purple crystal left behind after the vicious beast’s body disappeared. If one looked carefully, they could see something sealed within the crystal that looked like a tiny green sword. It rushed about within the purple crystal, seeming as if it would break out at any moment.

The martial artists were all shocked. Although they had killed countless nightmare beasts, this was the first time they had seen something like this.

A martial artist hesitated and then carefully picked up the purple crystal. An incomparably cold feeling seemed to dig through his body, sinking through his flesh and blood and even permeating through his soul. He felt as if his entire body was filled with a faintly spiritual feeling, and Laws that he found hard to understand in the past were slowly being perceived…

This sort of dim enlightenment was like a mortal being confounded by a problem, and then finally having a dream and waking up with a blurry solution.

This martial artist suddenly had the strange desire to directly swallow down this purple crystal. This was because he could feel a faint wisdom coming from this purple crystal, and had a premonition that he would obtain great benefits after eating it.

However, he restrained his thoughts and decided to study it first. For some reason, he believed that this purple crystal was condensed with energy completely different from the energy that formed their weapons and clothes. Although all of that was virtual goods that belonged to this dreamland world, this purple crystal gave off an incomparably genuine feeling, as if it were a treasure that belonged in the real world. These fantastical thoughts were something he felt from the moment he touched the purple crystal.

“Ba Dao, what is that?”

The several surrounding martial artists casually asked. Although they felt that this purple crystal was quite extraordinary, they didn’t care too much. After all, this was dreamland space and not the real world. If this was the real world, there was a possibility that it would be an extremely precious heavenly treasure. If so, they would study it, and then divide it equally after estimating its value. And even then, if it was far more precious than what they imagined, they might even fight to the death for it.

But in this dreamland space, all treasures were nothing but dreams that would vanish once they awakened, without leaving a single trace behind. Thus, they didn’t care about this purple crystal too much. Then again, it might not be anything too valuable anyways.

“Nothing. I think it’s just some strange treasure that this nightmare beast swallowed before. I think it’s a bit interesting so I’m going to keep it.”

The martial artist called Ba Dao said as he indifferently tossed the purple crystal into his spatial ring.

Most of his companions didn’t care too much, but there were one or two people that frowned. They felt that Ba Dao’s explanation was a bit too forced. A strange object that the nightmare beast swallowed? Was there something like that?

Moreover, Ba Dao’s words were clearly meant to play down this matter even as he calmly took the purple crystal for himself.

“I think… you should wait a minute.”

Someone suddenly said.

Ba Dao felt his heart drop. He maintained his composure and asked as if he didn’t care too much, “What is it?”

The person who spoke hesitated for a moment, then said, “Friend, things that are found should be examined by everyone here so that we can check if there is any danger… you should know that in this dreamland space, there are countless dangers everywhere. If you take something with you that you find like that, it might be dangerous. It might even be a powerful baby nightmare beast in egg form. If so, then we’ll be in danger!”

This person’s words were quite thoughtful. He didn’t immediately say words that cast a suspicious light on Ba Dao for stealing a treasure, but said something reasonable that no one would be able to reject.

These nightmare beasts were extremely strange existences. No one knew just what they were like before they were born. This purple crystal was bizarre, and even seemed as if there was some living creature sealed within it. There was the possibility that this was the larval form of a nightmare beast.

“That sounds fine. Ba Dao, take out that crystal so that we can take a look. It’s better to be safe than sorry.” Someone echoed.

Ba Dao awkwardly smiled, slowly tracing his spatial ring. He knew that if he didn’t take it out, he would definitely fall under suspicions.

In that moment, he hesitated in his heart. Was it better to just flee from here? But then again, perhaps everything he felt before was nothing but a dream. After all, this sort of matter was itself unbelievable.

“If I made a mistake or thought too much of it then I would be a fool, but… that brief enlightenment on the Laws I felt was indeed real. Just what is this thing?”

Ba Dao thought as he spoke. His movements in taking out the purple crystal were very slow.

“If it really is some wonderful treasure, then being killed in this dreamland space isn’t a problem. At worst I’ll lose some points and my ranking will fall, but I can still catch up. But, before these preliminaries started, Empyrean Vast Universe said that if a participant was killed, they would lose 60% of their virtual treasures. Would this thing disappear? What should I do? Should I make a desperate bet?”

Ba Dao thought. His palms were wet with sweat. His fingers had already touched on his spatial ring for two breaths of time. As this time grew, even some of Ba Dao’s friends felt that something was wrong. In particular, those two people who were suspicious at the start. Their thoughts became grim and they clenched the weapons in their hands.

The atmosphere became increasingly tense. At this moment, a sharp howl suddenly washed over everyone. At the first moment it was in the far off distance, but in just an instant it was right near their ears!

Ba Dao felt his back turn cold as an icy chill thrust into his heart. This freezing killing intent nearly caused his soul to rupture.

Danger!

Ba Dao was greatly shocked. He wanted to throw himself forwards but… it was already too late!

He felt his entire body turn cold as the world became dark around him. His mind blurred and his consciousness rapidly faded as he lost all his senses.

As for his companions, they only saw a brief red light flash in front of them as Ba Dao’s body was completely ripped apart!

“How did he die!? Who killed him!?”

No one had been able to clearly see what happened. They were all stunned. They tightly gripped their weapons and maintained full vigilance of their surroundings.

Then, they discovered that Ba Dao’s spatial ring was crushed by that red shadow just now. As that spatial ring burst apart, nearly everything there was left intact – it was only the purple crystal that vanished!

“Everyone be careful! Keep your backs to each other! We have run into some master, but do not panic, otherwise we will die even faster!”

The leader of the several martial artists shouted out, trying to stabilize the morale of those still standing.

However, his efforts were useless. The disparity was far too great!

As the several martial artists moved closer to each other, that red light flashed once more. Two more people had their corpses split apart as their heads flew into the air. Blood erupted like a fountain from their falling corpses!

“Big Brother!”

Everyone felt an extreme fear rising in their minds. Although this was only a dreamland space, they still felt an immense pressure in the face of such an abnormal opponent!

“Run away!”

The leader crazily shouted. But, he realized that the decision of running away was also meaningless. Everyone here would die without a doubt!

Pu! Pu!

“Ahhhhhh!”

In the instant when the leader turned to flee, he heard the screams of those behind him. He could hear the muffled thumps of their bodies hitting the ground and also the bubbling sound of their blood gushing out from their bodies.

“They all died?”

This thought flashed through the team leader’s mind before he felt his head suddenly lighten. The world spun around him as he saw his headless body from a distance. Then, his body was grasped by an incomparably sharp red-furred claw.

As soon as the claw grasped his body, an unbelievable sight occurred. As his world spun, he could see that his headless corpse suddenly shrank to the size of a tiny ball. His flesh and blood essence, his bones, his organs, everything was sucked away in an instant, leaving nothing behind but his skin and clothes falling to the ground.

He widened his eyes as far as he could, trying to search for the master of that red claw as his vision blurred even more, but all he could see was a faint outline. This figure was as tall as a person and also had a humanoid shape, walking tall on two feet just like a person. And in its claws, it had the purple crystal that Ba Dao had found, seeming as if it would swallow it at any moment.

However, before this martial artist could make out whether this monster was a human or a beast, because of the angle of his spinning head, all he could see was the sky and ground.

“Just… what… is that…”

This was the martial artist’s last thought before his head fell to the ground with a bloody plop.

“Roar! Roar! Roar! Awooo!”

That sharp howl resounded in the world once more, echoing throughout Demon Sealing Ridge as it became further and further away.

This brief battle on Demon Sealing Ridge was not noticed by anyone. This was simply because Demon Sealing Ridge was far too large. Even if that howl was heard by others, it still wouldn’t arouse their suspicion. After all, there were countless roars and howls that filled Demon Sealing Ridge every second of every day.

But slowly, over time, several masters began dying in rapid succession. These masters who died were all top 100 ranked masters of a great world, all of them ruthless and cunning individuals!

And several days later, this news finally spread out!

This was because those people that died were resurrected a day later. For various reasons, they didn’t disclose news of Demon Sealing Ridge’s monster at the start. But, as more and more people died, they were no longer able to conceal what happened.

Everyone was now aware that a red-furred monster had appeared at Demon Sealing Ridge, a bloodthirsty beast with unbelievable strength and speed. Of those that met it, no one had ever managed to survive. Moreover, they couldn’t even confirm whether this red-furred monster was a participant or a vicious beast.

Chapter 1199 – Towards True Martial City

The slaughter within True Martial Great World became increasingly intense as more and more martial artists gathered near True Martial City. Compared to Immemorial Imperial City, True Martial City had far broader grounds for hunting and killing. Just Demon Sealing Ridge itself was nearly a thousand miles long and wide.

Although Demon Sealing Ridge was the highest level hunting ground near True Martial City, not every martial artist chose to go there. For instance, Zhong Wenshu and Sacred Martial Mansion’s three prodigies chose to go to a nameless canyon nearby Demon Spirit Ridge. This canyon was winding and deep and also very well hidden. The level of the nightmare beasts within also wasn’t low.

The reason they had chosen this place was mainly for safety.

Whether it was Lin Ming or certain masters of True Martial City, it was possible they could be hunted down and slain.

“Did you hear the stories? It seems that some strange red-furred monster has appeared at Demon Sealing Ridge that especially hunts down top masters. Even masters ranked similarly to us have been killed.” Sacred Tianhao solemnly said.

“That is a matter that only the top 10 ranked masters need to deal with; we do not have to worry about it. It also shouldn’t affect our place, so we’re much safer here. Moreover, five months have already passed. The second round of eliminations approaches. There should be only a month left. During the second round of eliminations, the number of participants eliminated will be even more exaggerated than in the last round. I think that Lin Ming will start to move.”

“I wonder what the little bastard is doing so sneakily that he only comes out at the end. Whatever, we just have to avoid him and we’re fine.”

As Lin Ming was mentioned, Sacred Yueping grit his teeth. When the three prodigies of Sacred Martial Mansion fought Lin Ming, the disparity between them had been an unsurpassable moat. It was a vivid memory that would never be erased from his mind, the shame of his life.

Sacred Yueping’s guess wasn’t wrong. Ever since Lin Ming killed Sacred Martial Mansion’s three prodigies, he had continued to be closed up and didn’t even go out to hunt once. His ranking rapidly fell.

As the second round of eliminations began, the merit value of nightmare beasts suddenly experienced a massive rise. The many participants rapidly accumulated merit points. With Lin Ming not doing anything at all, his ranking naturally fell as his merit points remained stagnant.

On the first day, he fell from around rank 30,000 to rank 33,000 on the Divine Seal Decree. Afterwards, he fell around 2000-3000 ranks every day. In just one month, he fell off the top 100,000 ranks of the Divine Sea Decree.

And the further he fell, the faster he fell. Currently, Lin Ming was ranked around 280,000.

As for the Divine Seal Decree, it only ranked the top 300,000 martial artists of the entire Divine Realm. In other words, Lin Ming would soon fall off the Divine Seal Decree!

In Good Fortune Great World, Lin Ming’s change in ranking naturally was noticed by the countless disciples and Elders of the Unbroken Cult.

“That Lin Ming, isn’t he Junior-apprentice Sister’s husband? How come his ranking is falling straight down?”

“Yeah, wasn’t he very fierce?”

“It seems that he’s going to fall off the Divine Seal Decree soon.”

After some time, many disciples of the Unbroken Cult couldn’t help but discuss this in low whispers. But then, a gruff voice rang out. “Lin Ming’s drop in ranking is only because he hasn’t moved for these last two months. Then again, if we ignore that reason and just look at his 280,000 ranking, he will still become a late Holy Lord character in the future. He is a martial artist that ascended from the lower realms and yet he was able to achieve such success. But as for all of you, you are all martial artists born in the Divine Realm, and have done nothing with your lives at all! So, before you speak of others, make sure you have the qualifications to do so!”

The Unbroken Cult’s Great Elder callously berated them. These disciples were immediately embarrassed by their own words.

The Great Elder fiercely swept his eyes over all the disciples. The reason he said this was because when Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan asked him to help search for Lin Ming’s name, Lin Ming still hadn’t been able to surpass 1000 merit points, and this continued for a long time. From this it could be seen that for some unknown reason, Lin Ming hadn’t done anything at all. For the second round of eliminations, this was likely the same possibility.

“This Lin Ming… he really is able to stay still. There is still another month left in the second round of eliminations… he should be able to rush back into the top 30,000.”

The Unbroken Cult Great Elder thought out loud. But in truth, even he wasn’t too sure of what would happen. Before this, during the first round of eliminations, he hadn’t noticed Lin Ming’s ranking rising at all. He had only seen his extraordinary final result.

But this time, he was carefully observing from start to finish.

Within the Unbroken Cult’s floating palace, Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan were also staring at the Divine Seal Decree.

Although the two of them had correctly guessed why Lin Ming’s ranking had dropped, seeing such a steep drop still made them feel nervous. Qin Xingxuan was especially restless. She feared that some accident might have happened to Lin Ming. It wasn’t because she was concerned about how strong Lin Ming was, but because if Lin Ming couldn’t obtain a stellar result on the Divine Seal Decree, then the Unbroken Cult might not escort them to see Lin Ming.

As Mu Qianyu saw Qin Xingxuan’s uneasy appearance, she said in a gentle voice, “Little Sister Xingxuan, don’t be so nervous. There is absolutely no need to worry about Lin Ming’s strength. Even if he runs into a stronger powerhouse during this tournament and is defeated, he’ll quickly catch up and achieve at least a similar result to the last time.”

“Mm… I understand.” Qin Xingxuan nodded.

And at this time, within the dreamland True Martial Great World, Immemorial Imperial City –

Lin Ming was sitting on a stone bed. Suddenly, his eyes flashed open. Seven-colored rainbow-hued lights appeared around him. He greedily absorbed them all like a whale swallowing water. Soon after, these energies entered his soul, carving the fourth divine dream mark into his being.

The four divine dream marks were all different. The first two divine dream marks were much brighter than the last two. As for the newest two, they were much more bleak and dim. It was clear that this was because they hadn’t been nourished with enough divine dream energy.

From the time that Lin Ming entered the divine dream space with his five months of cultivation, he discovered that he had obtained a tremendous benefit in the aspect of his soul. His cultivation also gradually rose, nearing the middle Divine Sea realm with every passing day.

As for his battle spirit, it also approached gold perfection. If his battle spirit reached the perfect gold level, then the next boundary would be a blue soul battle spirit. At that time, the power and intensity of his battle spirit would take a qualitative leap upwards.

Lin Ming closed his eyes briefly, thinking out loud to himself, “My soul force is over twice as strong than before I trained in the Divine Dream Law! This sort of increase is far too terrifying. Empyrean Divine Dream is truly a remarkable heaven-gifted genius. In the domain of the soul, she was actually able to establish her own method to temper the soul and allow true essence to fuse into it…”

Lin Ming sighed. His own soul, if compared to that of someone who hadn’t trained in the Divine Dream Law, was just like the difference between a martial artist’s body and the body of someone who only had brute physical strength. The difference between these two was clear.

When one’s soul was powerful, there were all sorts of benefits. For instance, one’s divine sense, alchemical ability, refining ability – all of this was related to one’s soul. In the future, he also wouldn’t encounter a bottleneck in his cultivation due to the insufficient strength of his soul.

Of course, the most direct advantage now was his increased soul force. Lin Ming could also sense an area over twice as large as what he could in the past.

Moreover, the clarity of his divine sense had also doubled!

This was especially true to his sensitivity to divine dream energy. As Lin Ming understood the Divine Dream Law more and more, his sensitivity to this miraculous energy was 10 times what it was before.

Now, as Lin Min closed his eyes, he could clearly feel all of the masses of divine dream energy lights in a scope of a hundred miles around him. These lights came in different colors and shades. Some were darker, some were brighter, some were smaller, and some were bigger. All of them represented varying concentrations of divine dream energy.

And these concentrations of energy formed in two situations: one was a participant, and one was a nightmare beast.

Lin Ming also discovered that the divine dream energy within nightmare beasts was different from that carried within participants. The divine dream energy within nightmare beasts was often single masses of light that came in one color.

As for the divine dream energy of the participants, that was much more mixed. After all, these participants killed a massive number of nightmare beasts and also gathered all of those different energies into their bodies.

“I should go out and start hunting now. I need to kill some participants or nightmare beasts so I can gather more dreamland energy to nourish my divine dream marks.”

Lin Ming thought. Then, he left his training chambers and moved toward Nightmare Canyon, a thousand miles away from Immemorial Imperial City.

However, along the way he discovered that there weren’t many masters at all. With his sense he was able to easily search a range of a hundred miles for dense gatherings of divine dream energy. Yet, in this extremely broad hunting zone, he wasn’t able to find any highly ranked masters at all.

If there were few martial artists then the nightmare beasts would evolve at an extremely slow rate. The nightmare beasts would have a correspondingly low merit point value.

“Where did all the masters go? Could they have gone to another city?” Lin Ming frowned. After the first round of eliminations, only 1% of the participants on True Martial Great World remained. For such a small number of participants, they could only gain more merit points by gathering together. It seemed that the martial artists of Immemorial Imperial City had migrated somewhere else.

Lin Ming captured the most powerful nearby martial artist to confirm his own guess.

“True Martial City… it seems that the masters of Immemorial Imperial City have all gone to True Martial City…”

Chapter 1202 – Cultivating Essence, Energy, And Divine

After Lin Ming listened to this dark-skinned youth’s words, he laughed, and in a very reckless manner.

As that rampant underling from before saw Lin Ming’s smiling face, he was horrified. Even so, he mustered up his courage and put on a brave face, saying, “Is it funny? What are you laughing about?” Then, he pointed at the symbol on his robes. “This is the True Martial symbol, it is something that is impossible to fake. In this dreamland space, everything is the same as in reality and you can even look it up yourself. As long as you pour your true essence into it, you’ll know that it is real!”

Lin Ming chuckled. “I’m laughing at all the idiotic nonsense you’re spouting. Do you think I don’t know you’re from the True Martial Holy Lands?”

“You…” The dark-skinned youth stiffened. He gloomily said, “The True Martial Holy Lands is the influence that is currently in control of True Martial City. If you kill a disciple of the True Martial Holy Lands, you will be the one killed in the future! Do you really think that you can face the entirety of the True Martial Holy Lands by yourself!? Our lives are not valuable at all. Even if we die, we won’t lose too many merit points. But you are different. Your merit points are enough to rank you in the top 50 masters of True Martial Great World!”

The dark-skinned youth bit out, the threat evident in his words.

“Face the entirety of the True Martial Holy Lands?” Lin Ming rubbed his chin. “If you didn’t say that, I wouldn’t have thought of this. But now that you mention it, that’s quite a good idea. I’m missing some merit points right now, so if you people are planning on delivering some snacks to me then go ahead, I’ll welcome all of you.”

“You!”

The dark-skinned youth’s complexion sank. He suddenly said, “You have no idea of death or danger!”

“Attack together!” The dark-skinned youth shouted. After stumbling into such a lunatic, he had no hopes of still living after this. The final counterattack of these three people was fierce, but in front of Lin Ming it was nothing at all.

The Phoenix Blood Spear swept out; all of their attacks were completely crushed!

“You will pay for this!”

The dark-skinned youth shouted. His saber cut towards Lin Ming’s throat, but the Phoenix Blood Spear was already a step ahead; it passed right through his heart.

Soon after, a blazing spear light flashed out and the other two people were cut apart, their blood splashing out into the skies!

“I will… remember… you…”

The dark-skinned youth glared at Lin Ming as his body fell down.

In just 10 short breaths of time, the six martial artists had been completely wiped out. Their bodies turned into pure dreamland energy that fused into Lin Ming’s body, where it was absorbed by the divine dream marks on his soul.

“Six people altogether gave me a total of a million merit points. Not bad.”

Lin Ming looked up his own merit points and saw that he had finally broken through 10 million. He guessed that these people were ranked around 200 at True Martial Great World. As for that dark-skinned youth, he contributed the most points to Lin Ming at around 500 thousand. The other five people contributed the other 500 thousand. Compared to the first round of eliminations, although these participants were in similar positions, the number of merit points had increased by far too much. Otherwise, if Lin Ming killed participants of this level, the rise in his merit points shouldn’t be so high.

“My divine dream marks are even more complete… but, these newest two divine dream marks have an even greater need for dreamland energy than the first two. It seems that every time I form another divine dream mark, I’ll need more and more dreamland energy… I wonder just what it will be like the further I cultivate them? I do not have Empyrean Divine Dream’s transcendent divine might and can only rely on the Magic Cube to help me perceive the method to this miraculous ability. Even if the Magic Cube is a heaven-defying tool, it still isn’t enough. It might be able to help me at the start, but the further I go, the less useful it will be.”

As Lin Ming understood the Divine Dream Law more and more, his admiration towards Empyrean Divine Dream increased by leaps and bounds. He simply had no idea how Empyrean Divine Dream had managed to create such a brilliant transcendent divine might.

Lin Ming gradually realized that the Divine Dream Law was not just its own independent system of Laws, but also something that could be an independent cultivation system!

Currently, Lin Ming trained in two types of cultivation systems. One was the body transformation system and one was the essence gathering system.

As he thought about it, body transformation trained the mortal body. In terms of essence, energy, and divine, this would be called flesh and blood ‘essence’. Body transformation was to refine the flesh and blood and temper one’s essence. Finally, one’s body would be similar to a God Beast, a being with incomparably powerful defensive power. With just a single step, one could sunder the earth.

As for the essence gathering system, that was to cultivate the dantian and to grow one’s inner world, constantly gathering energy within it. In essence, energy, and divine, this represented energy. Heaven and earth origin energy was this ‘energy’, and essence gathering was to cultivate a breathing technique that could gather the spiritual energy of the world, becoming more and more in tune with the power of nature.

But whether it was training the body or training one’s dantian, there was something that was impossible to cultivate: that was the divine soul.

Normally, a martial artist would increase their soul force by studying a few supporting skills, such as alchemy, refining, array formations, and so forth. The further one studied these skills, the more they could increase their soul force.

There were even some sects that developed a number of arcane skills that trained the divine soul. For instance, the Overbearing Soul Tactic that Lin Ming had first practiced a long time ago was one such technique. But this technique didn’t fuse true essence into the soul, it simply enhanced one’s soul force.

There was an overwhelming difference between the Overbearing Soul Tactic and the Divine Dream Law. For comparison, the Overbearing Soul Tactic could be considered the exercise techniques of a mortal. If they jogged every day, lifted weights, and trained their body, then after a long time their body would become stronger and they would naturally have an advantage in fights.

As for the Divine Dream Law, that was the true training of a sect’s martial artists. One could train, enhancing their cultivation and rising in boundaries and accomplish miraculous things. They could split apart oceans and shatter mountains. The difference between these two techniques could be imagined.

So, if one continued with this train of thought, then if one were able to cultivate the Divine Dream Law to perfection, one could learn a completely new cultivation system – the soul cultivation system!

Body transformation, essence gathering, divine refining, if one could practice all three of these systems, they could completely train in essence, energy, and divine!

If a martial artist could cultivate all three systems, what boundary would they be able to reach in the future?

As Lin Ming thought of this, his mind bubbled with anticipation.

To a martial artist, essence, energy, and divine were all indispensable. If one solely cultivated body transformation or essence gathering, then they would always have a weakness.

An essence gathering martial artist had a weak body. They had to constantly create shields of protective true essence around themselves. And once this protective true essence shattered, their mortal body would easily be torn apart.

For instance, if Lin Ming killed someone now, even if they were a Divine Sea master, if he were to rip out their heart or tear off their head, then they would die, no matter how strong they were.

But if one was solely a body transformation martial artist, then even if their body was powerful, they would be lacking in flexibility. Without the support of the essence gathering system, they would not be able to display their speed, striking power, or explosive force to the limit.

But even if a martial artist cultivated body and energy, there were still flaws.

For instance, Mo Eversnow. She was a rare heaven-gifted genius who would have become a Great World King character in the future. Even though she dual cultivated in body and energy, she still managed to reach a half-step World King cultivation at an extremely young age. She had even nearly stepped into the legendary Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. But even for someone as gifted as her, once her body disintegrated and her inner world was shattered, leaving nothing behind but her divine soul, she became extremely weak. Her combat strength had fallen to that of the weakest early Divine Lord martial artist. Moreover, if she used too much energy, her soul would suffer damage and she might fall into a deep slumber.

In the end, this was caused by the fragility of Mo Eversnow’s soul. If she had been able to cultivate her soul to an extremely high boundary and allow her soul to directly move energy, then she would never have ended up in such a state. Even if a Holy Lord level powerhouse faced Mo Eversnow’s remnant soul form, they would still be instantly killed!

If there could really be called a peak of martial arts in this world, then the person who could climb to that peak could be called a True Divinity, a being whose lifespan surpassed the sun and the moon and even the boundless universe. Such a person might be skilled in all three aspects of essence, energy, and soul, someone who reached the peak of all existence!

If one cultivated essence, energy, and divine to the limit, would there be a qualitative change?

As Lin Ming thought of this, he could only sigh with emotion. He hadn’t even managed to fully dual cultivate body and energy, and now he had to add another cultivation system – soul cultivation!

If he cultivated all three systems to perfection, then Lin Ming might become the most terrifying martial artist to ever exist since ancient times.

However, if he failed to fully cultivate all three systems to perfection then he would have wasted his energy and also his time.

Of course, there was no need for Lin Ming to consider what cultivation paths to take. With his character, he was destined to never let go of any opportunity that walked across his path. He would cultivate essence, energy, and divine.

Especially since Lin Ming possessed the heaven-defying cheat tool called the Magic Cube!

For an entire day, Lin Ming constantly cut down nightmare beasts in Demon Sealing Ridge as well as familiarized himself with the surrounding environment. With his powerful soul force supporting him as well as his current understandings of the Divine Dream Law, he was able to sense all powerful nightmare beasts and participants within 100-200 miles. None of them were able to escape Lin Ming’s sense. Lin Ming was able to sense them, but they weren’t able to sense him. This gave Lin Ming a tremendous superiority.

As Lin Ming hunted more and more, he continually gathered dreamland energy within his body, becoming more and more powerful.

And at the end of the day, the six True Martial Holy Land martial artists that were killed by Lin Ming finally revived…

In the deep dark, the dark-skinned youth’s eyes flashed open, hatred and anger shining in them. “Brat, you are dead!”

Chapter 1206 – Highdragon’s Death

In this battle, Highdragon – had died!

As for Lin Ming, from start to finish, besides some minor injuries on his right hand, he was completely uninjured.

As for those wounds on his right hand, those were completely avoidable. Even if he gave up the grandmist space and the Eight Inner Hidden Gates to suppress the Snake Blood Soft Sword, he still would have killed Highdragon; it was just that he didn’t choose to do so.

From the moment that Lin Ming attacked, he had used absolute strength to completely suppress Highdragon. Highdragon hadn’t even had the ability to display full use of his Laws.

The disparity was obvious!

The scene of Highdragon’s defeat fell into the eyes of the disciples from the True Martial Holy Lands standing not too far away.

They were in a stunned condition; they were finding this hard to believe.

Their Senior-apprentice Brother Highdragon had… died!

In a situation where Lin Ming’s cultivation was two small boundaries lower, he had still killed Highdragon. Moreover, he had been calm the entire time. The difference in their strength was unbelievable.

As those disciples saw blood raining down to the ground, all of them looked towards Lin Ming with fear and panic in their eyes.

“How is this possible!?”

“Just where is he from?”

“He surpassed two small boundaries to kill a Great World King Holy Land disciple. This is probably the level of an Empyrean descendant!”

These True Martial Holy Land disciples naturally didn’t understand the true strength of an Empyrean descendant, but they couldn’t think of a more monstrous kind of genius to describe Lin Ming as.

A random youth that they encountered in True Martial City’s Demon Sealing Ridge was actually a monstrous genius comparable to an Empyrean descendant?

This caused them to feel horrified in disbelief!

Lin Ming turned around, looking at these people. His eyes were calm and indifferent, like a person looking at a group of ants.

But this gaze actually caused those True Martial Holy Land disciples to shrink back, their hearts racing and their souls seeming to freeze solid. It was like Lin Ming’s gaze had substantialized into two sharp spear lights, directly piercing through them all and making it hard for them to breathe.

“Run!”

These True Martial Holy Land disciples suddenly seemed to wake from their daze. All of them scattered in all directions!

“None of you will escape. All of you will die!”

Lin Ming’s figure flashed and he immediately appeared in the area where the fleeing True Martial Holy Land disciples were. With just a wave of his Phoenix Blood Spear, countless tiny blood spears shot out in all directions.

These tiny blood spears were extremely fast. They rapidly overtook those fleeing disciples, and with a few light sounds, all of those people were struck through by those numerous tiny blood spears. All of them let out miserable cries as they died one after another!

In just three breaths of time, eight or nine disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands had died. All of them had been cleanly killed by Lin Ming with utter ease.

Of these people, the strongest was the dark-skinned youth. Even after being pierced through with seven or eight tiny blood spears, he still had a single breath of life remaining. However, he was already choking on his blood.

“Demon… simply a demon…”

The dark-skinned youth whispered. He only had a few breaths of time left in his life.

In just two and a half days, the dark-skinned youth had died to Lin Ming twice. He only had 16% of his original merit points left.

This was a serious loss!

“As you said… either you die or I die.”

Lin Ming indifferently said, his voice resounding in the dark-skinned youth’s ears. If that dark-skinned youth didn’t think that Lin Ming was easy to bully, and had simply realized he made a mistake after dying the first time and didn’t try to seek revenge, then he wouldn’t have died a second time.

Puff!

A tiny blood spear punctured the dark-skinned youth’s head. Blood gushed out from his forehead; he had died!

“They’re all dead… but, the merit points of these people aren’t anything at all.”

Lin Ming shook his head, not even bothering to refine their energy. Rather, he focused on the dead Highdragon. That was the true main event.

Underneath the power of the dreamland Laws, Highdragon’s body quickly turned into pure dreamland energy that slowly floated towards Lin Ming.

In Lin Ming’s field of vision, this multi-colored mass of light was the strongest and brightest group of energy he had seen ever since he joined the First Martial Meeting preliminaries!

If he could continue to absorb dreamland energy like this, Lin Ming would be able to fully bring his third and fourth divine dream marks to perfection.

“Those True Martial Holy Land disciples also said that Highdragon is a top 10 ranked master of the True Martial Great World. I wonder just how many merit points he’ll give me…”

Lin Ming stretched out his hand. This multi-colored energy slowly flowed into his body.

For a time, Lin Ming felt as if his entire body was filled with a deep awareness. The warm and gentle dreamland energy spread through his entire body before converging on his soul, nourishing it, expanding it, growing it.

Lin Ming felt as if he had returned to the time when he had first obtained the Magic Cube as a teenager. When he was 15-16 years old, that was when he first entered the world of martial arts. That feeling when he rapidly grew was just like this feeling now.

This was a truly wonderful feeling!

Lin Ming looked for a well-hidden valley without a single person present. He sat down and began to meditate, tempering his divine dream marks.

…………….

At this time – Good Fortune Great World, within the Unbroken Cult’s floating palace.

Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, and many Elders of the Unbroken Hall were seated in a grand hall.

There was a specialized Unbroken Cult disciple whose sole purpose was to keep track of Lin Ming’s merit points and ranking on the Divine Seal Decree.

In these past days, Lin Ming’s merit points ranking had been steadily rising. From 290,000, it slowly rose to 260,000.

According to this speed Lin Ming would soon re-enter the top 30,000 rankings before the second round of eliminations began.

As evening approached, the fading sunlight peeked through the massive rolling clouds in the sky. It illuminated the incomparably vast golden Divine Seal Scroll, making its golden light even more dazzling. That golden scroll that seemed as broad as golden mountains and rivers appeared incomparably grand.

And at this time, Lin Ming’s name suddenly changed on the Divine Seal Decree. It flashed several times before suddenly disappearing. This meant that Lin Ming’s ranking had changed and his position naturally changed with it.

“Young Hero Lin’s ranking has changed!”

Several Unbroken Cult disciples realized this and began to search for Lin Ming’s new ranking. In these past few days, Lin Ming’s ranking had jumped several times but it was usually only dozens or hundreds of rankings. Wanting to search for his new position was a very simple matter.

But this time, the several Unbroken Cult disciples swept their eyes over several thousand names yet couldn’t find Lin Ming.

“Great Elder, Young Hero Lin’s name has disappeared!” The several Unbroken Cult disciples reported to the Great Elder after not finding Lin Ming’s position.

“Mm?”

The Great Elder opened his eyes from meditation.

“We looked upwards several tens of thousands of names but we couldn’t find Young Hero Lin’s name. It couldn’t be that…”

The several disciples trailed off. If one’s name disappeared so suddenly like this, besides a sharp rise, there was also another possibility, and that was that they had been killed.

There was no limit in the universe. There was always a higher mountain and a stronger person. Within a great world of the Divine Realm, there were countless masters about. To the Unbroken Cult’s disciples, the True Martial Holy Lands’ Highdragon would be a legendary genius, but he had still been killed by Lin Ming. It wasn’t that Highdragon was weak but that his luck was bad, and he had simply kicked himself in the face by challenging Lin Ming.

The Great Elder thought for a moment, then ordered, “Search separately. Two of you search ahead and two of you search behind…”

Before the Great Elder finished speaking, he suddenly recalled that he had the divine dream jade slip. Because Lin Ming’s position had appeared on the Divine Seal Decree, there simply wasn’t any need to use the divine dream jade slip, thus he had forgotten about it for a moment.

“No need. I will search for him with the divine dream jade slip!”

As the Great Elder spoke, he took out the divine dream jade slip. Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan looked towards him. Qin Xingxuan appeared extremely nervous, and her heart was chaotically beating. She was afraid that Lin Ming had been killed by some master. After all, even if Lin Ming was extremely strong, he might have run into some overwhelming powerhouse.

Mu Qianyu took a deep breath. She silently kept her eyes on the Great Elder as he searched for Lin Ming.

Soon, Lin Ming’s name appeared above the jade slip.

Ancient Phoenix Clan – Lin Ming!

And behind Lin Ming’s name, his merit points were continually changing. Or rather, it was better to say that they were crazily growing!

The first number that appeared was already 21 million! And it began to increase by a million at a time!

In just a brief moment, it reached 28 million and then broke right through 30 million!

31 million…

33 million…

35 million…

As the Great Elder saw this insane growth, he sucked in a breath of cold air. This Lin Ming, just what sort of powerhouse had he killed!?

Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan also widened their eyes. Their eyes shined as they looked at the divine dream jade slip.

Lin Ming’s merit points easily broke through 40 million, quickly rising towards 50 million!

43 million…

44 million…

45 million…

Finally, Lin Ming’s merit points stopped at 46 million.

From 15.6 million to 46 million, that was a sudden rise of 30 million! This meant that Highdragon’s merit points had originally been around 50 million!

As for Lin Ming’s ranking, he was now ranked 15th of the True Martial Great World!

When the Unbroken Cult Great Elder had first seen Lin Ming’s ranking, that had been after the first round of eliminations when his ranking had stabilized. He wasn’t like Huo Violentstone, who had kept track of Lin Ming’s ranking the entire time. So in his opinion, wanting to increase his ranking so suddenly was extremely difficult.

For him to suddenly rise up to rank 15, that meant that Lin Ming had killed a top 10 ranked master of the True Martial Great World. For Lin Ming to be able to kill such a character, that meant that his strength was ranked at least sixth to seventh on a great world, and could be considered among the highest peak geniuses of a Great World King Holy Land!

To the Unbroken Cult, this sort of talent was simply a myth.

“Great Elder, we have found Young Hero Lin on the Divine Seal Decree. He is ranked 30,862!”

After learning Lin Ming’s ranking, it was easy to find his position. This was because the True Martial Great World was a very lively and bustling great world with many masters. If one was ranked 15th, then they would be ranked around 30,000 out of the entire Divine Realm.

“30,000… from 260,000, he suddenly rose to 30,000… I thought that it would take a month to do so…”

The Unbroken Cult Great Elder whispered. This meant that Lin Ming’s strength was far greater than what he originally thought. It was hard to imagine just what achievements Lin Ming would accomplish in the future.

Chapter 1209 – Strength Beyond Strength

Chi chi chi!

Lin Ming’s aura seemed to substantialize into essence, becoming as sharp as a spear edge and tearing through the air, thrusting towards Wu Finalcloud and grating against this protective true essence.

Wu Finalcloud remained indifferent. He calmly said, “What a wonderful aura! You indeed have some skills, but let’s see if you can withstand my aura!”

Wu Finalcloud shouted and his aura surged out like an endless ocean. This aura gathered together into a massive wave that hurtled into the horizon, washing away the clouds. All of the nearby participants were forced back again and again by this aura.

This was a truly powerful man, able to look down at the world with utter disdain!

“Haha! Elder Senior-apprentice Brother is too fierce!”

“Just by the power of his aura alone, Elder Senior-apprentice Brother is definitely the top powerhouse of the True Martial Great World. He even closes in on the power of an Empyrean descendant. If he sees a god he will kill a god. If he sees a Buddha he will kill a Buddha!”

“Who dared to say that Dragon Fang was fiercer than Elder Senior-apprentice Brother? If Elder Senior-apprentice Brother was to release his full strength, who could possibly stop him? Let alone this Lin Ming with his mere early Divine Sea cultivation! If he could truly defeat Elder Senior-apprentice Brother then his talent would be equal to that of an Empyrean descendant!”

Lin Ming was at the peak of the early Divine Sea. For him, the disparity between his cultivation and Wu Finalcloud’s wasn’t that significant. Lin Ming jumped ranks to fight masters like others ate meals and drank water. But, to a peak talent, the closer they reached to the limit, the greater an influencing factor their cultivation would become. If he were to jump two small boundaries to defeat someone as talented as Wu Finalcloud, then that would truly be unbelievable!

As Wu Finalcloud displayed his invincible grandeur, all of the surrounding True Martial Holy Land disciples stared with wide eyes. They closely looked at the battlefield lest they miss a single detail.

Kacha!

Wu Finalcloud stepped forth and the rocks beneath his feet cracked apart. This step seemed to step upon the hearts of everyone present, making their hearts skip a beat.

“Let me take a good look and see whether or not you have the ability to have me use my transcendent divine might!”

As Wu Finalcloud spoke these words, while the disciples from the True Marital Holy Lands weren’t surprised, all the other participants were all shocked.

Transcendent divine might!

These three words, to them, were absolutely legendary words!

“Wu Finalcloud actually knows a transcendent divine might?”

“Heavens, transcendent divine might! That is a top martial art created by an Empyrean!”

These disciples from ordinary Holy Lands and martial families were all shocked speechless, but their expressions were full of envy. A transcendent divine might was something that they couldn’t even look up to.

As for the disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands, a sense of pride rose within their hearts as they saw these people’s responses. Even if they didn’t qualify to learn a transcendent divine might, they were still proud that their own Holy Land could possess one.

The True Martial Holy Lands’ transcendent divine might was obtained by the True Martial World King during his youth when he adventured through the Divine Realm. In fact, the reason that a Great World King Holy Land could obtain a transcendent divine might was that their Great World King was far too strong. When these Great World Kings were in their youth, they could easily obtain a top three ranking if they joined a First Martial Meeting. Such a person had a monstrous destiny, so obtaining a transcendent divine might wasn’t too strange.

However, even if a Holy Land possessed a transcendent divine might, only the number one disciple of every generation would have the qualifications to study it at the True Martial Divine Palace. This was because there was only a single jade slip and it was also incomplete.

For a single jade slip, only a single person was allowed to perceive it. The True Martial Holy Lands had many people, and besides the current top geniuses there were also the high level figures that had to train in it. How could they ever allow an ordinary disciple to take a turn perceiving?

Moreover, because it was incomplete, if a young disciple wished to practice it then they would need the guidance of a top master. This was an even greater cost of learning. Besides a disciple like Wu Finalcloud, other disciples like Highdragon weren’t able to enjoy such treatment.

“Humph, our True Martial Holy Lands already had this transcendent divine might when our sect was founded. It isn’t anything strange at all if Senior-apprentice Brother Wu Finalcloud knows a transcendent divine might.”

A True Martial Holy Lands disciple said with a matter-of-course expression and tone. But in his heart, he was actually extremely satisfied.

“This is the legacy of a World King Holy Land. Although the True Martial Great World has Dual Polarity Palace, Sacred Martial Mansion, and many other World King Holy Lands, these other World King Holy Lands, whether it be in inheritances, qualifications, merits, wealth, number of geniuses – none of them are able to compare with our True Martial Holy Lands at all!”

As this True Martial Holy Lands disciple saw all of these geniuses from ordinary Holy Lands and martial families look at him, his heart was overjoyed. This was the same as a nobleman arriving in the countryside and seeing all the wealthy villagers looking at him with awe in their eyes. This would naturally form an inherent sense of superiority in their background.

They wouldn’t help but think, “These are nothing but beetles that haven’t seen the world.”

“You people can be considered as having broadened your horizons this time. For you to be able to experience someone who knows a transcendent divine might, you should be thanking that dumb brat Lin Ming. Otherwise, none of you would have the qualifications to see Senior-apprentice Brother Wu Finalcloud…”

A disciple though in his heart. But, he also wished that Lin Ming could last a bit longer, because he too hadn’t seen Wu Finalcloud use his transcendent divine might before.

At this time, within the center of the battlefield, Lin Ming was looking at Wu Finalcloud with indifference.

Transcendent divine might…

What was the True Martial Holy Lands’ transcendent divine might?

In the past, when Lin Ming had fought the Crimson Light Holy Lands’ Crimson Strifecloud, what Crimson Strifecloud practiced wasn’t a true transcendent divine might, but a cultivation method that the Crimson Light World King had perceived through a shattered jade slip. Ultimately, it could only be considered the Crimson Light World King’s self-created technique.

The self-created cultivation method of the Crimson Strife World King versus the original cultivation method of an Empyrean – the two were obviously incomparable.

From this, one could see an obvious disparity. Although Crimson the Light Holy Lands were also a Great World King Holy Land, they were clearly inferior to the True Martial Holy Lands.

At this time Wu Finalcloud finally attacked. His sword released a 10,000 foot beam of golden light. The vorpal sword energy cut through all barriers.

“Blade Light Illuminating the World!”

The sword slashed out and that 10,000 foot long beam of light split through the skies and sundered the earth. The sword energy tore through the ground, leaving a gaping hole in the world.

In the face of such an aggressive sword strike, Lin Ming remained calm. He opened the Heretical God Force and raised the Phoenix Blood Spear high above his head before bringing it crashing down. With an indomitable momentum, it crashed into the ground. With a loud explosive sound, a massive shockwave even greater than Wu Finalcloud’s spread outwards, rolling up into the heavens. Where it went, countless rocks shattered and bits of stone soared into the skies.

The spear light and sword light collided. For a time, all the sound between the heavens and the earth was swallowed up by this strike. The terrifying impact formed a monstrous shockwave that savagely erupted!

Countless boulders collapsed and even nearby mountains cracked. All of the surrounding martial artists cried out in alarm and pushed their protective true essence to the limit, retreating again and again. Some people were sent flying backwards and were vomiting mouthfuls of blood. Although these were all genius disciples that stood thousands of feet away to watch the fight, they were still wounded by the shockwaves.

From this the momentum of the two martial artists’ battle could be seen.

At this time, Lin Ming stepped forwards. His body turned into a vague blue blur. He opened all seven gates and his strength instantly rose to millions upon millions of jins. The current Lin Ming could be called a vicious beast in human form!

“Use your transcendent divine might!”

Celestial Tyrant Manual – Hundred Layered Waves!

Bang!

A supernatural strength that surpassed a hundred million jins erupted, completely pouring into the Phoenix Blood Spear. Such a focused explosive power was something that a sword could not block.

Wu Finalcloud’s pupils contracted. He could see that it was impossible for him to block Lin Ming’s spear strike so his body suddenly blurred.

As the highest top junior master of the True Martial Holy Lands, Wu Finalcloud was no ordinary man. While he had extremely high attainments in striking power, his movements were equally extraordinary. As his figure blurred, he split apart into 108 afterimages, all of them completely indiscernible from each other.

“What bold words. Who cares how strong your spear strike is? If it cannot touch the enemy then it is useless. My movement technique may not be a transcendent divine might but it is still a top movement technique that was created by the True Martial World King!”

Wu Finalcloud recklessly laughed. Although a spear was stronger than a sword, as long as his movement technique was formidable enough, he would be able to avoid it.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. His energy focused within his inner world. The Heretical God Force opened, the Heavenly Demon martial intent erupted!

Ho – !

As a blood red lotus bloomed in the world, a vast and boundless energy enveloped the entire region.

Grandmist space – open!

Wu Finalcloud’s movement technique was originally part of the Concept of Speed. However, underneath the shroud of the grandmist space, 107 of the 108 afterimages suddenly vanished, leaving only Wu Finalcloud’s true form. Even Wu Finalcloud felt his body being affected by the grandmist space. His strength dropped by a tremendous scale and he found it increasingly difficult to move true essence within his body.

What sort of force field was this!?

As Wu Finalcloud was stunned in surprise, Lin Ming had already rushed in front of him!

The Phoenix Blood Spear in his hand came crashing down!

Wu Finalcloud’s eyes widened. He slashed out with his sword, cutting down at Lin Ming.

Kacha!

Underneath the strength of 100 million jins, Wu Finalcloud’s sword light was easily torn apart. The Phoenix Blood Spear continued onwards, crashing onto Wu Finalcloud’s head!

Wu Finalcloud’s complexion changed. “True Martial Body Barrier Art!”

As Wu Finalcloud saw the Phoenix Blood Spear about to strike him, he shouted out loud and a thick golden barrier appeared around his body. This was the Metal Laws.

The True Martial Holy Lands included masters of countless mystic arts. Every disciple could find a Law and cultivation method that suited themselves the most.

Lin Ming disregarded this new development and continued smashing his spear downwards. As his spear struck the golden barrier, there was a loud crackling sound as myriad cracks appeared in the barrier before it completely broke open!

However, because of the slight delay offered by this golden barrier, Wu Finalcloud was able to bring back his spirit artifact sword and send out a second sword strike!

Kacha!

The brilliant sword light collided with the Phoenix Blood Spear. Wu Finalcloud was sent hurtling backwards as if he had been struck by a mountain.

This tremendous amount of strength had not been completely diverted. A great part of it passed into Wu Finalcloud’s body, causing the blood within to tumble.

Only after flying back several miles was he able to stop himself and stand tall.

In this single exchange, Wu Finalcloud had suffered a serious loss. He forcefully calmed the roiling blood within his body and glared at Lin Ming, his complexion ugly.

“You…” Wu Finalcloud was unable to believe just how terrifying the explosive force in Lin Ming’s attack had been. Was he really only at the early Divine Sea!?

“What force field is that!?!?”

Lin Ming didn’t answer. He only faintly said, “Use your transcendent divine might.”

Chapter 1210 – Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art

Seeing Wu Finalcloud sent hurtling backwards by Lin Ming’s spear strike, all of the disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands were left panic-stricken. The invincible Elder Senior-apprentice Brother in their minds had actually been struck back by Lin Ming?

How was that possible?

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother!”

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother is fine!” Some disciples cried out with concern thick in their voices.

“How could Elder Senior-apprentice Brother possibly have anything go wrong. Elder Senior-apprentice Brother simply didn’t use his complete strength just now; he didn’t even use his transcendent divine might.” A disciple that worshipped Wu Finalcloud said. Even if his idol wasn’t as strong as he thought, he still wouldn’t admit it, because recognizing this was the same as denying everything he knew. Moreover, Wu Finalcloud hadn’t even used his transcendent divine might yet.

The ordinary disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands didn’t understand Wu Finalcloud’s real strength, they had simply run wild with their imaginations. But, the several top ranked masters of the True Martial Holy Lands were absolutely clear as to what Wu Finalcloud’s trump cards were. Once Wu Finalcloud used all of his abilities, his combat strength would multiply from before and there wouldn’t be any comparison between that and his previous self.

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother has met a worthy match!”

“That Lin Ming is truly unfathomable. To think that even Elder Senior-apprentice Brother’s Cloud Dimming Blade isn’t enough. He will need to bring out his second sword – the Great Blood Sword.”

Wu Finalcloud had two swords!

“This brat, how could he possibly suppress Wu Finalcloud!?”

Zhong Wenshu muttered as he hid in the crowd, staring at Lin Ming with hatred in his eyes. He couldn’t accept the reality of what was happening before him.

Originally, Zhong Wenshu thought he would be able to see something good by coming here. He thought he would see Lin Ming be utterly suppressed and killed, but he never imagined that Lin Ming would be so brutal that he could even force back Wu Finalcloud with his spear!

“The battle hasn’t ended yet. Wu Finalcloud still has his transcendent divine might. It’s unknown just who the winner will be!” Sacred Yueping gloomily said. Although this battle had been one-sided so far, it wasn’t strange for the losing side in a battle to use some miraculous move and turn the tables on the aggressor. Moreover, Wu Finalcloud still hadn’t used his true transcendent divine might.

To a disciple of an ordinary World King Holy Land, a transcendent divine might was a completely unreachable cultivation method.

“Transcendent divine might…” Sacred Tianhao hesitated. He had a faint premonition in his heart that even if Wu Finalcloud were to use his transcendent divine might, his victory or defeat would still be an unknown.

He had always felt that Lin Ming was too mysterious, too powerful, a being that surpassed all common reasoning.

Facing Lin Ming, even if you thought you were stronger, he would still easily suppress you. You would never know just where the limits of his strength lay.

Sacred Tianhao found it unbelievable that such a youth was only at the early Divine Sea.

“Wu Finalcloud is finally going to use his transcendent divine might!”

“I wonder just what sort of cultivation method that transcendent divine might is! I really want to see!”

Many surrounding martial artists said, some even rubbing their eyes.

The truth was that these people simply didn’t know what level of existence a transcendent divine might was. They had never even seen one, much less understood it. It was impossible for them to distinguish whether or not a cultivation method was a transcendent divine might based on how strong it was. Let alone these juniors, even Holy Lords and World Kings might not be able to do so, because most transcendent divine mights were secret existences that no one knew of.

“Just who are you!?”

Wu Finalcloud’s eyes burned as he gazed at Lin Ming, his complexion incomparably ugly. He could not believe that a disciple from a mere peak Holy Land could actually achieve such a mind-boggling level of talent. Perhaps even an Empyrean descendant would not be his match at the early Divine Sea realm!

“Haven’t you already investigated me?” Lin Ming asked back.

“Humph!” Wu Finalcloud coldly coughed. “Your talent is indeed unimaginably high, but, what will decide the ultimate outcome of this victory is strength, absolute strength! You wanted to experience my transcendent divine might, right? Then… let me fulfill your wish!”

As Wu Finalcloud spoke, his aura became increasingly powerful. His joints exploded, his body began to grow, and an endless, boundless energy gushed forth from his inner world. Tiny scales began to form all over his body, making him look like a demon.

This transcendent divine might even had the ability to change Wu Finalcloud’s body.

“The energy within his body is strengthening.” Lin Ming narrowed his eyes. He could feel the energy within Wu Finalcloud climbing to ever higher peaks. Without a doubt, this transcendent divine might was one that enhanced his striking power.

Up until now, Lin Ming had learned two transcendent divine mights. The Heretical God Force was an arcane skill whose main role was to help in cultivation and also help in comprehending Laws. Lin Ming’s power of thunder and power of fire were endowed unto him by the Heretical God Force.

As for the grandmist space, that was an auxiliary transcendent divine might.

Up until now, Lin Ming had never seen a direct attack-type transcendent divine might.

“This transcendent divine might is called the Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art! It is a transcendent divine might that changes the body. Once one displays the Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art, they will be able to obtain the power of a fiend demon, and their body will turn into that of a demon. Their speed, striking power, defensive power, even their comprehension of Laws, everything will double. Although my Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art is incomplete, its might when displayed underneath my hand is unimaginable! Now meet my strike!”

Wu Finalcloud wildly laughed. He put the long sword away in his spatial ring and took out a heavy sword!

Wu Finalcloud had two swords – one light and one heavy. The light sword was called the Cloud Dimming Blade and was used in coordination with his extraordinary speed. It was to help in displaying Metal Laws, Wind Laws, and the Concept of Speed.

And this crimson heavy sword was called… the Great Blood Sword. It was the sword Wu Finalcloud used when he was at his highest level of strength.

“Mm? Two swords?”

Lin Ming was a bit surprised. Up until now, he had seen several martial artists who used two swords. For instance, the Seven Profound Valleys’ Jiang Baoyun used two swords.

Dual Polarity Palace’s Zhong Wenshu was the same. He used twin black and white swords in order to display his distinctive Yin Yang Laws. This was also the reason for Dual Polarity Palace’s name. Yin and Yang, representing extreme polar opposites.

A double sword type martial artist often didn’t use both swords together. Rather, each sword had its own unique uses. A long sword was fast, tricky, and could change myriad times, but its striking power was lacking. When facing a crazy and savage frontal attack like Lin Ming’s Hundred Layered Waves, the sword light of a long sword would be far weaker in comparison and it would be extremely difficult to block such heavy-handed attacks.

Thus, they would bring out a second sword.

Although the Great Blood Sword had the shape of a sword, it wasn’t used for stabbing or slashing. Rather, it was used to violently smash onto others.

This was another extreme of swordsmanship – the edgeless heavy sword!

Now, with Wu Finalcloud’s energy having increased by several times thanks to the Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art, his strength and striking power had risen to a ridiculous level. It was incomparable from the past!

“Hehe, let me give you a warning. This Great Blood Sword is forged from crimson blood metal and is 1.2 million jins heavy. When I am in the condition of the Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art, my Great Blood Sword can display its greatest strength!”

It was impossible for an essence gathering system martial artist to have the bodily strength of a body transformation system martial artist. But, if they poured enough true essence into their weapon, they could also similarly stimulate the movement of their weapon, no matter how heavy it was. The only disadvantage would be that they would lack the flexibility of a body transformation martial artist.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. “So you want to meet me in a head-on melee?”

“Let’s go!”

Wu Finalcloud roared and sprang upwards!

With such a massive counterweight, the rocks beneath his feet shattered into tiny fragments.

Bang!

Wu Finalcloud’s sword came smashing down. But at this time, Lin Ming’s entire body was boiling over with excitement. This sort of fulfilling and wild battle was what he wished for!

All seven of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates opened! The power of the supreme dragon bone completely erupted!

Hah – !

A deafening dragon roar filled the air, as if a True Dragon were awakening within Lin Ming’s body!

All of the martial artists present heard this resounding dragon roar. They felt the blood energy within their body restlessly moving, gushing, tumbling about, even affecting their heartbeats.

This strength was…!?

Everyone was left horrified. Within the body transformation technique, the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was the highest legend. Besides Empyrean Primordius, it was possible that no one had managed to step into that mystical boundary.

As for the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, although they weren’t considered to be a myth, the last two gates were still fabled existences. There was basically no one that had opened them, thus none of the martial artists present had seen it before.

After opening seven gates, Lin Ming’s pupils contracted. The muscles on his body popped up as he grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear, aimed it at Wu Finalcloud’s sword, and brought it crashing down!

Kacha!

The Great Blood Sword collided with the Phoenix Blood Spear. With these two people at the center, a massive nova of energy erupted outwards. Countless black rocks filled the air, completely shattering. A giant series of fissures cracked through the earth, spreading out like an infinite spiderweb!

In such a terrifying strike, even a top grade saint artifact would instantly break apart. But Lin Ming and Wu Finalcloud’s weapons were spirit artifacts and extremely high rank ones at that. Even after such an intense strike, they still weren’t damaged.

Ka ka ka!

The Phoenix Blood Spear curved into a crescent arc.

Lin Ming’s feet both sank underground. The rock beneath him broke apart again and again, nearly becoming dust!

“You!” Wu Finalcloud grasped his sword in both hands, his eyes colored with disbelief at the sight of Lin Ming. ”How could you be so strong? How is this possible!?”

Kacha!

Wu Finalcloud’s sword cut out once more!

Lin Ming swept out his spear once again!

Spear and sword crossed, the sound of metal grating on metal pierced through the world!

Clang! Clang! Clang!

The two collided again! This was a brutal melee, a fight to the death to see who was stronger, who was faster!

As the two fought, all of the surrounding land was blasted away to nothing as countless fragments of stone rained down from the heavens. Every collision was like the ringing of a divine bell, a ruinous sound that echoed between the heavens and earth. Each ringing of this divine bell seemed to knock on the hearts of everyone present, causing their blood to tumble and surge within them!

The martial artists with weaker cultivations all paled, finding it impossible to stay nearby. Even if they wanted to stay close, they had no choice but to withdraw again and again. Otherwise, if they stayed, their organs would shatter and blood would leak from their heads until they died!

This was because as the two people fought, there was a massive amount of energy contained within the sound waves. A weaker martial artist would be shaken until they exploded to death!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Mountains and rivers shook. The earth trembled as countless black boulders tumbled down from nearby mountains, as if an earthquake was passing all throughout True Martial City!

This battle scene was incredible, unimaginable!

No one ever thought that a showdown between two peak masters of the True Martial Great World would evolve into such a scene.

Normally, when essence gathering system martial artists fought, they would display gorgeous and beautiful martial skills as they exchanged more and more moves. It would never be like the fight between these two, the most barbaric and savage method of directly struggling with strength!

Chapter 1216 – Red-Furred Monster’s Evolution

Lin Ming’s eyes locked onto the red-furred monster. This red-furred monster was around 10 feet tall and the hairs all over its body were as sharp and shiny as steel needles. Its chest, neck, and back were completely covered with thick black scales. Its body was grandiose, its claws sharp and fierce, and there was a thin and long tail that extended from its back. This tail seemed to have joints in it just like an iron whip, and on the end of this tail there was a long spike. This spike shined with a cold light. Just a moment ago, this spike had pierced through the hearts of three martial artists.

At this time, Lin Ming saw the red-furred monster stretch out its claw and take a purple crystal from Dong Bishu’s tattered corpse. This crystal had something like a small red snake sealed within it. The tiny red snake fluttered about, twisting within the purple crystal just like a living creature.

As Lin Ming saw this purple crystal, his eyes grew even brighter. This was…

Lin Ming’s eyes shot open. Although this was the first time he had seen this crystal, he felt a very special connection to it… as if this crystal was a part of his soul.

Lin Ming released his senses and locked onto that crystal. In the sensor map of his mind, he could see all the surrounding dreamland energy turn into countless masses of colored light. The dreamland Laws were able to divide into seven-colored lines, and as for that purple crystal, its energy signature looked just like a little purple baby. It had clear facial features, smooth and soft skin, and looked extremely cute and lovable.

“This purple crystal seems to have a life of its own…”

Lin Ming immediately thought. With his current understanding into the dreamland Laws, he was able to see that there was something beyond extraordinary within this purple crystal.

He had a faint feeling that if he could obtain this purple crystal, it would be an immeasurable advantage to his cultivation of the Divine Dream Law.

And as Lin Ming was thinking this, that red-furred monster actually swallowed up the purple crystal at a speed that no one could respond to.

After the purple crystal entered the red-furred monster’s body, it completely melted down, fusing into its soul. The red-furred monster growled a comfortable roar and its body began to emit crackling sounds. The armored bone scales on its body grew thicker and stronger, its tail elongated, and its muscles bulged outwards. Afterwards, two meat sacks began to pop up from its back

The red-furred monster cried out, writhing as if it were withstanding a tremendous amount of pain. It gathered all of its strength and emitted a guttural roar. Then, those two meat sacks on its back burst apart in a shower of green goo, and from this green goo a pair of meat-covered bones shot out. The bones then spread apart, revealing a wide set of blood-red wings, just like the wings of a vampire bat.

This red-furred monster had actually formed wings. It was clear that the reason was that it had eaten that purple crystal, thus the red-furred monster had evolved!

As Lin Ming saw this, he gripped the Phoenix Blood Spear and began to circulate the true essence within him. That purple crystal definitely had an inestimable advantage to his cultivation of the Divine Dream Law, and that red-furred monster had eaten it.

The red-furred monster had some slight differences from ordinary nightmare beasts, but in the end it was merely a monster formed within the divine dream space. If he were to kill it, he could obtain its dreamland energy, and that purple crystal’s energy would also be contained within this dreamland energy.

Lin Ming narrowed his eyes. With his own sense and ability to feel the Divine Dream Law, he analyzed the dreamland energy and dreamland Laws within that red-furred monster. He could feel that this red-furred monster had swallowed more than one purple crystal. As the participants were slaughtering each other for merit points, this red-furred monster had silently and unknowingly collected purple crystals, swallowing each and every one it could find.

As Lin Ming thought of this, he felt it a bit incredible. What was this red-furred monster? Was it some creature made by Empyrean Divine Dream? How come he could feel that this red-furred monster seemed to have its own thoughts and will?

He was nearly about to attack, when at this moment there was a loud ringing explosion from the distance. A blazing gold light shot through the skies and a white-robed youth shot through the horizon like a fiery meteor.

This youth was not some nobody, but the number one disciple of the True Martial Holy Lands, Wu Finalcloud.

Woosh! Woosh!

Following close behind Wu Finalcloud were two core disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands. They were both top 10 ranked characters of the True Martial Holy Lands and their strength was in no way weaker than Highdragon’s.

As Wu Finalcloud saw this red-furred beast, a thick killing intent glinted in his eyes. “I’ve finally caught you! You damned monster! You killed my True Martial Holy Lands’ core disciple Wu Zhanfeng, and now you’ve even killed my Junior-apprentice Brother Dong Bishu! You’ve run wild and out of control for all this time, and now today I will have you pay the price for all that you’ve done! Killing you is also considered as cleansing evil from this True Martial Great World!”

Wu Finalcloud took out the Great Blood Sword from his spatial ring. He certainly knew just how terrifying this red-furred monster was. Facing this beast, Wu Finalcloud had no intentions of starting off slow; he immediately took out his greatest weapon from the start.

And at this moment, the red-furred monster let out a diabolical roar as it launched its thin and transparent blood-soaked wings and hurtled straight towards Wu Finalcloud!

This red-furred monster originally had a terrifying strength and horrifying degree of defensive power. And now after having swallowed that purple crystal, its speed had risen to the limit!

Too fast! So fast that no one was able to react!

Wu Finalcloud’s pupils shrank. He instantly began revolving his transcendent divine might – the Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art!

With his strength crazily rising by several times, Wu Finalcloud shouted out loud and smashed his Great Blood Sword at that red-furred monster!

Dang!

With a ringing explosion, Wu Finalcloud’s Great Blood Sword was caught single-handedly within the claw of that red-furred monster! The thick sword edge was caught in its claw, unmovable, just like it was stuck in divine iron.

Wu Finalcloud’s complexion changed. How could this thing be so strong!? In that strike just now, he felt a strong jolt of pain shoot up his arm and his hand nearly went numb with paralysis!

This monster’s strength was even higher than that of Lin Ming!

And as for speed, it was no worse than Dragon Fang.

What in the world was this red-furred monster? Was it a nightmare beast? How could Empyrean Divine Dream think of creating such a powerful nightmare beast? If even he couldn’t defeat it, how many people were able to kill it?

Nightmare beasts were originally formed for participants to kill so they could gather merit points. If there was a nightmare beast that no one could kill, and that would instead kill everyone on sight, then wouldn’t these preliminaries simply lose all significance?

All of these thoughts flashed through Wu Finalcloud’s mind. At this time, he felt himself being pushed backwards, constantly being forced to retreat as he nearly lost control of the Great Blood Sword.

And at this time, from behind Wu Finalcloud, the two core disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands jointly attacked the red-furred monster from both sides!

Of the two martial artists, one used a long sword and the other used a thick saber. As they saw Wu Finalcloud being pushed back, both of them responded with a counterattack.

“Be careful!”

Wu Finalcloud shouted out. But, it was too late. The red-furred monster roared and its tail slashed forth like a sentient whip!

Xiu!

A sharp sound filled the air, as if space was being torn apart.

“Attack together!”

“Cut apart its tail!”

These two people were not idiots; they could also feel how terrifying the red-furred monster was. With sword and saber, they cut down on this iron tail.

Ding!

The two weapons intersected with the hard tail. The two martial artists felt their hands go numb as they nearly lost control of the weapons in their hands. The frailer sword let out a keening cry, as if it would snap apart if the force was any greater.

As for that iron tail, not only was it not injured at all by the sword and saber, but because of its absurdly fast speed, the end of the tail flew past the two weapons and shot directly towards one of the disciples’ hearts.

That disciple’s pupils contracted. He stormed backwards, wanting to avoid this strike.

However, the speed of that tail was far too fast!

That disciple barely managed to avoid having his heart pierced through. That sharp thorn pierced through the disciple’s protective true essence like it was paper and then penetrated through his body, passing right through his shoulder!

The disciple stuffily coughed. Before he even had time to respond, there was another light sound as the tail retracted. That disciple’s entire left shoulder, included his collar bone and muscles, was all twisted off by that tail!

With half his body covered in blood, the disciple cried out in pain, his face turning bone white!

“Fourth Junior-apprentice Brother!”

A raging anger blew up in Wu Finalcloud’s heart. He shouted out loud as all the joints in his body emitted great exploding sounds. His body grew and his muscles popped outwards as he activated the Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art to the limit!

Peng!

Wu Finalcloud used all of his strength and forcefully pulled out his sword from the grip of the red-furred monster. Then, he cut down on its head!

“Sword Shattering the Universe!”

This was Wu Finalcloud’s strongest attack.

However, this red-furred monster didn’t seem to care at all. It thrust out its claws, one claw towards Wu Finalcloud’s heavy sword and the other claw reaching towards his throat!

As Wu Finalcloud saw the brutal and savage counterattack of the red-furred monster, his complexion became beastly. He put forth his full force and continued cutting down with his sword as before.

Clang!

The great sword smashed into the claw of the red-furred monster and a loud ringing sound filled the air, as if that great sword had struck a metal rock. The red-furred monsters scales were chopped to pieces by the force, but at this time, that red-furred monster’s other claw approached Wu Finalcloud!

This claw came swinging out!

It was no longer possible for Wu Finalcloud to retreat. At this time, a thick golden barrier suddenly appeared around him. This was the Metal Laws that Wu Finalcloud had comprehended – the True Martial Body Barrier Art.

When he fought with Lin Ming, he had used the brief instant when the shield shattered to barely defend against Lin Ming’s Hundred Layered Waves. And now, this attack coming at him was clearly stronger.

Kacha!

The red-furred monster’s claw bluntly crashed into the golden barrier. The incomparably solid golden barrier shook for an instant before it was immediately ripped apart by the red-furred monster!

Puff!

After this claw tore through the barrier, it ruthlessly slashed Wu Finalcloud’s left shoulder. Wu Finalcloud’s body shook as he was sent flying backwards. His left shoulder had nearly been torn off!

“How could this thing be so strong!?”

Wu Finalcloud’s lips trembled. His arm was hanging uselessly at his side, it was simply impossible to use any strength with it.

As for the martial artists around the White Crag Mountain Range, all of them sucked in a breath of cold air. Although Wu Finalcloud had lost to Lin Ming and it was rumored that his strength was inferior to Dragon Fang’s, he was still an undoubtedly strong top master. Even so, he had been defeated in just a few moves?

Just what was that red-furred monster?

Chapter 1218 – Fighting The Red-Furred Monster

In the skies, robed in blue clothes and grasping a red spear, Lin Ming stood straight and tall, like a heroic challenger!

And in front of him, the red-furred monster was curled up like a crouching tiger, waiting for the opportune moment to strike. Facing this red-furred creature, no matter who it was, they would feel a tremendous pressure.

The several core disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands had already retreated a good distance away. Even the other martial artists scattered all around the White Crag Mountain Range drew back dozens of miles more from the battlefield. There were very few people that believed Lin Ming had any hopes of winning. And once Lin Ming was defeated, regardless of whether he escaped afterwards or died in the conflict, everyone else remaining would be stuck in dire straits. It was possible that the remaining participants would be drawn into a deadly bloodbath. At that time, when they all scattered to escape, having a bit more distance between them and that red-furred monster would increase their chances.

And at this time, the red-furred monster moved. It launched its red and blood-covered bony wings and rushed towards Lin Ming. Its speed reached an incredible level. Without any special move at all, it merely stretched out its claws and grasped towards Lin Ming’s throat!

This was the first time that the red-furred monster had officially attacked Lin Ming; the time before had merely been a hastily summoned counterattack.

When the red-furred monster had fought Wu Finalcloud, it had also used this simple-looking strike to attack Wu Finalcloud in a state where he had released the Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art and also the Demon Body Mutilation technique. In the end, after using every skill available to him, Wu Finalcloud had been the one to be severely wounded.

This was a terrifying strike!

If Ln Ming could defend against this strike then he would just about meet the qualifications to struggle with this red-furred monster. If he didn’t then he would be instantly killed!

Everyone watched this with their eyes wide open.

As Lin Ming saw this red-furred monster hurtling towards him, his pupils shrank. Explosive popping noises sounded out from all the joints in his body as the power of the supreme dragon bone and phoenix blood began to surge forth. From behind Lin Ming, the phantoms of an Azure Dragon and golden phoenix appeared.

A deafening dragon roar accompanied with a melodious phoenix cry split through the skies, echoing to the ends of the world. Lin Ming’s arms tightened and he rapidly thrust out the Phoenix Blood Spear in his hands. In that instant, he had shot out his spear 100 times.

These 100 spears gathered together, merging into a 10 foot thick azure spear light that shot towards the red-furred monster!

In this strike, Lin Ming had used the limit of his bodily strength. It could be called the strongest attack of his body transformation technique!

Bang!

Stormy shockwaves shook the world. Lin Ming’s spear crashed into the red-furred monster’s claws, causing energy to erupt and space to tremble.

The scales on the red-furred monster’s claws broke apart, but at the same time, that powerful vibrating force also passed into Lin Ming’s body through the Phoenix Blood Spear.

This vibrating force was like a titanic earthquake, vast and seemingly endless. Lin Ming’s protective true essence was swept over by these waves of power, instantly bursting apart!

The power of vibration subsequently broke into his body, passing into all the meridians, organs, and bones within him. In that moment, his blood tumbled and the energy within him became chaotic. There were even some meridians, muscles, and tendons that were damaged, nearly snapping apart!

If it weren’t for the fact that there was the supreme dragon bone fused into Lin Ming’s body and also that he had opened the Gate of View, this strike alone would have burst apart his organs and shattered all the bones in his body. His fate wouldn’t have been much better than Wu Finalcloud’s.

“What a formidable vibrating power. Is this… the Earth Laws? No wonder this red-furred monster defeated Wu Finalcloud even in his strongest state!”

Lin Ming’s eyes began to shine with a quiet and earnest light. The reason that this red-furred monster was so powerful was that every single one of its strikes was supported by the power of Laws. That crazy and brutal power of vibration would spread into the bodies of its opponents.

Lin Ming’s protective true essence was considered deep and formidable. Even so, in the face of this red-furred monster, his protective true essence had still instantly shattered without any chance of resisting it!

Fortunately, Lin Ming’s bodily defense was extremely formidable. Even so, he had still been damaged in this attack.

“He withstood it… Lin Ming actually withstood the attack of the red-furred monster! Heavens! His protective true essence shattered and yet he was still able to withstand it? Was it by relying on his bodily defensive power? He’s a monster himself!”

“It’s impossible to completely block it. If his protective true essence shattered then the shockwaves of that attack would definitely have rushed into Lin Ming’s body. Even if he cultivates the body transformation technique and his mortal body’s defensive power is formidable because of that, that attack must have injured him and left behind hidden wounds. If those hidden wounds accumulate then it will put his life in danger. Look at his arm! It’s bleeding!”

Lin Ming’s arm was indeed bleeding. When he withstood that tremendous impact force just now, his web of his palm had split apart and even some small blood vessels in his arm had ruptured, causing blood to flow down Lin Ming’s hand. As this blood dripped onto the Phoenix Blood Spear, it was incomparably bright red.

“It’s not as simple as you think. Look at that red-furred monster. Both of its arms have also burst open with blood.” Someone said with a true essence sound transmission.

“Don’t compare people with that monster. How could a human’s body possibly compare with the physique of that monster? Even if Lin Ming is a monstrous genius, I have a feeling that the monster’s regenerative ability and tenacity far surpass anyone’s imaginations. As for Lin Ming, if he continues to fight then those hidden wounds will continue to gather until he is finally defeated.”

As the martial artist just finished speaking, that red-furred monster seemed to deliberately confirm his words. The muscles of the red-furred monster twisted around, wriggling about until the flowing blood stopped and even its scales seemed to slowly regrow and repair themselves.

After colliding with Wu Finalcloud and Lin Ming several times and being wounded, that red-furred monster’s arms regenerated in several breaths of time!

As the participants all around the White Crag Mountain Range saw this, they sucked in a breath of cold air.

It had taken a great deal of effort to slightly injure it. This was particularly true for Wu Finalcloud. He had even desperately staked his life in order to injure that red-furred monster, but just now, it had nearly completely regenerated!

This sort of phenomenon would definitely instantly rout the confidence of any martial artist that hoped to defeat it.

With such an abnormal regenerative ability, just how could a human hope to fight against such a monster?

No matter who it was, in front of a being with such terrifying speed and strength, nearly invincible defensive power, ridiculous endurance and incredible recovery abilities, this sort of opponent left one wallowing in abject despair!

“It’s over. No one can hope to win against that!”

“I fear that even if Lin Ming and Dragon Fang joined together they still wouldn’t be able to do it!”

“Its recovery ability is too monstrous. It is like a child God Beast!”

As people were speaking, Lin Ming’s arm slowly began to stop bleeding. His flesh and blood moved, stitching themselves together as his wounds healed. His shattered skin and muscles also seemed to be reborn anew. A moment later, Lin Ming’s arm was completely healed to its original state. Even his broken meridians and blood vessels were slowly regenerating; all of his hidden wounds had been eliminated!

As everyone saw Lin Ming regenerate, all of their eyes popped open, their gazes filled with incredible disbelief.

“No way! Can Lin Ming also regenerate!?”

“I’m certain that he hasn’t taken a pill. And even if he did, there are far too few pills that have such a powerful regenerative effect that can be taken in the heat of battle!”

“How can a human’s body have the same restorative ability that a vicious beast has? Is this the Life Laws?”

Some people suddenly thought. If one practiced the Life Laws to a high boundary they could truly control the replication of their cells to a certain degree. They could even completely repair some non-vital organs; that is, everything besides the heart, brain, and spinal cord. Moreover, regenerating all of this came at the cost of a massive amount of true essence – it couldn’t be used too often.

“If this is the Life Laws then it is still useless. Lin Ming will soon exhaust all of his energy.”

“A person simply cannot compare to a vicious beast in endurance, especially since Lin Ming encountered such a freakish beast!”

The red-furred monster’s great strength had struck a chord of fear within all the martial artists present. Just by looking at it, they could feel their aura diminish.

At this time, the red-furred monster’s ghostly green eyes were blazing as it stared at Lin Ming. It hadn’t imagined that its own full-powered attack would be withstood by Lin Ming, and then Lin Ming would also be able to follow it in regenerating its body.

It issued a deep growl and slowly twisted its claws and neck, creaking its bones. Lin Ming also cracked his knuckles and hands together. Facing the red-furred monster, his eyes were sharp and fierce.

Rahh!

With a loud roar, the red-furred monster launched itself forwards once more!

This was a battle of savage head-on collisions! The red spear and red claws smashed into each other. Each time they struck, there was a loud thunderous pulse that split the air!

Bang! Bang! Bang!

The attacks all had a force behind them that surpassed 100 million jins of strength. Mountain shelves cracked, causing clouds of crushed stone to billow into the air. Just the shockwaves of this battle between man and beast were able to level this mountain range!

The red-furred monster’s formidable strength had exceeded Lin Ming’s expectations. In every attack, a powerful vibrating strength would spread into his body. His protective true essence shattered every time!

These powerful attacks were several times stronger than Wu Finalcloud’s final attack! If it were anyone else, they would have instantly died in the face of such a barrage.

Luckily, Lin Ming had dragon marrow and phoenix blood fused into his body, thus his regenerative ability and defensive strength had reached an unbelievable degree. Even so, in the face of such a brutally ruthless melee, he felt all the blood tumble within his body and energy wildly rush through his meridians, nearly causing them to break.

However, as Lin Ming withstood these extreme attacks each and every time, the red-furred monster wasn’t much better off.

The red-furred monster’s strength and explosive force were several times greater than Wu Finalcloud’s, but it had a serious weakness in its inferior combat skills. Every time it collided with Lin Ming, it had to resist at least two of Lin Ming’s attacks.

The Phoenix Blood Spear was an extremely high ranked spirit artifact, and its sharpness was without doubt. After Lin Ming poured his gold battle spirit into it, even if the red-furred monster had a body as hard as divine iron, the Phoenix Blood Spear would still leave trails of blood etched into its body.

As these trails of blood accumulated again and again, they gathered into a heavy wound.

The red-furred monster’s muscles wriggled, repairing all of these wounds. The phoenix blood and dragon marrow within Lin Ming raced through him, also repairing all of his wounds.

This was a battle of attrition, a match between their endurance and their restorative abilities!

This violent fight continued for several dozen breaths of time. Man and beast had collided over a hundred times already!

Every collision was like two planets bumping into each other. Each strike caused the mountains to shake, the rivers to vibrate, and the earth itself to tremble. Every explosive sound echoed in the hearts of the numerous martial artists scattered throughout the White Crag Mountain Range, like a steel ball smashing into their chests, causing their blood to restlessly move and even their heartbeats to be affected.

In such an intense fight, Lin Ming didn’t slowly exhaust his true essence and weaken as everyone had imagined he would. Rather, from beginning until now, he didn’t reveal any signs of burning out at all. He still remained incomparably aggressive and ruthless as before, like a vicious beast in human form.

All of the participants around the White Crag Mountain Range were stunned. Heavens! This was an absurdly terrifying endurance!

In his battle against Wu Finalcloud, although Lin Ming had also revealed his great strength, that battle contrasted to this one could only be considered a slap fight between babies. Only this homicidal collision between Lin Ming and the red-furred monster could truly be called a blood on blood melee! Every single time they crashed into each other they would both undoubtedly be injured! Not only did they have to withstand a huge consumption of energy, they also had to stimulate the energy within their bodies to restore themselves. To continue this fight to this point, the amount of energy they used was unimaginable!

Chapter 1219 – Thunder Tribulation

“That’s crazy… Lin Ming’s body actually isn’t any worse than the red-furred monster’s!”

“They must have struck each other at least 120 times by now. Lin Ming’s body has to withstand the tremendous impact of the energy shockwaves every time which will inevitably injure him, yet he’s able to recover after every strike. Is he even human?”

The participants scattered around the White Crag Mountain Range were all left speechless as they stared at this fierce battle taking place in the skies.

As for the True Martial Holy Lands, Wu Finalcloud had taken some medicine and had restored some of his origin energy. He also looked at Lin Ming battling in the sky, a strange color on his face.

It was clear that when he had used the Heavenly Demon Metamorphic Art to battle Lin Ming, it was simply a useless and suicidal action on his part.

When he fought with Lin Ming, even if the peak of his strength had lasted 10 times longer he would still have lost. The difference between them was that great!

As everyone was discussing this, Lin Ming had already exchanged 200 attacks with the red-furred monster. The red-furred monster’s two claws were covered with blood, the flesh on its chest had cracked, its scales had been torn off, and blood was leaking from its mouth. Even so, its body was constantly regenerating, but, the rate at which it was regenerating was slowing down at a visible rate.

As it looked at Lin Ming, its ghostly green eyes were shining with an inexplicable light.

In contrast, Lin Ming had consumed a great deal of energy too. But, this was a form of combat that he favored. This strong vibrating power, this feeling of true pain seeping through his body, this truly made his blood seethe with excitement.

Lin Ming wiped away the bloodstains from the corners of his lips, a cheery smile on his face. “You seem to have an intelligence of your own; you’re different from those other ordinary nightmare beasts. Can you understand my words?”

Lin Ming said with a true essence sound transmission. As he did, a strange look passed over the red-furred monster’s face.

“It seems that you understand me… then tell me, what is that purple crystal?”

Lin Ming had extremely little understanding into the mysteries of the divine dream space; he wanted to obtain more information about this world.

At this time, the red-furred monster released a deep roar and launched its bony wings once more. Its blood vitality suddenly rocketed up into the skies, billowing upwards like a volcano. With the support of this powerful blood vitality, its body began rapidly regenerating once again!

As everyone thought that the red-furred monster was about to attack again, an unexpected change occurred. The red-furred monster swiveled around and flew off in the other direction!

It was extremely fast. In the blink of an eye it swiftly flew dozens of miles away, nearly seeming as if it were teleporting. The speed of its flight caused a sharp grating sound to fill the air.

“What!?”

The martial artists around the White Crag Mountain Range were all shocked.

“Lin Ming forced away that monster!”

“This… this is… this is too fierce! That monster was actually forced back!”

“This Lin Ming is even more monstrous than that monster!”

Everyone was so shocked that they didn’t know what expression to make. This was the first time they had seen that nightmare beast running away.

As everyone thought that the battle had ended like this, Lin Ming’s figure flashed. He turned into a beam of light and chased right after the nightmare beast!

With the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and the Mystic Lightning Shade rapidly revolving and also with the speed from the Gate of Wonder, Lin Ming’s speed had reached an unbelievable level. He was even a bit faster than that red-furred monster!

Lin Ming’s figure turned into a series of afterimages as he vanished into the horizon.

“He’s chasing it! He’s really chasing it!”

Everyone was bewildered to see both man and monster rush away with incredible speed.

Lin Ming had forced back that nightmare beast and had even decided to pursue it! This was far too fierce!

“A desperate enemy shouldn’t be pushed too far. Moreover, that nightmare beast didn’t seem much weaker than Lin Ming to begin with. If he rashly chases it, I fear that he will encounter danger instead.”

“The beast tide is everywhere now. As long as that red-furred monster hides itself in the swelling beast tide, then Lin Ming can only be forced to give up. On the other hand, if Lin Ming isn’t careful and he’s sucked into the beast tide instead and forced to face off against hundreds and thousands of mutated nightmare beasts, he will certainly perish.”

“That’s right. Defeating and killing are two completely different concepts. That red-furred monster is just too fast. If it decides to escape then it’s impossible to cut it down. The only method is if someone’s strength far surpasses it, otherwise chasing it is far too audacious an action.”

In everyone’s view, Lin Ming’s endurance and formidable strength were without question. And just now when Lin Ming and that red-furred monster had flown away, that red-furred monster hadn’t fallen into a great disadvantage and didn’t seem much weaker than Lin Ming. Perhaps it only escaped because it feared that it would consume too much of its energy and then be open to sneak attacks from the surrounding masters.

In this sort of situation, no one thought that there was any meaning to Lin Ming chasing after it. Instead, chasing that monster might cause Lin Ming to wind up dead in the midst of the beast tide.

And at this time, Lin Ming had already chased that red-furred beast for several hundreds of miles.

Lin Ming frowned. If those participants could think of such scenarios, then he could too. He knew that chasing this red-furred monster was extremely dangerous.

But there were far too many secrets on that red-furred monster, even ones that were related to his cultivation of the Divine Dream Law. He had no choice but to chase after it.

What Lin Ming feared the most was that the red-furred monster would submerge itself into the all-encompassing tide of nightmare beasts. If that were to happen then he would have no choice but to give up his chase.

However, what happened surprised Lin Ming. The central beast tide was located at True Martial City still and this red-furred monster was flying in a direction that clearly wasn’t towards True Martial City.

“How strange… this monster has an intelligence of its own so why isn’t it luring me to True Martial City instead? If that happened then it would be in an invincible situation. Could it be that there is an even more dangerous area that it wants to bring me to?”

Lin Ming grit his teeth as this thought flashed through his mind. He revolved his energy and accelerated his speed.

With his speed, travelling a hundred miles only took several breaths of time!

And this speed was actually only a bit faster than the red-furred monster. If he wanted to overtake the red-furred monster he would have to chase after it for some time. During this time, they could have flown back and forth to True Martial City several times.

“How troublesome!”

Lin Ming didn’t worry that the red-furred monster was leading him to some special danger zone because he had his own methods of saving his life. Taking a step back, even if he died it wouldn’t really matter. In this divine dream space, true and final death did not exist. And as for his ranking dropping, Lin Ming didn’t care about trivial things like that.

The special energy within this red-furred monster was what Lin Ming valued the most.

The chase continued for some time. Before long, both man and monster had flown 8000-9000 miles. Their speed was so fast that the ordinary nightmare beasts they encountered along the way were unable to react at all.

They even had to pass through a small group of nightmare beasts.

And at this time, a change occurred. As the red-furred monster passed through this small group of nightmare beasts, a purple iron-winged dragon suddenly hurtled towards the red-furred monster!

It was impossible for an ordinary nightmare beast to follow the red-furred monster’s speed. But, this iron-winged dragon was a mutated nightmare beast and also one that excelled in speed. It wasn’t a problem at all for it to chase after the red-furred monster.

“Mm?” Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. The nightmare beasts would actually attack the red-furred monster?

No wonder! This red-furred monster wasn’t a nightmare beast to begin with, so it wasn’t strange that it was being attacked. This was also why it didn’t choose to escape towards True Martial City.

Then, just what was this red-furred monster?

These thoughts instantly raced through Lin Ming’s mind. At that moment, the red-furred monster roared like a rolling cloud of thunder. It reached out its claws and tore off the head of that iron-winged dragon!

This mutated iron-winged dragon was equal to a top 40-50 ranked master of a great world. But in front of this red-furred monster, it was slaughtered like a chicken.

However, killing the iron-winged dragon caused the red-furred monster a moment of delay. During this brief moment, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a severe light. “This is my opportunity!”

Lin Ming revolved his energy to the limit. As he rapidly consumed his energy he instantly erupted with his strongest level of strength. In a single breath of time he rushed to just a mile behind that red-furred monster. To him, a mile away wasn’t anything at all!

“I only have one move left. Although it’s not fully complete yet, there’s nothing else stronger!”

At this time, Lin Ming had no more intentions of holding back. In the previous battle, because he wanted to fight with his body transformation technique in order to feel the thrill of a melee battle in his bones, and also because he didn’t want to reveal his cards too early, he didn’t use this move in front of everyone. But now was different. If he missed this chance he might not get another one. If so, he naturally had to use all of his techniques to their fullest.

“Heavenly Demon martial intent – grandmist space!”

The Prime Emperor Lotus Flower slowly bloomed from behind Lin Ming. The grandmist space instantly covered the red-furred monster. Underneath the grandmist space that suppressed all Laws, the red-furred monster’s speed suddenly dropped. And taking advantage of this chance, Lin Ming rushed right towards the back of that red-furred monster!

In this instant, the power within Lin Ming’s body rapidly ascended. The blood of the Ancient Phoenix, the Heretical God Force, all of this power came surging outwards without end. All of this power, after converging with Lin Ming’s inner world, fused into the Phoenix Blood Spear and then erupted outwards!

Chi chi chi!

Endless bolts of thunder suddenly appeared in the skies, rushing to gather onto Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear. His spear light cut through space, emitting a terrifying sharp whistling sound. All of the thunder was swept up in Lin Ming’s spear strike, forming a massive purple vortex that spanned between the heavens and the earth.

It was like the world itself was about to break apart!

Heavenly Dao Judgment – heavenly thunder tribulation!

Lin Ming roared out loud. From within Lin Ming’s inner world, the power of thunder tribulation that had been absorbed by the Heretical God Seedling from his nine by nine Ninefall suddenly exploded outwards.

The power of thunder tribulation that stood above the Heavenly Dao Laws cut straight towards the red-furred monster!

This was also Lin Ming’s self-created elementary transcendent divine might!

Chi-la!

The Phoenix Blood Spear cut across the sky with endless arcs of thunder spinning around it. Space trembled, and the entirety of the surrounding skies for hundreds or even a thousand miles turned into a roiling purple thunder dominion!

From that small group of nightmare beasts, half of the nightmare beasts were caught up in this strike, instantly turning to ash!

The red-furred monster cried out in pain and agony. Placed within the grandmist space, its speed had dropped a lot from before. Lin Ming’s spear was now equal to heavenly tribulation. Underneath the absolute suppression of Laws, no one was able to avoid heavenly tribulation; they could only resist it!

Roar!

The red-furred monster roared in suffering. It stretched out its claws and grasped down at that thunder spear light!

Bang!

A blazing divine might lit up the heavens and a blinding light filled the world, seeming to swallow up everything in existence. For the surrounding hundreds of miles, all of the mountains and rivers and valleys completely collapsed due to the terrifying strength of this strike. Everything was razed to the ground. Lakes instantly evaporated and countless towering great trees were burnt to cinders.

The red-furred monster’s two arms were also charred black by this terrifying strength before instantly blowing into pieces.

Lin Ming’s long spear continued unabated, stabbing into the red-furred monster’s chest!

Puff!

The Phoenix Blood Spear penetrated right through the red-furred monster and emerged from its back. Blood shot out before being instantly evaporated by the turbulent energy shockwaves. Its fur, its scales, everything was completely scorched black by the power of thunder tribulation!

A thick and terrifying purple pillar of light shot into the skies!

Chapter 1220 – Eyes Blinded by Lightning

A terrifying explosion swept through the skies for several hundreds of miles. The violet shockwaves sundered the earth, shattering all barriers. In that moment, it was like a purple sun had dropped onto the earth!

Even from 10,000 miles away, this divine light was clearly visible!

“Awoooo!”

The red-furred monster roared out in pain. A massive half-foot-sized hole had been burnt through its body. Half its heart had been scorched and nearly all the blood in its body had been burnt away!

It furiously stretched out its claws, wanting to use its dying breath to grasp at Lin Ming’s head!

Lin Ming sneered. The Phoenix Blood Spear in his hand was pulled out!

Puff!

The scorched half of the red-furred monster’s body was ripped off; bits of flesh and blood rained out!

However, the life force of this monster had reached a nearly unimaginable level. It dragged its grievously wounded body and threw itself towards Lin Ming.

Without any expression, Lin Ming thrust out his spear again. The violent and wild power of thunder pierced into the red-furred monster’s head.

With a stab and a thrust, the red-furred monster’s head exploded like a watermelon. Its strong and sturdy body twitched for several moments, then, it finally died!

“I’ve killed it at last.”

Lin Ming let out a long breath. And at this time, because of that strike just now, the skies above him were covered by thick rolling thunder clouds. These thunder clouds gathered together into a massive vortex with waves of purple thunder glittering everywhere. With this strike, he had actually recreated a temporary thunder dominion. From the far off distance, one could make out the endless purple light sizzling within this thunder dominion.

And at the White Crag Mountain Range, many of the participants hadn’t yet left; they were busy planning their future paths after having lost the safety of True Martial City.

And at this moment, in the distant horizon they could see a massive purple pillar of light shoot into the skies!

“Look over there! What is that!?”

It wasn’t known just who shouted that, but everyone turned to look. They could see that in the distant skies, the world had turned purple. Countless arcs of lightning fell like torrents onto the world!

“Is this divine light borne from thunder?”

“That is definitely the Thunder Laws. Even from so far I can sense its immense strength. Heavens, I wonder just who is fighting?”

Watching from the White Crag Mountain Range, this pillar of light was narrow. But, the impact it caused was unimaginable. Because of this purple pillar of light, dark clouds shrouded the skies, blanketing the lands for hundreds and hundreds of miles. All of the martial artists could feel the terrifying energy contained within these clouds. Even from 10,000 miles away, this feeling still caused their minds to shake with fear!

“That direction… isn’t that the direction that Lin Ming and the red-furred monster flew in?”

“Yes, that’s it, that’s the direction! Could it be that it is Lin Ming fighting the red-furred monster?”

“Heavens! Just what sort of ability, what sort of fighting method is this? Is it Lin Ming’s attack or that red-furred monster’s attack?”

Someone shouted in panic, a sense of awe and dread in their voice. Everyone looked at each other, bewildered, disbelief written all over their faces. This strength was simply far too terrifying!

At this time, a top 20 great world ranked core disciple of the True Martial Holy Lands hesitated for a moment before saying, “It shouldn’t be…”

“If that red-furred monster had such strength then it wouldn’t have needed to flee. As for Lin Ming, I feel that his strongest aspect lies in his body transformation technique. In terms of the essence gathering system and his comprehension and use of Laws, he’s a bit lacking. The two of them shouldn’t be able to send out such an attack.”

“Then who could it possibly be? Is there an even more powerful existence on the True Martial Great World? Is it a super monster even greater than the red-furred monster, something like a sovereign of nightmare beasts?”

Someone whimsically asked, lost in his own daydreams. In the Divine Dream World, if a variation monster like this red-furred monster could be born, then it wouldn’t be strange if a nightmare beast sovereign could appear too.

If there really was such a monster, then Lin Ming would truly be in dire straits!

“There’s a possibility… if so, I fear that Lin Ming would have already died by now. Don’t push a cornered enemy too far; the sayings of the ancients aren’t wrong. Lin Ming was too reckless.”

“It’s just that the beast tide was too fierce right after the third round of eliminations started, otherwise something like this wouldn’t have happened to Lin Ming. But, even if Lin Ming was foolish this time, with his strength he will still be able to jump back into the top three ranks of this great world.”

Everyone shared their speculations. However, no one dared to go 10,000 miles to take a look at the real situation.

With their strength, let alone that red-furred monster or that possible nightmare beast sovereign, if they were to encounter a small group of nightmare beasts then they would be completely swallowed up as food until there weren’t even bones left of them!

“If a nightmare beast sovereign has truly appeared, then our chances of survival have gotten even worse. To confirm this, could our top 10 ranked senior-apprentice brothers look and see if their rankings have changed?”

A True Martial Holy Lands disciple suddenly said.

It was easy for them to discern the rankings of the top 10 on the True Martial Great World because they occupied most of the positions. They would only need to verify their own rankings to find out.

Lin Ming was originally ranked fourth on the True Martial Great World. If he were killed, he should fall to or around the tenth place. The fifth to tenth place martial artists could see if he fell by checking if their own rankings had jumped by one.

When the beast tide first erupted, the core disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands had immediately gathered together when they fled and there were even several top 10 ranked masters amongst them. These martial artists all checked their rankings before frowning and saying, “My ranking hasn’t changed.”

“Mine hasn’t changed either.”

“Mm? It hasn’t changed? Does that mean Lin Ming hasn’t died?”

At this time, a core disciple of the True Martial Holy Lands seemed to realize something. He looked up his own ranking and sucked in a cold breath as he saw it.

He was originally the third ranked martial artist of the True Martial Great World. But now, his ranking had dropped to fourth place!

If his ranking dropped and those from fifth to tenth place didn’t, then that could only mean that he swapped places with whoever had been ranked fourth!

And that person had been Lin Ming!

“Lin-Lin Ming’s merit points have suddenly surpassed mine!”

In the top five rankings of a great world, there was a difference of at least 10 million merit points between two people. In a normal situation, the only way that Lin Ming could have leapt ranks was if he killed a top 10 ranked master of a great world, otherwise it would have been impossible for him to jump up ranks so fast. And now, Lin Ming had been chasing that red-furred monster so it was impossible for him to kill other masters.

That only left a single possibility… Lin Ming had killed that red-furred monster and obtained a massive number of merit points!

The martial artists present weren’t idiots. As the ex-third ranked disciple said that Lin Ming’s ranking had changed, everyone realized just what might have happened!

And at this time, the still not recovered Wu Finalcloud examined his own ranking. As he did, his fingers faintly trembled…

Lin Ming’s merit points had surpassed his own!

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother…”

A number of people also thought of Wu Finalcloud and turned to look at him. As they saw the strange expression on his face, a foreboding premonition appeared in their hearts.

This is…

Wu Finalcloud bitterly smiled and shook his head, “He’s passed me… Lin Ming’s merit points have passed my own. I have dropped to third place…”

Wu Finalcloud’s words confirmed everyone’s guesses. To suddenly jump up over 20-30 million merit points in a single go, there was only a single possibility – and that was that Lin Ming had killed the red-furred monster.

To defeat someone was a completely different concept from killing them. As everyone recalled the red-furred monster’s terrifying speed, horrifying defense, and also despair-inducing endurance, wasn’t wanting to overtake it and kill it easier said than done? Perhaps even four or five martial artists that had a similar strength to it wouldn’t be able to keep it from escaping!

But now, it had actually died to Lin Ming’s hands!

Moreover, Lin Ming had chased the red-furred monster through the endless beast tide that surrounded them from all over. He had not only done that but had overtaken it and killed it!

Just how was this possible!?

Everyone looked up towards the pillar of purple light that shot into the skies once more. That pillar of light… could it have been sent out by Lin Ming?

As everyone realized this, they felt their jaws drop down. That roiling thunder dominion that encompassed the skies 10,000 miles away was still lingering there, scorching the world!

The feeling that Lin Ming gave off to everyone had always been that he was a martial artist who focused primarily on the body transformation technique. When he defeated Wu Finalcloud, and even with the red-furred monster, he had relied on his body transformation technique to contend with them. In terms of the essence gathering system and especially in the comprehension of Laws, Lin Ming didn’t seem too extraordinary at all.

But as they saw that terrifyingly titanic thunder dominion that was caused by the Thunder Laws, all of them were left speechless. This level of the Thunder Laws… just what sort of ridiculous power was this!?

Could it have been that Lin Ming’s greatest strength lay in his Laws, but from the beginning until now, no one had been able to force him to use them?

“This is… too unbelievable!”

“What a monster… he is invincible in the body transformation technique, invincible in endurance and recovery, and even his essence gathering system and comprehension of Laws have reached such a level… with such a terrifying explosion of power, just what sort of technique could have caused it? The difference between him and us is just too great…”

Chapter 1222 – Perfect Gold Battle Spirit

“These three strange wisps of energy are actually able to shatter my soul and reform it using themselves as the center. This process is similar to the wonders of Ninefall soul reformation and with an entirely similar result!

“My soul force has become three times stronger. Whatever it is I absorbed, the effects are just too strong!”

Lin Ming found it hard to believe that such incomparably thin lines of energy were able to achieve such a heaven-defying effect.

As he sank his mind into his spiritual sea, he suddenly noticed some differences.

“This is…”

Lin Ming closed his eyes. Vague images, obscure and ancient languages, many things suddenly passed through his mind.

For a time, Lin Ming wasn’t able to understand just what these strange and mysterious images were. It was only when a crowd of creatures similar to the red-furred monster appeared in his mind that he realized these were the memories of that red-furred monster!

“After absorbing the dreamland energy left behind by the red-furred monster, I’ve actually obtained some of its memories? Is this because of the Magic Cube?”

Lin Ming recalled that the feeling of absorbing that dreamland energy was the same as swallowing an ownerless soul fragment from the Magic Cube for the first time when he was 15 years old.

But Lin Ming couldn’t bother with figuring out why he could see these memories. He wanted to hastily search these memories for anything related to the Magic Cube. There were simply far too many secrets on the red-furred monster.

He focused his mind and sat down on the ground, trying to fully digest these memories. Perhaps because of the different natures of the monster’s soul and his human soul, Lin Ming found it extremely difficult to fuse with these memories. Even for the strange writing, Lin Ming had a great deal of difficulty understanding any of it. He had to comb through the memories for corresponding hints in order to make out some meaning from the words.

These memories were incredibly incomplete. Only after searching for a long time did he find some clues.

“Elementary spirit source… those three wisps of soul energy I absorbed are actually wisps of elementary spirit source! If the elementary form is so powerful, what sort of degree would true spirit source be like? And just what is spirit source to begin with?”

Lin Ming was familiar with the term elementary. Grandmist energy also had a so-called elementary grandmist energy form.

“This spirit source… is it something similar to grandmist energy?”

Lin Ming couldn’t help but think this. He continued searching through these memories for more information.

“Mmm… this is…” Lin Ming’s mind shook. As he looked further and dug out more information, he was inexplicably shocked.

“Grandmist energy… genesis energy… spirit source!”

“Three types of source energy!”

Originally, Lin Ming thought that grandmist was the foundation of the universe and the earliest, most source existence. But now, he discovered that the source of the universe was comprised of not just grandmist energy but also two other kinds.

Grandmist energy – the source of matter.

Genesis energy – the source of energies.

Spirit source – the source of soul.

The universe had a soul. Not only did the universe have a soul, but planets and stars also had souls, called star souls.

As for the soul of the universe, if that were to be called a different name, then that would be… the Heavenly Dao!

The Heavenly Dao was omnipotent and omnipresent. When a martial artist cultivated the Laws, they would comprehend the Heavenly Dao and follow its rules to display their skills.

Cultivation methods, martial skills, every Concept, everything was through methods defined by the Heavenly Dao.

If one wanted to surpass the Heavenly Dao then one had to withstand the punishment of the Heavenly Dao.

This was also known as heavenly tribulation. By crossing heavenly tribulation, one could gain the right to surpass the Heavenly Dao and perhaps even form their own rules. If a human could achieve such a boundary then they were called an Empyrean!

Empyrean, a word that meant the heavens. The inherent meaning within this title was that the person this title was bestowed upon had a status on par with the Heavenly Dao.

Empyrean, a word that also meant respect. In total, to be an Empyrean meant to be respected just as much as the heavens!

This was the meaning of an Empyrean!

From the very start, Lin Ming never understood just what the Heavenly Dao was. He only knew that it was an extremely abstract existence. But at the same time, the Heavenly Dao seemed to have a thought and will of its own, punishing anyone that dared to violate its edicts.

And now, Lin Ming was finally aware. The Heavenly Dao – that was the soul of the universe!

And this so-called spirit source was present at the forming of the universe, a source energy that eventually became the Heavenly Dao.

The soul of the universe. Out of the three aspects of essence, energy, and divine, it could be called the ‘divine’.

As the universe had a soul, at the same time it also had a body!

Every star, every moon, every planet, all the vast galaxies and boundless worlds, everything was the body of the universe!

Even humans, plants, vicious beasts, all lives that existed were also a part of the universe’s body.

Grandmist energy formed all matter within the world, and was also the source of the universe’s body.

Of essence, energy, and divine, the body of the universe could also be represented by ‘essence’.

Finally… there was genesis energy.

The source of all energy, all origin energies, all true essence – all the various forms of energy were evolved from genesis energy.

Of essence, energy, and divine, this was the ‘energy’ of the universe.

Humans possessed essence, energy, and divine. Correspondingly, the universe also had its own essence, energy, and divine.

Grandmist energy corresponded with ‘essence’, genesis energy corresponded with ‘energy’, and spirit source corresponded with the ‘divine’.

There just happened to be three of these source energies. This was also what the myths meant by three creating all of myriad existence!

As Lin Ming understood these truths, he felt his spiritual sea suddenly shake. It was like a thin layer of membrane had been pierced through, in that that moment, many truths and Laws were immediately comprehended by him. In that instant Lin Ming could feel his own strength crazily rise and his soul force was again strengthening at a terrifying speed.

Lin Ming’s first four Concepts of Thunder and Fire completely fused together. And in his spiritual sea, his battle spirit also violently trembled. As it trembled, all of its power constantly gathered onto itself, becoming more and more solid and more and more sharp. With this sort of change, Lin Ming’s battle spirit had broken through gold large success to gold perfection.

Now he was only a single step away from a blue soul battle spirit.

And after achieving a blue soul battle spirit, that would be a completely different situation!

Lin Ming sank his thoughts into his body. He discovered that the countless Law fragments that had buried themselves into his flesh during his Ninefall had begun to slowly fuse into his flesh. As for his Thunder and Fire Laws, in that moment just now they had instantly reached perfection of the first four Concepts. Lin Ming could even faintly feel himself touching upon the fifth level Concepts.

In just a few breaths of time, Lin Ming had obtained an immeasurable advantage. Although he had yet to break through a cultivation boundary, his practical strength had substantially increased. This was mainly manifested in the comprehension and use of his Laws as well as his battle spirit.

If Lin Ming were to use his Heavenly Dao Judgment now, it would be even mightier than before.

Even if he were to use the most basic Penetrating Rainbow, Chasing Thunder, Chasing Sun, or Bury the Heavens, just a single strike would be able to easily kill a top 10 ranked core disciple of a Great World King Holy Land.

Lin Ming was overjoyed as he sensed the changes in his body. Unfortunately, his true mortal body wasn’t in the Divine Dream World, otherwise he would have likely broken through to the middle Divine Sea.

However, now that his soul had made a breakthrough, his inner world was brimming with energy. If he left the divine dream space then he wouldn’t need much effort to break into the middle Divine Sea realm. It could be called an inevitable event.

“I see… so the Magic Cube, Demon Bead, and Purple Card in truth represent spirit source, grandmist energy, and genesis energy. They are divine tools somehow condensed from the essence, energy, and divine of the universe.”

Lin Ming became increasingly aware of the origin and use of the three divine tools.

“When Empyrean Primordius obtained the Demon Bead, that was also the universe’s ‘essence’, thus he was able to dual cultivate in body and energy, reaching a boundary at which he could rip out his heart and it would still beat onwards for 100,000 years. This was likely thanks to the support of the Demon Bead. As for the grandmist energy he cultivated, that is the source of the universe’s ‘body’. No wonder Empyrean Primordius was such a remarkable person that could achieve such heights in the Grandmist Laws.”

Lin Ming unraveled more of the secrets of Empyrean Primordius and the Eternal Demon Abyss, and most of his guesses were likely true. It seemed that if he obtained the Demon Bead in the future, it would play a critical role in him cultivating the Grandmist Laws.

The Grandmist Laws were in truth the Laws of the universe’s ‘essence’. There might even be true grandmist energy within the Demon Bead.

“Empyrean Primordius cultivated dual body and energy, but Empyrean Divine Dream cultivates spirit source, thus she is likely a dual energy and soul cultivator. This is why she was able to form the Divine Dream World and also leave behind these elementary spirit sources within it. These elementary spirit sources were likely rewards for the trial challengers here, but there are probably far too few people that could hope to obtain them.”

Lin Ming thought out loud. With the red-furred monster’s titanic strength, the ordinary geniuses of a great world simply wouldn’t be able to kill it.

However, this was also well within reason. Elementary spirit source was an incomparably precious treasure. It was impossible for Empyrean Divine Dream to reward it too freely, thus she would only allow the most peak geniuses to obtain it.

Chapter 1223 – Tian Mingzi

Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds, Vast Universe World –

Although the 3000 great worlds of the Divine Realm were grouped together, the truth was that they vastly differed in size and number of masters present.

Vast Universe World was one of the top 10 ranked great worlds. In terms of area, it was over 20 times larger than the Crimson Light World that the Ancient Phoenix Headquarters was located on. Compared to the True Martial World, it was still seven or eight times larger. The number of masters present was incomparable with the lower ranked great worlds.

The highest ranked great worlds all had a title, and that was a first-order world. Out of the 3000 great worlds, only 100 of them were considered first-order worlds.

A world like the True Martial World was a great world only inferior to first-order worlds. They were called second-order worlds and there were several hundred of them.

As for the Crimson Light World and Atlas World, they were considered third-order worlds. There was the greatest number of third-order worlds, over 2000 of them.

Not only were the first-order worlds larger but there were far more masters present on them. Moreover, many first-order worlds were occupied by Empyreans! This was one of the implicit assessment marks of a first-order world.

On the Divine Seal Decree, the highest ranked participants were mostly from these first-order worlds.

The most sacred land of the Vast Universe World was also where Empyrean Vast Universe’s Holy Palace was located – the center of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.

At this time, within a grand hall of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, there was a group of people gathered. These people all had an unfathomably deep cultivation. But at this time, within Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, all of them were restraining their aura as much as possible, resembling nothing but ordinary people.

Within Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, unless one was an Empyrean, all other characters, no matter how famous or honorable they were, had to humble themselves.

In this group of people, there was a tall and sturdy man wearing a spacious robe with a square face and round ears. He sat in the seat of honor and was lifting a cup of wine. He laughed as he said, “The several top ranked participants are really all Empyrean descendants. However, Grand Universe World King, your Grand Universe Holy Land is doing quite well. Since the Empyrean descendants aren’t counted, one of the top ranked participants comes from your Grand Universe Holy Land.”

The Grand Universe World King was the Great World King of Vast Universe World. However, because of the unstated taboo of having a name similar to Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, they certainly couldn’t name themselves the Vast Universe Holy Lands. Thus, their name instead was the Grand Universe Holy Lands. Correspondingly, the Great World King of Vast Universe World was also called the Grand Universe World King.

“Haha, Lord Envoy, I truly cannot withstand such high praise. My Grand Universe Holy Lands only has a single person that has barely managed to reach rank 12 on the Divine Seal Decree. Even if the Empyrean descendants aren’t considered, Bo’er is just chasing the tail of the top 10 rankings. All of my other disciples have met defeat!”

At a seat just to the side of the tall and sturdy man, a hearty-looking blue-clothed old man stroked his beard as he spoke in a modest tone. Even so, he couldn’t conceal the smile in his words. It was clear that he was satisfied that one of the disciples from his Grand Universe Holy Lands was almost in the top 10 ranks.

“Virtuous Nephew Yuwen Bo has considerable hopes of entering the top 10 ranks of the First Martial Meeting. If he does, then he’ll likely come to Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.” The tall and sturdy man chuckled.

“Haha, I don’t dare to hope for him to enter the top 10. But, if there really is such hope, then I humbly request that Lord Envoy looks after him at that time.”

As the blue-clothed old man spoke to here, he respectfully cupped his hands across his chest.

This tall and sturdy robed man was Empyrean Vast Universe’s chief disciple and the first lord envoy of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. His name was Vast Cosmos.

To be able to be named after Vast Universe Heavenly Palace and also be named Cosmos, one could infer his status.

The so-called chief disciple of Empyrean Vast Universe was not like Wu Finalcloud, who was merely a chief disciple of a single generation. Rather, Vast Cosmos was the disciple that had attained the highest achievements ever since the founding of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.

In fact, Vast Cosmos had long since reached the boundary of a half-step Empyrean!

Although a half-step Empyrean was extremely far from being comparable with a true Empyrean, it was still a boundary vastly superior to a Great World King.

In addition, Vast Cosmos had the special distinction of being able to personally represent Empyrean Vast Universe. Vast Cosmos’s status far surpassed that of a Great World King. Even if it were the Great World King of a first-order world, they would still have to be respectful towards him.

And in this First Martial Meeting, the top 10 ranking disciples would obtain a special reward – to enter Vast Universe Heavenly Palace and also be able to receive the personal guidance of Empyrean Vast Universe’s chief disciple.

This chief disciple was naturally Vast Cosmos.

Vast Cosmos laughed and said, “Grand Universe World King is too modest. Although it was said that the top 10 may enter Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, the true Empyrean descendants, even if they were in the top 10, definitely wouldn’t take a liking to a humble and common teacher like myself, and they certainly wouldn’t come to Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. At that time, if Nephew Yuwen can achieve a position near the top 10 he can certainly enter Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.”

Hearing Vast Cosmos say this, the Grand Universe World King was overjoyed and repeatedly expressed his thanks. If one could enter Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, then even if they couldn’t learn a transcendent divine might they could still learn the self-created martial arts of Empyrean Vast Universe. If those martial arts were placed in the Grand Universe Holy Lands, they would definitely be the highest level of martial arts.

“This First Martial Meeting is unprecedented in its magnificence and grandeur. It is far more marvelous and ambitious than the last several dozens of First Martial Meetings. This time, it could truly be said that there are countless talents gushing forth. Also, Tian Mingzi, your Skydark Holy Lands has a disciple that has reached rank 15 on the Divine Seal Decree. Is that little fellow your direct descendant? If I remember, his name was Nether Limitless, right?”

Vast Cosmos asked a black-clothed man who was sitting on another side of the hall.

This black-clothed man was handsome and elegant, looking no more than 20 years old. His arms were laid calmly on his knees. His palms were clear and fair, his 10 fingers were slender and beautiful, and his eyes had blood red pupils, making him seem a bit fiendish.

This man was Mo Eversnow’s absolutely irreconcilable blood enemy and also the chief culprit that caused the destruction of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands – Tian Mingzi.

In the past when Tian Mingzi annihilated the Verdant Feather Holy Lands he had been a World King. Now, 50,000 years later, his cultivation had reached an even more terrifying boundary.

The black-clothed man faintly smiled and eloquently said, “I didn’t expect Lord Envoy to remember Limitless’s name. I must thank Lord Envoy for the wonderful praise.”

“Haha, Tian Mingzi, there is no need to be so polite. Haven’t you just passed 100,000 years in age? You became a World King only tens of thousands of years ago and now you are already a Great World King. Moreover, you preside over the first-order world of Demondawn Great World. In the future it wouldn’t be strange if you were to become a half-step Empyrean. This sort of talent is truly deserving of envy.”

Vast Cosmos bluntly said as he laughed.

As he spoke, this roused a round of discussion amongst everyone else in the hall.

“That’s right, Skydark World King only established the Skydark Holy Lands 50,000 years ago and yet you have progress that one can truly be proud of. Old me can only be ashamed of my own inferiority. My Grand Universe Holy Lands have existence for over 7 million years and now you’ve nearly reached the same level!”

The Grand Universe World King smiled as he tossed out some more praise.

“That’s right, Skydark World King is the youngest among us yet his strength has faintly risen above ours. I think he will surely become a half-step Empyrean in the future.”

“Haha, even Tian Mingzi’s direct descendant Nephew Nether Limitless is also extraordinary. I think there is an extremely high possibility that he will become a World King in the future!”

Of those sitting in this hall, the ones with the lowest status were ordinary World Kings and there were even many Great World Kings of second-order and first-order worlds. These were all characters with extremely lofty statuses, and yet all of them were praising Tian Mingzi. From this alone, one could see just how prominent his reputation was.

For the last 100,000 years, out of all those that had become Great World Kings, he was the youngest.

From the time he founded the Skydark Holy Lands, it had only taken him 50,000 years to develop it to such a giant scale. Moreover, rumors said that he had obtained the appreciation of Demondawn Great World’s true overlord – Empyrean Demondawn. If such a character favored him then Tian Mingzi’s future prospects could be imagined.

He even had a slight ray of hope of becoming an Empyrean in the future. Just what sort of concept was an Empyrean? In the entire Divine Realm, an Empyrean was born only every million years or so. This was a level of existence that a World King could never compare with.

To this sort of character, even if they couldn’t form good relations with him, they at least shouldn’t offend him.

Tian Mingzi smiled as he said, “Everyone, I can hardly accept all this praise. I am merely a junior in this prestigious gathering, and I still have a long road ahead of me in the future. I will have to ask all the seniors here to look after me. As for Limitless, he has only made a tiny bit of progress, nothing worthy of complimenting at all. Compared to Fairy Maiden Xiao Moxian from Demondawn Heavenly Palace, there simply isn’t any comparison at all.”

Tian Mingzi’s great world was exactly Demondawn Great World. The Holy Land he established naturally couldn’t have the name of Demondawn, thus he came up with his own name for it.

…….

As all of this was happening in Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming was still in the Divine Dream World, sifting through the memories of the red-furred monster. He had been doing this for the last three days.

The new information he discovered left him incomparably shocked.

The memories of the red-furred monster were filled with all sorts of strange and mystical images. As these images combined together, Lin Ming was able to extrapolate that the red-furred monster came from a different realm. This different realm was called Soul World by the red-furred monster.

In Soul World, all lives there were soul life forms!

As for the red-furred monster, it was also a soul life form. Its appearance within the Divine Dream World was its soul form.

Soul World was not one of the Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds. Soul World was broad, boundless, nearly infinite in its area, far greater than any great world of the Divine Realm! It seemed as if it were a completely independent dimension outside of the Divine Realm!

“There is actually such a place in this universe? Is it a divergent mystic realm?”

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath, feeling greatly shocked. He originally thought that the Divine Realm was the entirety of the universe, but now it seemed as if this might not be true.

If Soul World was a divergent mystic realm, then the vastness of these divergent mystic realms far surpassed Lin Ming’s imagination.

In the red-furred monster’s memory, Lin Ming saw that Empyrean Divine Dream had once been to Soul World!

This matter was already from an extremely long time ago. At that time, Empyrean Divine Dream’s cultivation had been very low.

The red-furred monster, as well as numerous other soul beasts from Soul World, had tried to attack Empyrean Divine Dream. However, she had ended up completely demolishing all of them.

But Empyrean Divine Dream did not kill them. Rather, she locked them all into the Divine Dream World, and the Divine Dream World had become their prison.

As Lin Ming learned all of this, he was lost in thought for some time. He guessed that Soul World was a divergent mystic realm of some sort, and when Empyrean Divine Dream’s cultivation was extremely low in the past, she likely entered this divergent mystic realm to adventure and seek her own lucky chances. Finally, she had stumbled across some heaven-defying lucky chance and learned the secrets of Soul World. With this, she established the Divine Dream Law and completed her own transcendent divine might!

Chapter 1225 – Fated Encounter

“Honorable Master.”

Yan Littlemoon bowed towards Huo Violentstone. During the period of time after Lin Ming left the Ancient Phoenix Clan, Yan Littlemoon had officially taken Huo Violentstone as her master.

Huo Violentstone guffawed. “Good! You’ve done a good job! Xiao Ping, well, he also did good.”

Xiao Ping was once the number one disciple of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, but now he was overshadowed by Yan Littlemoon. During the preliminaries, Xiao Ping had only achieved around rank 150 in his great world, a much worse result than Yan Littlemoon.

“I thank Highest Elder for the generous praise.”

Xiao Ping ruefully smiled, a strange taste in his heart. To be beaten by a young girl who was eight or nine years younger and also had a lower cultivation than him, to him that was a great loss of face.

“Alright, clean yourselves up and prepare to go to the semifinals. Our Ancient Phoenix Clan will have four disciples entering the semifinals this time, it’s truly a good harvest.”

“Four disciples?”

Yan Littlemoon and Xiao Ping were both startled. As fellow disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, they helped each other in the Divine Dream World and also had a general understanding of all the other disciples’ merit points and were thus able to guess just who was capable of passing the preliminaries and who wasn’t. This time, there should have only been three disciples that passed. Besides Yan Littlemoon and Xiao Ping there was also a core disciple that was ranked around 1800 of a great world. He just barely managed to pass.

Then just who was the fourth person?

Huo Violentstone already expected that Yan Littlemoon and Xiao Ping would ask this. He mysteriously said, “You two should also be able to guess who this fourth person is…”

“Is… is it Senior-apprentice Brother Lin Ming?” Yan Littlemoon suddenly recalled that several years ago, Lin Ming had left the Ancient Phoenix Clan to go out adventuring. Considering the time that passed so far, he should have managed to reach the early or middle Divine Sea realm by now. With Lin Ming’s talent, he naturally wouldn’t miss such a grand event!

“Yes, it’s exactly Lin Ming!” Huo Violentstone said, happily stroking his beard. He couldn’t conceal his wide grin.

Yan Littlemoon suddenly realized just why Huo Violentstone was in such a good mood. So the reason must have been because Lin Ming also joined the First Martial Meeting. With Lin Ming’s talent, he naturally would bring honor to the Ancient Phoenix Clan.

As Yan Littlemoon thought of Lin Ming, a strange color washed over her face. Towards Lin Ming, she felt something that she couldn’t yet explain.

“Are Senior-apprentice Brother Lin’s results much better than ours?” Yan Littlemoon asked.

“Haha, Lin Ming gave us all a pleasant surprise. At his highest ranking, he managed to kill his way into the top 1000 rankings of the Divine Seal Decree and became first ranked in the True Martial Great World. But afterwards… that brat was just too lazy, far too lazy, and because of that his ranking fell. He finally ended as fourth place on the True Martial Great World, but he still managed to keep in the top 10,000 rankings of the Divine Realm.”

Even though Yan Littlemoon and Xiao Ping were already prepared, they still sucked in a cold breath upon hearing this. To become the first ranked martial artist of the True Martial Great World! And the True Martial Great World was also a second-order word. This result was simply too freakish.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin, he really…” Yan Littlemoon sighed. For all these years, she didn’t dare to laze around for even half a minute. Moreover, she had displayed the power and potential of her bloodline to the limit. She had hoped that she would be able to slowly overtake Lin Ming’s footsteps, or even if she couldn’t she would still be able to see his back. But now, she realized that the difference between them was only becoming increasingly wide.

As for Xiao Ping, his mouth dropped open again and again, at a complete loss for words. He felt incomparable envy and jealousy simmering in his heart. He suspected that during their trip into the God Beast Mystic Realm, perhaps the supreme dragon bone had been stolen away by Lin Ming.

When the supreme dragon bone had suddenly vanished, no one knew just where Lin Ming was. He had thought that Lin Ming had died but in the end Lin Ming had also been transmitted out of the God Beast Mystic Realm. Because Lin Ming’s cultivation was just far too low at the time and his strength also wasn’t worth mentioning, Xiao Ping hadn’t been suspicious of him. But with things as they were now, Xiao Ping felt doubtful of his past judgment.

There was likely some heaven-defying secret on that boy’s body!

But now, even if he was 100% sure that Lin Ming had taken the supreme dragon bone, there wasn’t anything he could do about it. With Lin Ming’s current status, let alone taking back that supreme dragon bone, the Ancient Phoenix Clan might instead bestow several drops of phoenix blood essence to him!

That was phoenix blood essence! This was something that Xiao Ping yearned for in his every dream. For his entire life, without some massive lucky chance, there wasn’t any way he would ever obtain even a single drop.

“Where will the semifinals be held? What are the rules?”

Yan Littlemoon asked Huo Violentstone. In the preliminaries, the elimination rate had reached a despairing percentage; only one out of every billion participants had managed to make it through. Even so, the original number of participating martial artists in this First Martial Meeting was far too great. Although the elimination rate was astoundingly high, there were still around 10 million martial artists throughout the entire Divine Realm that had made it through the preliminaries. It wouldn’t be easy to screen out these people at all.

Huo Violentstone said, “The rules have already been passed out. Out of the 3000 great worlds, every 100 great worlds will be divided into a group and that group will compete in a small world. In every group of 100 great worlds, there are many participants from first-order worlds and second-order worlds. Every group will have over 300,000 participants, but only 300 people will make it out of every group in the semifinals.”

“Only… 3… 300 people?” Xiao Ping’s mouth fell open again. This elimination ratio was far too exaggerated. In 100 great worlds, in which many first-order and second-order worlds were included, only 300 people would make it through.

This meant that if one wished to make it through they would need to be one of the top three ranked masters of a great world. And, since their Crimson Light World was a third-order world, the top three ranked masters were a bit less worthy than the top three masters of other great worlds. In order to pass, one would need to be in the top two rankings or perhaps even the number one ranking!

In other words, no matter how hard he and Yan Littlemoon tried, it was impossible for them to pass the semifinals.

Their journey here would both end in the semifinals.

To bid farewell to the grand stage of the First Martial Meeting like this, Xiao Ping felt a bit melancholic. Although he knew that powerhouses existed all over the Divine Realm like clouds and he simply wasn’t worthy of mentioning, Xiao Ping always held a faint hope close to his heart that he would be able to amaze the world with a magnificent feat. But now, he wouldn’t even be able to pass the semifinals. Not just that, but he would fall far short.

Yan Littlemoon was also well aware that she wouldn’t pass the semifinals and this was a completely hopeless wish. That meant that in the entire Ancient Phoenix Clan, only Lin Ming had a chance of passing.

She asked, “What is the competition method like?”

“No idea.” Huo Violentstone responded, shaking his head. “Lin Ming is at the True Martial Great World. That great world isn’t too far from ours. We should be able to run into him during the semifinals!”

“Is that so…” Yan Littlemoon took a deep breath, not sure of what she was feeling.

‘Lin Ming, so many years have passed, what are you like now?’

……….

At this time, the True Martial Great World, the martial field of the First Martial Meeting preliminaries –

Hu – !

Lin Ming’s soul form was ejected from the Divine Dream World. Consciousness was restored to his body.

He clenched his fists and stood up. He could see that for 10 miles around him, there were fellow participants scattered all over who had passed the preliminaries just like him.

At the start of the First Martial Meeting when everyone first entered the Divine Dream World, this entire field had been occupied by martial artists. The surrounding area for miles had been tightly packed with participants. But now, the participants remaining were all scattered around loosely.

“Lin Ming.”

At the moment Lin Ming regained consciousness, a warm and familiar voice resounded in his mind. This voice came from Mo Eversnow.

“Miss Mo.”

With a thought, Lin Ming’s mind entered the Magic Cube space.

Here, he saw Mo Eversnow as well as Fishy.

Fishy was currently sleeping. This little girl’s appetite was becoming increasingly large, to a ridiculous rate. Lin Ming had left 8-9 million violet sun stones in the Magic Cube space but most of them had been eaten up by her already.

The current Lin Ming could be described as a broke man cleaned out of all wealth. After buying the Boundless World Pill, the leftover change had been nearly entirely eaten up by Fishy. Not just that, but he still owed a debt of 6 trillion!

As Lin Ming thought of this debt, he fell somewhat silent.

After Lin Ming entered the Magic Cube space, Fishy seemed to sense him and suddenly woke up. She rubbed her large and sleepy eyes. After seeing Lin Ming, she perked up and excitedly smiled.

“Big Brother Lin Ming!”

“Fishy.” Lin Ming held Fishy’s hands. Although her real age was unknown, she had the appearance of a little 11-12 year old girl. In Lin Ming’s eyes she was a cute little child.

For these nine months, Fishy had basically eaten and slept again and again. She had been living a fun and carefree life.

“We have to immediately go to the semifinals. It seems that the semifinals won’t be held in the Divine Dream World. We’ll have to ride a spirit ship to a designated location.”

Lin Ming said. Then, his thoughts suddenly stirred. “Oh, there’s a message.”

His consciousness left the Magic Cube space just as the flames of a sound transmitting talisman lit up right in front of him.

This was information sent from Immemorial Imperial City’s River Feather.

When Lin Ming had first bought the Boundless World Pill, River Feather had lent Lin Ming 100 billion violet stun stones even though he didn’t completely understand his situation. Although this didn’t seem like much, Lin Ming had indeed made good use of River Feather’s loan. Lin Ming held a very good impression towards him.

“Brother Lin, congratulations!”

River Feather used a sound transmitting talisman to determine Lin Ming’s position and then rushed to catch up. As he was shouting out from afar, his voice could be described as filled with joy and delight. Lin Ming’s results had far surpassed anything he had hoped for. Even the disciples of the True Martial Holy Lands were inferior to Lin Ming. River Feather realized that he had truly stumbled into a great person this time!

As long as he could continue solidifying his relationship with Lin Ming, his status in his family would rise straight up into the skies.

“Brother Lin, the name list of those competing in the semifinals has been passed out. I’ve already bought a jade slip. Come, take a look.”

As River Feather spoke, he offered up a jade slip.

Lin Ming took the jade slip and swept his sense through it. This jade slip listed 100 great worlds of the Divine Realm.

These Divine Realm great worlds came in varying sizes. The larger ones had over 10,000 participants and the smaller ones had 1000-2000 participants. There were over three million participants in total.

The name of the Crimson Light World caught Lin Ming’s attention: this was where the Ancient Phoenix Clan Headquarters were located.

Just as he was about to search for the Ancient Phoenix Clan for any familiar names, he suddenly felt a disturbance in his spiritual sea. Mo Eversnow’s consciousness was intensely fluctuating.

“Miss Mo, is something wrong?”

Lin Ming was slightly stunned. In his mind, Mo Eversnow was someone that was always calm, neither happy nor angry. She rarely lost her composure.

Mo Eversnow took a deep breath. She closed her eyes, her long eyelashes faintly trembling. After some time, she opened her eyes once more, an icy cold light flashing within them.

She slowly said, enunciating every word,, “Tian Mingzi’s descendant is inside!”

“Mm?”

Lin Ming was shocked.

Tian Mingzi!

This was a name that he had heard many times before. But today was his first time actually coming into contact with it!

Tian Mingzi’s descendant. Who knew that Tian Mingzi’s descendant would actually be in the semifinals too? This could truly be called a fated encounter.

Chapter 1236 – 20th Step

All the way forwards, Nether Limitless was still in the lead as before, his momentum nearly unstoppable.

Close behind Nether Limitless was Bloodless Sword. Bloodless Sword also easily defeated his opponent on the eighth level, but he had to use his weapon unlike Nether Limitless. For some contestants that didn’t use weapons, they didn’t care much for Bloodless Sword so they didn’t follow him in this.

With a sword cutting down a spirit body, Bloodless Sword continued his climb to the ninth floor.

“Haha, Elder Senior-apprentice Brother is very steady.”

“As a swordsman, there’s no point in not using your sword.”

“Right, there’s no point at all! In truth, Elder Senior-apprentice Brother doesn’t even need to use his sword because he has already reached the sword of the heart boundary. In his hands, there is no difference whether he is wielding a sword or not.”

In the audience, Fairy Feng heard the cheers of everyone around her and the hosts casting the situation on the altar. She shook her head and said, “Lin Ming likely didn’t use his weapon because he simply didn’t think it was necessary. I never imagined that such a little thing like this would cause such comparisons.”

Huo Violentstone said, “It’s not strange. In this semifinal, the geniuses that climb the Divine Seal Altar aren’t competing in just speed but also how calmly they can cut down the spirit bodies. Many people are becoming famous because of this!

“Those martial artists that have a shallow background hope to become famous so that they can be taken in by some great influence.

“As for those martial artists with a great background and who also come from a great influence, they hope to become famous in order to bring glory to their Holy Lands and possibly even garner the attention of an Empyrean!”

When an Empyrean chose a descendant, their pool of candidates was every single genius of every great influence in the Divine Realm. The First Martial Meetings of the past had all been good places for an Empyrean to choose their descendant.

An Empyrean could live for nearly a hundred million years. Even so, most would receive several hundred descendants or even less than a 100.

Of these people, the weakest amongst them were ordinary World Kings.

Rather, it would be more accurate to say that these ordinary World King descendants were Empyrean descendants that had exhausted all of their potential before growing up.

As for those who were able to develop, they were able to become Great World Kings or even half-step Empyreans. There were even those select few that could grow into new Empyreans!

With this, if a disciple of a Great World King Holy Land was chosen by an Emyprean, that would absolutely be the greatest honor of all.

That Great World King Holy Land disciple, if they were to receive such an honor, would invite all the guests they knew and hold a grand feast filled with heroes, a great celebration that would continue for several days.

This sort of feeling was the same as the mortal world where the daughter of a wealthy family would be married into the imperial palace as a royal concubine.

Although the family wouldn’t have many more opportunities to see their daughter again, that daughter would still grow up and live a good life in the palace, and would also be able to bring a great advantage to her family.

The relationship between a Holy Land and an Empyrean Heaven Palace was similar to this.

Now, Nether Limitless and Bloodless Sword wanted to use this First Martial Meeting to their advantage; their ultimate goal was to become an Empyrean descendant.

And the one presiding over these semifinals was also the direct disciple of an Empyrean. If their performance was exceptional, they might be noticed by an Empyrean!

They weren’t afraid of showing off, only that they wouldn’t show off enough!

“I must reach the top, that is my only goal! Xiao Daochild said that the chances of us reaching the summit are slim, but I must do it so that everyone can see me!”

Nether Limitless’s blood boiled over. After another quarter hour he defeated the spirit body of the ninth step.

In defeating his opponent he didn’t use a weapon as before. Facing the spirit bodies of the ninth step or even the spirit bodies of higher steps, there really wasn’t a difference to Nether Limitless in how difficult it was.

And at this time, Lin Ming was now facing his opponent on the seventh step.

His opponent was a white-clothed woman with long hair. Her facial features were blurred.

These simulation spirit bodies all had different appearances, techniques, and cultivation methods. Lin Ming guessed that the different spirit bodies formed by the array formations on the Divine Seal Altar were similar to the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s own Illusionary God Combat Array. That was, they were able to use array formations to record a martial artist’s specific techniques and styles, and use this data to recreate a simulation spirit body.

These simulated spirit bodies were nearly the same as the real person. Whatever weaknesses the real person had, these spirit bodies would also have.

The weapon that this woman used was a soft sword. With just a glance, Lin Ming was able to feel the special characteristics of her true essence fluctuations, her use of weapons, her steps, and with this information he was able to guess that she was a martial artist that excelled in speed.

If he could suppress her in the aspect she excelled in the most, then he could instantly defeat her.

Chasing Thunder!

Lin Ming’s vision sharpened as he immediately opened Mystic Lightning Shade. His feet stepped on Golden Roc Shattering the Void and he attacked with his fastest move – Chasing Thunder!

Xiu!

A brilliant electric purple light shout out, cutting through the air and directly striking the white-clothed woman!

She was fast, but her speed was still far from being able to compare with Lin Ming.

Chi chi chi!

An electric light flashed out. But, at this time, something that left Lin Ming extremely surprised took place. The attack he sent out was one that even an ordinary Divine Transformation realm powerhouse wouldn’t be able to withstand. But, this white-clothed woman was actually completely uninjured. Her protective true essence was totally immune to Lin Ming’s Thunder Laws!

“Mm? She’s becoming stronger instead? She can absorb the power of my Thunder Laws for herself and convert it to her own strength? How is that even possible?”

Lin Ming was so startled that he was left speechless… this woman’s protective true essence was able to absorb his own thunder attack and transform his strength into her own!

This sort of ability was only possessed by certain ancient vicious beasts and God Beasts. There were some ancient vicious beasts that had achieved a certain degree in their compatibility with the Laws and were completely immune to certain Law-based attacks.

For instance, there was the mythical Thunder Dragon. If one were to use thunder-based attacks against one then that was the same as delivering a nourishing tonic to it. The only method to overcome this was if one’s own power of thunder had reached a boundary where it was able to disregard the Laws of the world. For instance, Empyrean Thunder Punishment was this sort of top powerhouse.

Those beings that had this ability were either God Beasts or existences close to God Beasts. Lin Ming had never heard of a human that possessed this type of ability.

Lin Ming had the Heretical God Force which was itself a transcendent divine might. Even so, it could only absorb the power of thunder and fire that didn’t surpass his own boundary. If a thunder or fire attack that far surpassed Lin Ming’s limits were to strike him, it would still severely wound him.

“How strange! Why would this sort of opponent appear at only the seventh level!”

Lin Ming was puzzled. But, he didn’t pause in his movements. If the power of thunder didn’t work, he would switch to flames!

Chasing Sun shot out, smashing into the white-clothed woman. Then, something even more unbelievable occurred. This white-clothed woman was also immune to fire-based attacks!

“She’s immune to the Fire Laws? Immunity to thunder, immunity to fire, it’s as if this opponent was specifically targeted at me!”

Lin Ming thought something was strange. Starting from the sixth level, something unusual had been occurring. The opponents he faced were clearly far more formidable than the others!

“Did I hit the jackpot? Did I accidentally stumble into some hidden difficulty level? Or are there people purposefully trying to play tricks on me? But that doesn’t make sense… I have no idea what enemy I might have made that would be going against me here.”

Out of all the enemies Lin Ming had provoked, the strongest ones were the three prodigies of Sacred Martial Mansion, Zhong Wenshu, and Wu Finalcloud. However, they were all from World King and Great World King level Holy Lands, so it was impossible for them to affect the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting.

“If thunder and fire don’t work, then I will defeat you with absolute strength!”

Lin Ming couldn’t bother with getting to the bottom of what was happening right now. He directly took out the Phoenix Blood Spear and opened the first four of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. The power of the Gate of Pain erupted, multiplying Lin Ming’s striking power by several times.

A spear thrust out, the speed reaching the limit. The power of 8-9 million jins of strength blew up. With a loud explosive sound, the white-clothed woman exploded into countless motes of light!

“He really is a dual body and energy cultivator.”

Within the inner world of the Divine Seal Altar, the gray-clothed man’s eyebrows shot up. He was the one deliberately causing trouble for Lin Ming in order to probe his strength by forcing him to use new moves.

“He dual cultivates in body and energy, and his body transformation technique has already opened the fourth gate… the Gate of Pain! Those geniuses that choose to walk the paths of dual body and energy cultivation have nearly disappeared. Among the Empyreans, nearly none of them do this. There are only some geniuses of small sects that are too full of themselves who believe they can walk down the road of dual body and energy cultivation.

“That young kid Vast Universe is resolutely opposed to dual cultivating body and energy. After all, not everyone can be like Empyrean Primordius and experience such heaven-shaking lucky chances! And without those lucky chances and under the current restrictions of the Heavenly Dao Laws, the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace become a demonic curse that can never be broken through. In truth, disregarding the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, barely anyone in this universe can hope to break past the life and death threshold of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates.”

The old man traced his beard. The road of martial artists was broad and profound. By just walking down one cultivation system to the limit, one could become an Empyrean. But out of a trillion trillion lives, how many people were able to become an Empyrean?

If one couldn’t even bring one cultivation system to the limit and yet tried to split their attention with another, that was simply far too ambitious. Not just that, but the body transformation technique system was currently prohibited by the Heavenly Dao Laws.

The gray-clothed man also didn’t believe in dual cultivating body and energy.

“This boy actually chose to dual cultivate body and energy. Is it because he is overconfident in himself or is it because his master is an idiot? Or, perhaps he has some other cards in hand? His skeletal age is just over 30 years. With his essence gathering system cultivation at this level, his body transformation technique has at most four gates opened… that’s also quite good. If he continues on this road then I suspect it will harm him. In the next step, I must take a good look at how he fares in other aspects…”

The gray-clothed old man thought out loud. He didn’t have much faith in Lin Ming’s body transformation technique.

“Something seems strange with Senior-apprentice Brother Lin.”

“In the last two steps, he won with some difficulty. He even had to bring out his weapon on the seventh step. And in the future, the further he goes up the harder his opponents will be.”

“He’s in a bit of danger…”

From the Ancient Phoenix Clan as well as from the Crimson Light World, there were many people that were worried for Lin Ming. Just how strong was the Divine Seal Altar’s artifact spirit? If it did something, there were very few people that could see through it.

“Humph, what are you worried about? Senior-apprentice Brother Lin clearly hasn’t shown his true abilities. He’s clearly saving his strength for the future. The truly magnificent battles are still coming up! Not just that, but there are 300 people that can pass these semifinals. If Lin Ming can be in the top 300 then he’ll be fine. It’s his win as long as he can attend the finals.”

As this disciple spoke, he seemed to lose confidence in his own words.

Although their words and tone didn’t admit defeat, the truth was that if things continued like this, then even they couldn’t tell just how Lin Ming’s final results would be.

As for the twin girl hosts at the base of the Divine Seal Altar, they no longer spoke about Lin Ming. They only paid attention to the powerhouses at the top, shifting their attention to the several martial artists in the first group. They were currently the most dazzling characters in the semifinals.

The battle between Nether Limitless and Bloodless Sword was the focus of attention for nearly everyone in the audience.

Like this, the over 200,000 participants continued their struggle climbing upwards!

Tenth step, eleventh step, twelfth step, thirteenth step, fourteenth step…

Every step was harder than the last!

More and more participants were eliminated.

Nether Limitless already reached the 20th step. Once he ascended another step then he would no longer be fighting spirit bodies.

He would have to defeat other participants!

Chapter 1237 – The Battle Begins

On the first 21 steps of the Divine Seal Altar, one would fight simulation spirit bodies produced by array formations. Starting from the 22nd step and upwards, one would no longer fight simulation spirit bodies but would have to fight and defeat other participants on the same step!

This produced another problem. That was that the first group which was in the lead was stronger overall, thus the opponents they faced were also more powerful.

Thus, if they wished to maintain their status of being in the vanguard, they would have to pay a certain price.

If they were too weak they would be defeated and their ranking here would drop.

A participant was only able to lose five times before they were eliminated; they naturally didn’t wish to waste these chances.

As some people realized this, they began to slow down their pace. If they instantly rushed to the 22nd step and had to directly face Nether Limitless, then that truly wouldn’t be fun.

In fact, only a very small minority of people were able to climb up to the 22nd step.

After such a long time with people continually being eliminated, out of the original 300,000 participants, there was not even a hundred thousand left. But, out of these remaining participants, the overwhelming majority would find it impossible to reach the 22nd step; they would be eliminated before then.

There was no doubt that if one could not reach the 22nd step then they would not pass the semifinals.

The sun fell down over the horizon and the curtain of night rose high up into the skies. The semifinals had now been going on for two days!

Two days, 48 hours, this time period was an extremely great test on every participant’s mental state, physical strength, and endurance.

A massive number of participants weren’t able to withstand the Empyrean pressure, or they weren’t able to defeat the spirit bodies, or they might have even exhausted themselves. But no matter what, if any of these happened, the participant was eliminated.

The disparity grew despairingly large!

The hundred thousand plus participants were like ants crawling up a hill, sparsely distributed all over two sides of the Divine Seal Altar.

As some people were still struggling to reach the 11th step, Nether Limitless had already defeated the spirit body of the 21st step and was beginning to climb to the 22nd level!

Nether Limitless had defeated all spirit bodies of the first 21 steps with relative ease.

No one was surprised by these results. This entire way he had killed all the spirit bodies with unstoppable momentum.

The disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands became increasingly wild and crazy as they shouted out Nether Limitless’s name. The entire arena seemed to echo with the name of ‘Nether Limitless’.

And on the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s side, the disciples were relatively muted.

The Ancient Phoenix Clan wasn’t in too good of a situation.

The Ancient Phoenix Clan, with Lin Ming included, had a total of four disciples entering the semifinals. The weakest of them had already been eliminated.

Xiao Ping’s situation wasn’t looking too good.

Whether he could reach the 22nd step was questionable.

As for those that would likely reach the 22nd step, they were Lin Ming and Yan Littlemoon. But, the truly brutal part of this competition would finally begin upon stepping onto the 22nd step, because at that time, they would have to duel and defeat other participants. That was the true test of strength.

From the 21st step to the 22nd step, Nether Limitless’s climbing speed wasn’t slow.

Without accident, he was the first one to reach the 22nd step!

After mounting the 22nd step, Nether Limitless stood proudly on the flat plains, waiting for other participants to reach him.

He held his katana as he stood against the wind, the aura of a ruler wreathing him.

In that moment, because of Nether Limitless’s existence, many of the other martial artists felt a great pressure on them. They faintly didn’t dare to climb up, because climbing up to the 22nd step was the same as facing Nether Limitless.

“Nether Limitless has already stepped upon the 22nd step, he alone is deterring all other participants… oh! Someone else has climbed up! That is Bloodless Sword!”

The twin hosts loudly shouted. Because the current position of the competition was too high up on the Divine Seal Altar, they had ridden a spirit boat up so that the entire audience could clearly see them.

Bloodless Sword was only a bit behind Nether Limitless. After Nether Limitless reached the 22nd step, Bloodless Sword was right behind him.

The two stood a thousand feet apart, in sharp contrast to each other, neither of them willing to give an inch!

The entire audience felt their breath catch in their throats!

Would it be a battle between kings at the very start! This was simply too amazing!

However, after some time passed, the two still didn’t fight. They simply stood there, waiting.

“It seems… they aren’t planning on fighting so early. The two of them aren’t idiots. Even if Nether Limitless can defeat Bloodless Sword, he will have to pay a great price to do so. It will affect how far he can go afterwards.”

“Yes. The 22nd step should not be the stage of their battle.”

It was clear that Nether Limitless and Bloodless Sword took each other as strong rivals in these semifinals. If the two fought, it would have to be at the 30th step or above.

Thus, a third person finally reached the 22nd step.

This person was a purple-clothed swordsman; his nickname was Purple Blade. He was ranked in the top 300 of the Divine Seal Decree and also first on his own great world!

To be able to be the third to climb to the Divine Seal Altar’s 22nd step, that was enough to prove his strength.

With Purple Blade’s arrival, Bloodless Sword and Nether Limitless still remained unmoving.

They continued to wait.

Slowly, over time, the others gained courage and more and more people climbed up to the 22nd step.

However, there was a 1000 foot null zone around Bloodless Sword and Nether Limitless that no one dared to stand in, lest they find themselves targeted as opponents.

In this way, six hours passed. Several thousand participants had already reached the 22nd level.

Still, no one fought!

All of the powerhouses stopped here, seeming to unanimously agree to restore their strength on the 22nd level.

They waited for more people and weaker people to climb up.

The 22nd level was where the strong would hunt the weak.

And at this time, Lin Ming also climbed towards the 22nd step.

Mixed within the martial artists here, no one would notice him.

The truth was that starting from the tenth step, Lin Ming was able to confirm that someone was targeting him. However, this mysterious existence didn’t push things too far. These spirit bodies always excelled in some area and were able to create a bit of trouble for him. However, truly slaying these spirit bodies didn’t consume too much of Lin Ming’s strength.

Generally speaking, these weren’t deliberate obstacles but rather probing moves.

To probe his bottom line. To probe his talent.

This caused Lin Ming to be increasingly confused. Just what great expert would target him here?

From the start until now, his performance had been only satisfactory at best. Whoever this mysterious figure was, they should have been watching Nether Limitless instead.

Lin Ming’s pace was steady, neither fast nor slow. He finally stepped onto the 22nd step with the third group.

“There are quite a number of people here.”

As Lin Ming climbed up to the 22nd step he hadn’t been able to see what was happening on the step itself. But now that he looked around, he saw around 4000-5000 people. Casually choosing any of them, one could see they were peak powerhouses. Many of them were near the same level as Wu Finalcloud.

There were truly countless masters all around. Those that could climb up to the 22nd step were extreme elites that could close their eyes and become Holy Lord level characters in the future.

These people had carefully chosen where they would stand. Basically, nearly no one stood around those that felt strong in fear of bringing disaster upon themselves. As for those that felt weak, there were many people crowded near them. Everyone was thinking of pinching these weak persimmon-like people to pieces.

When Lin Ming stood on the 22nd step, three people calmly and quietly walked towards him, discreetly surrounding him. Among them, a tall martial artist shaped like a bamboo pole smiled at Lin Ming. However, his smile harbored ill intent.

They judged whether or not someone was weak with two criteria. First was how they felt about this person, and second was how long it took them to climb up to the 22nd level. The later one climbed up, the weaker one was assumed to be.

Although this type of judgment wasn’t necessarily accurate, it was still better than randomly guessing.

After all, nearly all the martial artists present had extremely solid foundations and the Law fluctuations around them were vivid. Moreover, many of these people were hiding their aura so it was difficult for others to judge them based on that alone.

“Brother Long, Brother Fei, it’s quite rare for a little early Divine Sea brat to appear here. How about you let me handle him?” The thin martial artist who was smiling at Lin Ming said to the other two people around him with a true essence sound transmission.

“Hehe, even if he’s at the early Divine Sea, he might not be weak!”

“I certainly understand this, but in equal conditions, wouldn’t it always be easier to deal with someone with a low cultivation than a higher cultivation? Brother Long, Brother Fei, you’re both so strong and this little brother here is so weak. Now that there is actually an opponent who showed up that climbed so slowly and also has a low cultivation, won’t you look after this little brother of yours?”

In order for the thin martial artist to be the one to challenge Lin Ming, he flattered again and again. He simply didn’t know who Lin Ming was. Although the twin hosts had introduced Lin Ming, the participants had all been busy crawling up the Divine Seal Altar at the time. Although they heard of him, they didn’t have an image of him in mind. Even Nether Limitless and Bloodless Sword didn’t know who Lin Ming was.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin is being targeted.”

The Ancient Phoenix Clan’s disciples were all watching Lin Ming. Currently, Lin Ming was the only person of the Ancient Phoenix Clan who had reached the 22nd step.

As for Yan Littlemoon and Xiao Ping, they were still hard at work climbing up the 20th step.

“Humph, they actually think that our Senior-apprentice Brother Lin is easy to bully! I wonder just how strong he is…”

Of the participants that were able to reach the 22nd step, none of them could be underestimated.

“These people think I’m some fat sheep or something.” Lin Ming faintly smiled. “My climbing is relatively slow and my cultivation is also at the early Divine Sea; it’s not strange that I’m being targeted. My cultivation is the lowest of the participants here. This is also good. I was worried that I would have to spend some time looking for an opponent, but now someone delivered themselves straight to me.”

Lin Ming grinned.

As the thin martial artist saw Lin Ming’s happy expression, he frowned. Why was this boy smiling?

Just as he was thinking this, the sound of exploding energy erupted from the far off distance, following by a pitiful scream. Some people had already begun fighting!

The first one to attack was Nether Limitless!

Using the Space Laws, Nether Limitless instantly crossed 100,000 feet, actually arriving right in front of the person furthest from him! With his personality, he instead decided to fight the one furthest from him!

That person was immediately frightened out of his mind.

Just as that person was about to raise his weapon, Nether Limitless’s katana had already cut out, slashing through his protective true essence.

Peng!

That person’s protective true essence shattered and he was sent flying backwards, vomiting blood!

Nether Limitless had kept his hand. This was the real world and those that died would not revive somewhere else. However, the rules of this grand competition forbid intentional murder.

The martial artist who was struck backwards was wrapped up in a layer of purple energy before he even landed.

This purple energy rapidly healed the martial artist’s wounds. At the same time, it also brought him hurtling downwards to the 21st level!

If one lost, they would have to fall down one step!

Nether Limitless’s attack had become a signal. At this time, a massive number of participants struck out with their attacks.

The battle had begun!

Chapter 1238 – The One Who Should Be Sorry Is Me

“Let the battles begin!”

“War has broken out!”

The two twin hosts spiritedly shouted.

At that moment, most of the participants on the 22nd step began to battle each other!

Even though they were all participants that had reached the 22nd step, the disparity in strength between them was enormous!

The strong would only need several breaths of time to kill the weak!

And from the very start, the powerhouses had already chosen their targets. As soon as the battle began, they rushed towards their chosen opponents.

This was basically a battlefield where the strong slaughtered the weak!

Of course, there were some people that misjudged the strength of others. Once they made this fatal mistake, they might find victory difficult or even have kicked a wall and be defeated instead. Although one was strong, with some bad luck, they might encounter someone stronger. They could only embrace their own defeat.

The accuracy of one’s eyesight was also another important standard that dictated whether or not one would be able to pass the 22nd step.

If one had poor eyesight, it was impossible to blame others.

Once the battle began, all of the martial artists in the arena were roused to the extreme.

There was no need to mention martial artists who had fellow disciples of the same sect competing on the Divine Seal Altar. They went all out in shouting.

As for those martial artists that didn’t have any fellow disciples competing or their fellow disciples had already been eliminated, they still shouted as loudly as they could, cheering for the martial artists that originated from their great world.

In short, with these billions of people present and watching these hundred thousand plus geniuses compete, a wild and manic atmosphere spread through the crowd, turning everyone crazy!

For a martial artist that walked down the road of martial arts, they had to encounter all sorts of dangers, slaughtering, arduous and high-intensity training, risking their lives, playing the games of intrigue and betrayal, every martial artist lived under a tremendous pressure. They needed a way to vent!

“Senior-apprentice Brother Dragon One, you can do it!”

Of the four great God Beast Clans, besides Lin Ming, only Dragon One had reached the 22nd step to become one of the 4000-5000 martial artists there.

To be ranked 4000-5000 out of the participants of 1000 great worlds was already an extremely impressive result!

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin is being targeted!”

“Senior Apprentice Brother Lin, be careful!”

The disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan were completely focused on Lin Ming. At this time, on the 22nd step of the Divine Seal Altar, the thin martial artist grasped a long staff as he walked towards Lin Ming. The 22nd step included participants of varying levels; it was possible to bump into some powerful genius!

Qin Xingxuan clenched her fists together. Mu Qianyu held onto her hands; she could also feel the nervousness coming from Qin Xingxuan. This was a battle in the real world. It was possible that one could be severely wounded.

Explosions of energy, horrified screams, whistling winds, muffled sounds, violent shockwaves, all sorts of brutal battle scenes were occurring all over. At the same time, the thin martial artist pointed his staff at Lin Ming’s head, challenge in his eyes!

“Brat, I must say I’m sorry. This is a battlefield where the strong prey on the weak. Weaklings like you are doomed to be stepping stones for masters like me. Because of the rules, I’ll be a bit gentler. For you to fall underneath my hands is also your good luck. At the very least, I won’t severely injure you to the point where it affects your next match.”

The thin martial artist chuckled. Then, he flourished the staff in his hands, his killing intent locked onto Lin Ming. In that instant, he was like a spider hunting an insect caught in his web.

Lin Ming smiled. “The one that should be sorry is me. But, you’re quite lucky that I am your opponent. I also know how things are. I’ll be gentle with you.”

“Brat, you are courting death!” The thin martial artist’s eyes widened. An early Divine Sea boy actually dared to be so arrogant in front of him!

“I’ve changed my mind. In this battle I will break all your bones!”

The thin martial artist shouted out loud and smashed his staff at Lin Ming.

His speed was quick. As his staff came pounding down, it contained the solemn weight of the Earth Laws.

This staff strike was like a falling mountain. Not only was it terrifyingly powerful, but it was nearly impossible to dodge!

All of those that could step onto the 22nd step were top 50 ranked characters of their great world. They were chosen prides of heaven that were coddled since birth. Their moves were naturally unordinary!

Even if the thin martial artist judged himself superior to Lin Ming, he still put his full strength behind this attack. On the 22nd step, there was no truly weak individual, only those that were relatively weaker. If one underestimated their enemy, they would truly suffer a miserable loss.

Within Lin Ming’s pupils, each and every movement of the thin martial artist was clearly reflected.

“Earth Laws, four level Concepts, moreover he has fused them perfectly together. This is the same as before I comprehended the fifth level Concept of Thunder and Fire!”

Lin Ming could instantly see through the strength of this thin martial artist. “Since I’m facing other participants now and not simulation spirit bodies, there shouldn’t be any other tricks played on me.”

Lin Ming languidly brought up the Phoenix Blood Spear and swept it out. He only used the Fire Laws, with the first four level Concepts fused together – Blue Lotus Flame Dance!

Hu hu hu –

Flames burned. As Lin Ming thrust out his spear, a blue lotus bloomed atop it.

Lin Ming’s spear was extremely fast. The brown true essence that the thin martial artist sent out was instantly seared away. All he saw was a beautiful blue lotus appear in front of him before a wave of blue flames rushed towards him.

“What!?”

The thin martial artist was shocked.

He suddenly realized that his opponent was far more formidable than he had guessed!

“Is there a mistake here!? An early Divine Sea martial artist I casually found is actually so strong! His striking power actually surpasses my own!”

The thin man drew backwards. At the same time, a thick brown-colored barrier appeared around him.

Earth Protection Shield!

The Earth Laws were weak in attacking but excelled in defense.

The thin martial artist had absolute confidence in his own Earth Protection Shield!

“What shit luck! I was completely mistaken and actually ran into a master of the Fire Laws! I can only defensively counterattack and try some roundabout tactics. I must withstand the first several waves of his attacks and look for a chance to defeat him. If I don’t save as much energy as possible then I’ll be in danger once I reach the 24th or 25th step!”

The thin martial artist’s thoughts raced. As a martial artist skilled in the Earth Laws, defensively counterattacking was the field he excelled in the most.

However, just as Lin Ming’s blue flames enveloped the thin martial artist’s Earth Protection Shield, an unbelievable scene occurred.

The fire true essence was pervasive, digging through every single weakness it could find. Moreover, it also contained the attribute of endlessness, causing the thin martial artist’s Earth Protection Shield to rapidly disintegrate!

At this speed, the Earth Protection Shield would be completely burnt through in just several breaths of time!

“How is this possible? He clearly only understands the fourth level Concept of the Fire Laws, so how can he burn through my shield!?”

The thin martial artist didn’t even have the time to ponder this. At this time, Lin Ming stepped forwards and appeared right in front of him.

Eight Inner Hidden Gates – four gates open!

The power of several million jins erupted. Lin Ming’s spear came smashing down onto that brown barrier.

Kacha!

It was like a several million jin heavy hammer crashed into a bronze bell. With a terrifying eruption, cracks began appearing in the thin martial artist’s Earth Protection Shield.

“Crack… it cracked!?”

The thin martial artist originally thought that his shield would be able to persist for several more breaths of time, giving him some time to change his methods. But, the shield had already completely collapsed.

Lin Ming took advantage of this opportunity and brought the Phoenix Blood Spear pounding down on the thin martial artist.

The thin martial artist was frightened to the point that his soul nearly evaporated. He wanted to take out a magic tool from his spatial ring but he no longer had enough time.

The Phoenix Blood Spear heavily crashed onto the thin martial artist’s protective true essence.

If even his Earth Protection Shield couldn’t block this attack, then his protective true essence would be even more useless.

With a loud explosive sound, the thin martial artist stuffily humphed as he was sent soaring backwards while coughing out a mouthful of blood.

And in his right hand he had just taken out a golden shield. This golden shield was half the height of a human and shining with a dazzling light; it was a low-grade spirit artifact. However, there was no time to use it.

Lin Ming’s attack had been too fast and too fierce, bringing with it an unstoppable momentum. The thin martial artist simply didn’t have enough time to defend against it. By the time he brought out his shield, he had been sent flying back!

“Fuck this… aren’t you too strong…?”

The thin martial artist opened his mouth to speak but all that came out was gurgled blood. And at this time, a purple energy wrapped around him.

As this purple energy healed his wounds, it also brought him back down to the 21st step.

This meant that he would have to climb up to the 22nd step again. If he climbed up once more, it would consume even more of his strength.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin won!”

“So fierce! He won so easily!”

Seeing Lin Ming win so easily, the disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan were left in a bit of a daze. They originally thought that even if Lin Ming won, he would still take some time to do so.

“Too amazing! He hasn’t met those abnormal freaks yet. That staff-wielding martial artist looks like a frail stick; how could he ever compare with our Senior-apprentice Brother Lin?”

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin is awesome! Too fierce!”

The disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan were all overjoyed. They naturally didn’t think that they would be weaker than others. No one wanted to destroy their own hopes and ambitions, because their power was correlated with their own faith. Even if they had such thoughts, they would never voice them out loud.

“Brother! Damnit!”

Not too far from Lin Ming, those two fellows that had surrounded Lin Ming with the thin fellow were glaring at him. They had clearly been his companions.

One of them had already finished his battle. If he was able to finish his battle so quickly, he naturally wasn’t one of the weaker participants.

That martial artist stared at Lin Ming, fear flashing in his eyes.

Lin Ming thought little of it. If this fellow wanted to fight then he would welcome it, but it seemed that he lacked the courage to do so.

That person finally didn’t say anything more. He instead began climbing up to the 23rd step.

At this time, on the 22nd step, there were still many others ferociously fighting. In a one on one battle, no one was allowed to interfere.

Many of the people fighting didn’t have too great of a strength disparity with their opponents. If they fought like this, it was extremely taxing. Even if they won they would have to consume an immense amount of strength. They would have to stay on the 22nd step for some time to restore themselves.

The truth was that the competition taking place on the Divine Seal Altar did not forbid the use of recovery pills. But, the medicinal efficacy contained within recovery pills was not completely consistent with a martial artist’s own true essence. Using three or four was fine, but if one used too many then that would cause their true essence to become impure and also affect their combat strength.

Many people were like Lin Ming and ended their battles early. They leapt onto the cliff and began to climb to the 23rd step. The further they went, the stronger their opponents would be.

Lin Ming leapt. His body flew up like a bird, crossing hundreds of feet at a time.

On the 23rd level, the pressure increased once more. But, those people that were able to conclude their battles early were masters amongst masters. Even in the face of this pressure, the speed at which they climbed was still fast.

Chapter 1239 – Crimson Strifecloud’s Daughter

As Lin Ming started to climb up to the 23rd step, the Ancient Dragon Clan’s Dragon One was defeated!

The one who defeated Dragon One was a small and ordinary young man with nothing special about him. But, in front of him, Dragon One still suffered a miserable loss.

It could only be said that there were far too many masters in the semifinals.

With Dragon One sent back to the 21st step, the result was that he had fallen behind Yan Littlemoon.

“The Dragon Clan’s Dragon One was defeated!”

Fairy Feng said from beside Huo Violentstone.

“Mm… I saw.” Huo Violentstone said. He nonchalantly turned his head to look at the person responsible for the Ancient Dragon Clan disciples here, Laughing Dragon.

At this time, Laughing Dragon couldn’t laugh at all.

As for Huo Violentstone, he didn’t gloat over this. And he definitely didn’t let Lin Ming’s success go to his head. This was because the intensity of the semifinals was far higher than the preliminaries’. The difficult stages were still to come. There was no way for Huo Violentstone to feel relaxed.

As Laughing Dragon felt Huo Violentstone’s gaze on him, he said, “Hehe, Old Huo, it looks like the four God Beast Clans only have your Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Lin Ming remaining. It seems Dragon One will at most be able to climb to the 23rd or 24th step before he is defeated. It’s impossible for him to go any further. As for your Yan Littlemoon, she’s in the same position. Dragon Two, Dragon Three, Xiao Ping, and also the disciples of the Kirin Clan and Roc Clan will be much worse. None of them should be able to pass these semifinals.”

To pass the semifinals was the same as entering the top 10,000 ranks of the Divine Realm. This was truly far too difficult a task for Dragon One, Yan Littlemoon, and the others.

“Lin Ming will definitely enter the finals!” Huo Violentstone confidently said.

“Haha, I hope so. Although I have to admit that I’m feeling a bit sour over this, I still hope that the four God Beast Clans will do well.”

The four God Beast Clans competed and plotted against each other in peaceful times. But when facing a mutual enemy, they still banded together to protect their interests.

No matter which clan it was, it was a wonderful occasion to produce a strong powerhouse. Of course, having this powerhouse appear in their own clan was always the best.

Huo Violentstone didn’t say anything else. Instead, he looked towards the Divine Seal Altar and Lin Ming. His normally loud and boisterous manner was completely restrained and his expression was a bit solemn.

In these semifinals, one step could lead to life and one step could lead to death!

This was because the disparity in strength of the martial artists could be extremely great. In this competition, if someone were to easily defeat someone on one step, they could themselves be easily defeated on the next step!

Thus, each fight was not easy at all.

And at this time, more and more martial artists climbed up to the 23rd step.

This was the same situation as before. The martial artists that climbed to the 23rd step waited for some more martial artists to ascend.

Those martial artists that first mounted the 23rd step had a great advantage over the others.

This was because they were able to meditate on the Divine Seal Altar, eliminating the pill impurities within their bodies as they restored themselves to a better combat state.

Soon, 3000 people gathered on the 23rd step.

At this time, it was no longer Nether Limitless signaling the start of the battle. Rather, anyone that decided on who they wanted to fight would instantly begin.

Someone began running towards Lin Ming.

This person was a tall and explosive young woman. Her steps were lithe and she was as dexterous as a cat.

She had deep crimson red hair, and her skin was not white like jade, but rather a healthy and sexual wheat color. She wore tight-fitting leather armor. It was unknown what vicious beast this leather came from, the beautiful patterns were naturally engraved into it. Although the vicious beast had died a long time ago, these patterns still emitted faint fluctuations of the Laws. This was an indication that the vicious beast had been of a very high level.

The tight leather armor was extremely short, revealing her smooth and flat belly and intoxicating navel. It also served to accentuate and bring out her tall and busty twin peaks.

On the lower half of her body, she wore a very tight skirt that was made of similar leather. This tight skirt completely followed the curves of her round thighs.

Her weapon was a sickle blade. The blade edge shined with a cold light, perfectly fusing together with the deadly and exaggerated curvature of the weapon.

The young woman smiled as she looked at Lin Ming, bringing up the sickle blade in her hands.

“This woman…” Lin Ming’s eyebrows shot up. The feeling she gave off was that of a wild leopard: beautiful, vigorous, and yet filled with an explosive force and exotic danger.

This woman was far fiercer than the last martial artist he had faced.

In the arena, the martial artists of the Ancient Phoenix Clan also noticed her.

“That woman… seems a bit familiar.” Palace Master Lian Zhen said from beside Huo Violentstone.

Huo Violentstone was stunned for some time. Then, he ruefully smiled and said, “If I’m not wrong then she is the daughter of Crimson Strifecloud, the current Crimson Dragon Envoy of the Crimson Light Holy Lands. Her mother should be the daughter of our Ancient Phoenix Clan’s last patriarch, the little princess that had a perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline. In the past, there were countless pursuers that chased after her, but in the end she was married off to Crimson Strifecloud.”

As Huo Violentstone spoke to here, he deeply sighed. Once upon a time, he too had been one of the little princess’ suitors.

In truth, although the Ancient Phoenix Clan had married the little princess off to Crimson Strifecloud because of political reasons, it was by no means wronging or harming her. Crimson Strifecloud had been an extraordinary character. With the little princess’ background, her beauty, her phoenix bloodline, and her primordial yin, Crimson Strifecloud would not have treated her coldly.

Even so, Huo Violentstone had always kept this matter in his heart. In his opinion, marrying someone off in exchange for benefits was the sorrow of the weak.

“No wonder. She really does look like her mother. It’s just that her skin color and hair color are different. That coloring should have been inherited from her father!” Lian Zhen nodded, his expression complex. He didn’t think that one day, Lin Ming would battle the daughter of the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s little princess!

“Not only is her coloring that of her father, but her disposition is also her father’s. I can see none of her mother’s virtuous grace and gentleness on her.”

The past Crimson Strifecloud had bronze skin and a full head of red hair. His character was well known to all.

And now, his daughter was also the same.

“You’re the one called Lin Ming? I know you!” The red-haired woman said. She actually knew who Lin Ming was.

“And you are?” Lin Ming was a bit startled. He wasn’t like Nether Limitless, who had rushed straight up to the top 20 ranks of the Divine Seal Decree, causing everyone in the Divine Realm to know of him. Rather, he had finished the preliminaries ranked around 10,000 on the Divine Seal Decree. That shouldn’t be a level where everyone would know of him.

“My father is Crimson Strifecloud. I heard Father say that you defeated the spirit body he left behind in the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Illusionary God Combat Array. Is that right?”

Lin Ming froze for a moment; this was actually Crimson Strifecloud’s daughter!

Wasn’t this a bit too theatrical?

He had defeated Crimson Strifecloud and now his daughter had appeared!

From the sound of it, this woman had deliberately come here for him?

He carefully looked at this young woman in front of him. He could feel the aura of the Ancient Phoenix Clan from her, and could also feel that she had the Ancient Phoenix bloodline. Of course, her bloodline density was much lighter than Yan Littlemoon’s. This was the shortcoming of transplanting the Ancient Phoenix bloodline. As long as one continued reproducing down generations, the bloodline would become increasingly pale, slowly fading until it finally disappeared.

“Your mother is the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s little princess?” When Lin Ming was at Fire Spirit Star, he had also heard the stories.

“That’s right. But my mother is a weak woman. Luckily, I am not like her.”

As the red-haired woman spoke, she stroked the edge of her sickle blade with a single finger before stretching out her tongue and licking the blade. This was an extremely wild and barbaric action, one filled with sex appeal.

Lin Ming frowned. He didn’t like listening to this woman’s words, as if she were disparaging and looking down upon her own mother. “You and I can be considered as having come from the same roots. Are you planning on being my enemy?”

In Lin Ming’s opinion, if this red-haired woman dared to challenge him, she naturally had the confidence that she could win. Her goal was to use him as a stepping stone to reach the 24th step. For two geniuses who came from the same roots to step on each other to reach the next step, this was a bit too dramatic.

The red-haired young woman laughed. “Same roots? You wish. I come from the Crimson Light Holy Lands, a Great World King level influence. As for you, you are only from the Ancient Phoenix Clan, a mere ordinary Holy Land. How could you say we come from the same roots?

“The reason I will fight is not because I think highly of you, but because you managed to defeat the spirit body phantom that my father left behind within the Illusionary God Combat Array during his youth. Although you defeated that phantom spirit body, the truth is that it was simply unable to reproduce the true strength of my father during his youth. Moreover, that matter leaves me very uncomfortable. Aren’t you just a common martial artist? How could my father possibly lose to you? Thus, I must defeat you.”

The red-haired woman said as if this was all a matter of course. Her words carried with them an arrogant tone. This was a natural feeling of superiority that one was born with. In fact, many people of Great World King Holy Lands looked down at those from ordinary Holy Lands. In particular, someone like Lin Ming was even more of a commoner than the rest. He was simply the weed amongst the grass.

“I see.” Lin Ming said, thinking this whole situation a bit funny.

“To think that you can still smile, how interesting. It’s as if you don’t realize what sort of situation you’re in. Soon, you won’t be able to smile anymore. Before our battle begins, let me tell you something. My talent is the greatest of my father’s 100 children, and I am far stronger than he was in his youth! Finally, let me tell you my name so that you may carve it down in your mind. My name is Crimson Wishjade.”

For Crimson Wishjade to encounter Lin Ming here, it couldn’t be called a stroke of fate. Rather, for a peak influence like the Crimson Light Holy Lands, they naturally wouldn’t allow their most outstanding disciples to miss out on the First Martial Meeting. Crimson Wishjade was originally born too early to enter the First Martial Meeting. However, she entered a time enchantment and by adjusting the flow of time, she was able to pass several hundred years in just several years.

“If that’s the case, then let me teach you a lesson on behalf of your mother!” Lin Ming extracted the Phoenix Blood Spear. He had always felt a trace of sympathy towards the little princess who was forced to marry into the Crimson Light Holy Lands because of her clan’s politics. And now, the little princess’ daughter actually took the Crimson Light Holy Lands as her honor and the Ancient Phoenix Clan as her shame. This left him with a bad taste in his mouth.

“Teach me? Heh! It seems you want to die.”

Crimson Wishjade revealed a thick murderous intent. And in the audience, a tall middle-aged man with a full head of red hair was watching this battle.

He was Crimson Strifecloud.

“Little Jade, you really are giving me a headache here. Your character will cause you to suffer a loss sooner or later… I already warned you that Lin Ming isn’t simple at all, and I can’t even tell how this battle will end up. I don’t think that your chances of winning are even 50% and yet you are actually so full of confidence…” Crimson Strifecloud sighed.

Currently, Lin Ming was countless times more powerful than he was in the past when he had rushed through the Illusionary God Combat Array.

However, Lin Ming’s opponent was also powerful. In the past, the Crimson Strifecloud within the Illusionary God Combat Array was only at the eighth stage of Life Destruction, but the current Crimson Wishjade was at the late Divine Sea realm. This was also the reason that she was so confident. If a late Divine Sea martial artist couldn’t defeat an early Divine Sea martial artist, then that was truly shameful!

Chapter 1240 – Absolute Suppression

“Although you are only from an ordinary Holy Land background, I will fight you with everything I have from the start. I will carve into your heart the glory of the Crimson Light Holy Lands. I will defeat you with my greatest strength so that you can understand the disparity between us!”

As Crimson Wishjade spoke, red scales began to appear on her face. Her hair grew longer and even her body grew taller.

Her long and slender legs filled with strength. Once this strength erupted, even a piece of divine iron that could forge a spirit artifact would be easily kicked in half.

“This is the Crimson Light Family’s unique bloodline – Scorching Blood!” Huo Violentstone grimly said from within the audience.

In the Divine Realm, there were many families that had their own bloodline inheritances.

The Scorching Blood bloodline, capable of making one’s blood burn like fire. Although it was inferior to the Ancient Phoenix bloodline in quality, it won in density. The Scorching Blood bloodline could be inherited even without reducing the density. Through screening over numerous generations, their bloodline became stronger. This was a seal carved into their very genetics that could not be changed!

As for the Ancient Phoenix Clan, their phoenix bloodline was only transplanted after birth. The degree of their hereditary transmission was much lower and the amount of phoenix blood they could transplant was also lower, because high quality phoenix blood was simply far too precious.

Hu – !

Crimson Wishjade’s body ignited with monstrous waves of flames. The Crimson Light World King Family also focused on fire-based abilities. This was the reason Crimson Strifecloud married the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s little princess in the past.

“Little Jade… although her words are a bit too arrogant, she does have the capabilities to fight him. At least she isn’t blindly underestimating him. Maybe she can win…” In the audience, Crimson Strifecloud whispered to himself. He was aware of Crimson Wishjade’s complete strength. But, as for where the limits of Lin Ming’s strength lay, he didn’t know at all. Victory or defeat would depend on how much Lin Ming’s strength surpassed his imagination.

At this time, on the 23rd step of the Divine Seal Altar, Lin Ming was facing Crimson Wishjade, who was fully displaying her Scorching Blood bloodline. He faintly smiled and said, “You want me to understand the disparity between us, but… I fear that you may be mistaken in just who is weaker and who is stronger.”

“What shameless boasting! A disciple of an ordinary Holy Land is actually so arrogant! I will show you just what happens to people like you!”

Omm –

Crimson Wishjade raised her sickle blade up high. At this time, the phantom of an immortal firelord appeared behind her. The power of scorching blood swelled up as a conflagration of flames rose upwards, galloping forwards like a rushing army. Raging flames spread throughout the surrounding area!

On the relatively quiet 23rd step, such an explosive battle was extremely eye-catching!

It had to be known that the entire 23rd step was covered with an immense Empyrean pressure. The weaker martial artists weren’t even able to display 30% of their full strength; it was impossible for them to release such a massive attack!

“Crimson Flame Domain! This is the Crimson Flame Domain!”

There were many types of fire domains. The one that Crimson Wishjade used now was the Crimson Flame Domain. It was much stronger than the Blue Lotus Domain. This sort of domain was intrinsically fused into the Scorching Blood bloodline of the Crimson Light Family.

As monstrous flames burned into the skies, the entire audience and all the martial artists on the 23rd step turned towards them.

This was a battle between two great powerhouses!

“Mm? Someone is using the Crimson Flame Domain, and it’s a woman too… I think she should be the extreme genius being raised in the Crimson Light Holy Lands and also the peak master of the Crimson Light World. Her opponent is… eh? Her opponent is Lin Ming!”

On the spirit boat floating in front of the Divine Seal Altar, the two hosts shouted out with gusto. They had looked over the information of all the participants here, thus they knew most of the geniuses and where they came from.

They had originally no longer bothered with Lin Ming, but now, Lin Ming caught their attention once again. Many of those in the audience also noticed them.

Then, Crimson Wishjade attacked. Her sickle blade slashed down!

In that moment, Crimson Wishjade seemed to fuse with the phantom firelord behind her. The Crimson Flame Domain expanded outwards, enveloping the entire battlefield.

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and swept it outwards!

Blue Lotus Flame Dance!

In a battle of Fire Laws against Fire Laws, a towering blue lotus rose into the air. A brilliant blue beam of fire shot straight out!

However, as this beam of fire hurtled towards Crimson Wishjade’s blade light, the beam of fire suddenly slowed down as if there was a tremendous amount of resistance!

On the other hand, Crimson Wishjade’s sickle blade seemed to speed up with overwhelming momentum, making one’s heart race.

“My Crimson Flame Domain can gather all fire element heaven and earth origin energy without needing to use any true essence. It is capable of ruling over all flames in this world. For you to use the Fire Laws to battle with me is simply seeking your own death.”

Crimson Wishjade coldly sneered. Her saber light suddenly split into thousands of little wisps. Every wisp of saber light was like a petal of a red lotus. For a time, the entire sky was flooded with countless red lotus petals; it was an incomparably gorgeous scene!

“Since that’s what you think, I will use the Fire Laws to defeat you!”

Lin Ming smiled. In terms of the Fire Laws, regardless of comprehension or utilization, he had never felt weak, especially against his peers. Against them, he was fully confident that he was king!

Crimson Wishjade had the Crimson Flame Domain, but as for him, he had a transcendent divine might!

Moreover, Lin Ming had already comprehended the fifth level Concept of the Fire Laws – Virtual Fire! This was a boundary that ordinary geniuses could never hope to match.

As Crimson Wishjade rushed towards him, from within Lin Ming’s inner world, the Heretical God Seedling indignantly spread out. The power of fire rushed out like a tide; the Heretical God Force opened to the limit!

In that instant, on top of Lin Ming’s spear light, the phantom of a divine tree seemed to appear. This phantom only appeared for a brief instant, but in this instant, Lin Ming’s spear light became several times sharper!

Even the Fire Laws between the heavens and earth seemed to be influenced by this and twist around. The fire origin energy around Crimson Wishjade that rushed towards him like a surging  tide was suddenly cut apart and controlled by Lin Ming!

Peng peng peng!

In the split moment when the divine tree phantom appeared, those thousands of red lotus petals that fluttered in the skies were all destroyed as if they had been scorched to nothing!

Within the Crimson Flame Domain, all of the wild fire origin energy there was controlled by Lin Ming!

What?

Crimson Wishjade was shocked. She had never encountered such a scene before!

In a battle of martial artists that used the same Laws, the one that was able to use their comprehension of Laws to control the heaven and earth origin energy could directly suppress the other.

Crimson Wishjade’s perception was extremely high to begin with, and she had also inherited the Crimson Light Family’s Burning Blood bloodline as well as phoenix bloodline from her mother who possessed the perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline. To her, the Ancient Phoenix bloodline was the finishing touch upon her own bloodline. After comprehending the Crimson Flame Domain, she was even more confident that no one could challenge her in the aspect of Fire Laws!

But now, she was the one being suppressed by Lin Ming.

“Crimson Flame Domain, completely open!”

In that instant, brilliant golden rays of light shot out from all over Crimson Wishjade’s body. The skin of her body turned a deep fiery red.

She had activated her Scorching Blood bloodline to the limit.

As Lin Ming faced Crimson Wishjade giving her all, he merely swept his spear out.

Crack!

Lin Ming shouted out loud. All of the surrounding fire origin energy was swept up by Lin Ming’s spear. A giant tear formed in Crimson Wishjade’s Crimson Flame Domain!

Lin Ming strode into the Crimson Flame Domain. At this time, he was like a war god descended to the world, unstoppable and indestructible. As he walked forwards, every single bit of fire origin energy gathered to him. There was even some fire origin energy that manifested into spiritual flame beings. There were fire crows, fire kirins, fire wolves, and so forth. All of these beings surrounded Lin Ming, bowing to him, worshipping him! This was a phenomenon that occurred when one comprehended the Fire Laws to an exceedingly high degree, capable of ruling over the world!

Faintly, behind Lin Ming, the phantom of a divine tree appeared. It took root in the endless inferno of flames. It rose higher and higher, growing into a towering tree!

Within this sea of flames, a divine tree was born!

This phenomenon was seen by all present, but no one knew what it meant.

“This is…”

Within the Divine Seal Altar, the gray-robed old man was watching all of this happen. He paid particular attention to this divine tree.

The gray-robed old man was extremely interested in Lin Ming. He didn’t think it was strange if Lin Ming knew a transcendent divine might, but the key point was that he didn’t know of the Heretical God Force.

The Divine Realm had existed for countless billions of years. Before ancient times, there were even more ancient times, continuing all the way back until the creation of the universe!

In all this time, there was an untold number of Empyreans that had appeared. And among these Empyreans, many of them had created their own transcendent divine might.

Of these transcendent divine mights, 90% of them had been lost to time. But, there was a small number that had been preserved. These were located all over the Divine Realm or in some unknown ancient mystic realms.

Sometimes, these mystic realms weren’t dangerous at all. After all, far too long a time had passed. Any powerful array formation would have weakened or even vanished, and any formidable guardian beast would have exhausted its lifespan and died.

To obtain the transcendent divine mights located in these mystic realms, it depended on one’s luck and not strength.

The gray-robed old man had an extraordinary degree of experience, but even he didn’t know every single transcendent divine might.

There was no one that could accomplish such a feat.

Moreover, many transcendent divine mights had special peculiarities. For instance, the Heretical God Force was not an offensive transcendent divine might but an auxiliary arcane skill. Even if one saw the towering divine tree that rose in the boundless sea of fire behind Lin Ming, it was impossible for them to judge whether or not this phenomenon originated from an arcane skill, cultivation method, special physique, or bloodline.

“How interesting. I wonder just where this young boy comes from.”

The gray-robed old man muttered to himself. “This little baby girl can’t even force out his true strength. Luckily, there are some other nice talented brats ahead of her. If they fight Lin Ming, I should be able to see some more.”

At this time, on the 23rd step of the Divine Seal Altar, Lin Ming had already rushed towards the front of Crimson Wishjade. All of the surrounding fire origin energy was swept up around him, all of it under his control.

“You!”

Crimson Wishjade’s pupils shrank. Her Crimson Flame Domain had actually been ripped open! Not just that, but within her own domain, he was actually able to grasp complete control of the Fire Laws and suppress her!

“Lin Ming is actually this strong!?”

In the audience, Huo Violentstone was extremely shocked. Even though Crimson Wishjade had such immense talent, she was still completely surpassed in a battle against Lin Ming. This was something he had never imagined from the start. After all, they hadn’t seen Lin Ming’s performance in the preliminaries, they had only seen the change in his merit points.

One’s merit points and one’s true combat strength were two different matters. Otherwise, the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting would have been simply settled with a ranking of merit points.

Lin Ming ignored this all. From between his eyebrows, the blood of the Ancient Phoenix burnt, emitting a flaming golden light!

Since he said he would use the Fire Laws to defeat Crimson Wishjade, he naturally wouldn’t use his body transformation technique or the Thunder Laws. In Lin Ming’s view, Crimson Wishjade was merely a peak talent of a Great World King Holy Land. As for the Crimson Light Holy Lands, they were only from a third-order world. Crimson Wishjade likely couldn’t even compare with Wu Finalcloud, who came from the True Martial Great World, a second-order world.

Chapter 1242 – Rapid Drop In Numbers

Lin Ming and Crimson Wishjade’s battle was the most intense fight to erupt on the Divine Seal Altar so far, and also the highest level showdown. Everyone was watching it.

As for Nether Limitless and Bloodless Sword, after they defeated their opponents they didn’t immediately climb up to the 24th step. Instead, they stopped for a moment to look at Lin Ming’s battle.

“Interesting.” Nether Limitless smiled. Then, he turned and began to climb up.

Bloodless Sword also began climbing up to the 24th step. In their eyes, Lin Ming was only worth paying some attention too, but he wasn’t a great worry.

As for the other participants, they weren’t able to remain so calm. The pressure that Lin Ming placed on them was far too great.

“What a terrifying fellow!”

“He’s impossible to defeat!”

“Originally just characters like Nether Limitless, Bloodless Sword, and Dragon Fang were able to leave us gasping for breath, but now this dark horse Lin Ming has come from nowhere. How can we still live? If any of us aren’t careful then we’ll be ruined!”

Of the martial artists present, 99% of them didn’t have any confidence in facing Lin Ming!

“This fellow is quite skilled. Isn’t he a participant from your True Martial World? He doesn’t seem like a disciple from your True Martial Holy Lands.”

Near Wu Finalcloud, a black-clothed swordsman with vibrant green hair said.

“He isn’t.” Wu Finalcloud frowned. He didn’t like to speak about Lin Ming; to him, Lin Ming was his shame.

“Indeed. Well, if such a person existed in your True Martial Holy Lands I would have known about him already. Brother Finalcloud, aren’t you the big brother of the True Martial World? While that Dragon Fang is a character that can’t be provoked, it seems even this Lin Ming is going to outshine you soon. Do you plan on doing anything?”

In the eyes of that green-haired youth, Crimson Wishjade was simply a martial artist from a third-order world; she was naturally weaker than Wu Finalcloud. Wu Finalcloud and Lin Ming should be able to fight for some time.

But, what he didn’t know was that Wu Finalcloud had already been defeated by Lin Ming. This battle had occurred in the Divine Dream World and it couldn’t be seen by outsiders.

“Who cares? If someone overshadows me, then I’m supposed to challenge them? Do I look like an idiot to you?” Wu Finalcloud responded.

The green-haired martial artist thought that this response didn’t suit the normally haughty and arrogant Wu Finalcloud. “Are you admitting that you aren’t his match?”

The green-haired martial artist thought something was a bit strange. In his opinion, it was natural for Wu Finalcloud to avoid Dragon Fang. As for Lin Ming, although he was able to defeat Crimson Wishjade, they should still be on par with each other. But now that he listened to Wu Finalcloud’s words, it seemed that he may have lost to Lin Ming before!

“I don’t need you to worry about me. You do what you want; it’s not my problem.”

Wu Finalcloud no longer spoke. He turned around to climb up the 24th step. He wasn’t an idiot. If he knew that he would be suppressed by Lin Ming, why would he bother making such jokes? He believed that in that fight just now, Lin Ming hadn’t even displayed half of his strength.

Wu Finalcloud even had a creeping suspicion that if Lin Ming were to fight with Dragon Fang, Bloodless Sword, or so on, it was still a mystery who was weaker and who was stronger.

Against such a freak, anyone that encountered him would be in for a bout of bad luck. He couldn’t avoid him fast enough.

As for the green-haired swordsman that just spoke, Wu Finalcloud hoped that he would bump into Lin Ming and experience some suffering himself. This was simply how people were. After suffering a loss and also knowing that he wouldn’t be able to win in the future, he also hoped that others would do what he did and eat defeat.

Wu Finalcloud climbed towards the 24th level. With his strength, as long as he didn’t encounter the freakish powerhouses here and steadily continued upwards then it wouldn’t be a problem for him to pass the semifinals.

“Amazing! After being low-key for such a long time, Lin Ming actually defeated Crimson Wishjade in a single fell swoop! Crimson Wishjade is amongst the greatest geniuses to appear in the Crimson Light Holy Lands! Moreover, he also easily defeated her! It seems that Lin Ming had been intentionally saving his strength!”

The two twin hosts shouted from above a spirit boat. They certainly didn’t know that Lin Ming was being deliberately probed by someone as he fought the spirit bodies.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin has defeated the highest ranking martial artist from the Crimson Light Holy Lands? Moreover… he did it so easily?”

On the 21st step, Yan Littlemoon was shocked as she heard this. Because of where she was, she hadn’t been able to see Lin Ming’s battle at all.

The Crimson Light Holy Lands was the ruling power of the Crimson Light World, the great world where the Ancient Phoenix Clan Headquarters were located. To the Ancient Phoenix Clan, that untouchable mountain known as the Crimson Light Holy Lands had actually been defeated by Lin Ming.

Yan Littlemoon felt this was a bit unbelievable. All of the disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan began loudly cheering in unison.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin is too dashing!”

“Haha! Well fought! This feels great!”

“Our Ancient Phoenix Clan can finally hold our heads up with pride!”

The disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan were all extremely excited. The Crimson Light Holy Lands had always been a pressure on them, and none of them had ever even thought about pushing back. But now, Lin Ming had done so, and he had done so amazingly.

He had truly and honestly swept away the Crimson Light Holy Lands! How could they not feel amazing about such domineering aggression?

On the 24th step, the number of martial artists in the first group had been reduced by over half again. Now there were only around 1600 people.

Even after meditating and resting for two hours, only another 200-300 more people climbed up.

From the start, those that won in the first group were able to climb up to the 24th step. But, these waves of participants behind them, even if they won their matches, weren’t necessarily able to climb up to the 24th step.

After being defeated by powerhouses on the 23rd step, some people simply weren’t able to continue. Although the Divine Seal Altar’s artifact spirit had healed their wounds, they still weren’t able to restore their exhausted energy.

Even though one could be defeated four times, just a single defeat would have a very great influence on their following results.

On the 24th step, Lin Ming sat down. The area a thousand feet around him had actually become empty!

The people nearby were all staring at him with some fear in their eyes.

This was a type of treatment that only universally acknowledged monstrous geniuses like Dragon Fang and Bloodless Sword received!

Now, with the strength Lin Ming had displayed so far, he had been recognized as a top 10 master of these semifinals.

“Hahaha! No one is daring to approach Senior-apprentice Brother Lin!”

“All those losers that were stupid enough to think of stirring up some trouble with Senior-apprentice Brother Lin Ming are now hiding from him! How fierce!”

“Too fierce! There are only 10 people in total that can enjoy such treatment! But among them, Senior-apprentice Brother Lin has the lowest cultivation!”

To sit alone on the Divine Seal Altar and have everyone give him a thousand foot berth, that was indeed the loneliness of a top master.

The disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan all began to cheer out loud for Lin Ming. The battles of the 24th step were about to begin!

There were now just under 1900 martial artists on the 24th step. The ones that were still down under basically wouldn’t be able to climb up anymore.

Once these 1900 people fought, less than half of them would be able to climb to the 25th step!

Lin Ming stood up. The martial artists around him immediately tensed, their minds tightening as if they stood on needles. There were even some martial artists that began stepping backwards. And at this time, Lin Ming moved. His speed was extremely fast. With a single step, he arrived in front of a small martial artist.

This martial artist only came up to Lin Ming’s chest. Compared to a normal man, he was a bit shorter. There was some fur on his face, making him seem like a short-furred monkey. This was clearly the manifestation of some special bloodline trait.

As this monkey-like martial artist saw Lin Ming, he nearly bit his tongue in surprise.

“Shit, how can my luck be so bad!?”

He had been so far away and yet this evil star had eyed him!

He had wanted to run further away. The problem was that there was even more freakish monsters that occupied this step and he would eventually have to bump into one or two of them. Especially that Nether Limitless. That fellow completely didn’t read the mood, instead randomly fighting someone far or near with a seemingly random pattern.

If one was chosen by those dozen plus peak powerhouses, they could only blame their bad luck.

“Hold on! Great hero, stay your hand!”

Just as Lin Ming rushed forwards, that little fellow shouted out. His voice was sharp and extremely grating, similar to the howling of a monkey.

“Mm?” Lin Ming slowed down.

The little fellow sadly laughed for a moment before saying, “You don’t need to do anything. I’ll make my own exit out of here.”

The little fellow immediately turned around and ran to the cliff of the 24th step. Without further ado, he jumped straight down.

As Lin Ming saw this, he was left speechless.

Was this okay?

The truth was that admitting defeat of one’s own volition was much better than being beaten up and defeated.

The Divine Seal Altar was a protracted war. Regardless of it being climbing to the next step or battling other participants, all of this consumed a massive amount of strength.

Moreover, this exhaustion would accumulate over time at a perpetually increasing rate!

There were many people that were mainly eliminated not because they were defeated five times or because they couldn’t withstand the Empyrean pressure. Rather, they squandered their strength, and after exhausting their strength, they took pills to recover. Because this caused the true essence within their bodies to become chaotic and mixed up, they weren’t able to display even half of their strength. They were thus naturally eliminated due to this.

So, on the 24th step, Lin Ming won by default!

On the 25th step, his opponent admitted defeat once more!

The ones that admitted defeat were not just Lin Ming’s opponents, but also Nether Limitless, Bloodless Sword, and Dragon Fang’s opponents!

The number of participants decreased again. On the 26th step, there were less than 500 people remaining!

Of the original 300,000 people only this many were left over!

However, not all of these 500 people were able to pass.

In the semifinal region where Lin Ming was located, only 300 people would be able to finally pass the semifinals.

These 300 people would be selected from whomever was able to climb the highest. Those that reached a similar level would be prioritized based on how much time they took. Thus, for many participants, even though they knew they might step on some mine if they followed the first group, they still grit their teeth and continued upwards with them, all in order to save time.

For ones like Yan Littlemoon and Dragon One, although they hadn’t yet been eliminated, it was impossible for them to pass the semifinals.

Without a doubt, 99% of those that passed these semifinals would originate from these 500 people. As for the others, they might have encountered a storm of bad luck that made them bump into monstrous geniuses again and again. Even so, they would continue climbing later until they reached the top 300.

On the 26th step, the pressure rose once again.

The rivers of heaven and earth origin energy had become much thinner on the 26th step. But, the Empyrean pressure had increased to the point that it was like a continuous waterfall crashing down on them!

Moreover, the higher one went, the stronger the pressure was.

“How… how… how is this possible, I… I can’t climb up any more!?”

Half-way to the 26th step, a martial artist had reached his limit. Every step he took was extremely difficult.

“All this time, I’ve defeated every opponent, and I’ve also maintained my position in the first group, but I… I actually can’t climb up any more…”

The martial artist grit his teeth and desperately struggled to stay on. However, the massive pressure continued to crash into him. Finally, his hands slipped and he fell from that massive cliff.

This was the first time that someone from the first group who had maintained complete victory over his opponents had dropped down because they couldn’t withstand the Empyrean pressure!

This meant that after every step, more than half of them would be eliminated!

For over half of the remaining participants to be eliminated with every step, this rate of elimination was far too terrifying. Before long, the number of people remaining on the Divine Seal Altar would be able to be counted with one’s hands.

At that time, only a few powerhouses such as Lin Ming, Nether Limitless, Bloodless Sword, and Dragon Fang would be remaining!

That would be the true battle of the Divine Seal Altar; it was unavoidable!

Chapter 1246 – Lin Ming VS Nether Limitless

“Is something wrong with Purple Blade?”

“He’s randomly climbing about; he’s not going in a straight line at all!”

In the audience, many people noticed something strange happening with Purple Blade. He had already been left far behind by the other four people.

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother, you can do it, put your back into it!”

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother, don’t give up!”

The disciples from Purple Blade’s Holy Lands were all cheering for him. However, he wasn’t able to hear their cheers at all.

His sweat had already covered his eyes and his consciousness had gone completely blurry.

“Blood… my hands are holding blood? Am I crawling in a sea of blood… the end, I cannot see the end…” Every time Purple Blade took a step up, he felt as if he were grasping a mountain of swords. His palms and legs ached with a cutting pain.

His exhaustion had reached the limit. He felt as if he weighed 10,000 jins, and the pain was so intense he thought he would die at any moment.

With his final fading will, he forcefully grasped what he could. But, he no longer had the strength to take another step up.

Purple Blade had already lost consciousness. At the moment when the flow of energy within his body stopped, he was no longer able to withstand the pressure on the 31st step. The body of an essence gathering system martial artist was frail to begin with, and without the protection of energy around him, he simply wasn’t able to withstand the impact.

Blood rained down and Purple Blade fell from the cliff.

An aura of energy caught him, cradling him; he had been defeated!

“Purple Blade has lost! He was the third to reach the 22nd step, and yet he actually wasn’t able to reach the 30th step!”

“Heavens, this is far too difficult! Will there even be anyone capable of reaching the 32nd or 33rd step?”

Originally, many people thought that Purple Blade was inferior to Nether Limitless, but close in strength to Dragon Fang and Lin Ming. Now, they all realized just how great the disparity was.

“The other four are already nearing the top!”

“Lin Ming, Dragon Fang, and Nether Limitless are in the lead. Bloodless Sword has fallen behind them just a bit. Does this represent the difference in their strengths?”

“That might not be true. To find the actual difference in their strength, they have to undergo true combat. The Divine Seal Altar is merely a platform used to test the comprehensive fusion of one’s cultivation and talent.”

“It seems that all four of them will be able to reach the top. If so, they will have to fight!”

“I’m really looking forwards to it. Regardless of who fights who, it will surely be a clash of rivals!”

“These two fellows!” Nether Limitless looked at Lin Ming and Dragon Fang with disbelief in his eyes. “What are those two doing that they are climbing up so quickly? I have to give my everything in order to just barely keep up with their speed!

“Is it possible that the two of them have some sort of special immunity to soul pressure?”

Thinking about it, Xiao Daochild had said that the Divine Seal Altar was not just a test of one’s cultivation and thickness of true essence. It was also a test of one’s will, potential, and all sorts of other factors combined together. Nether Limitless thought all of this was a bit grating to his ears.

He was confident that his own strength and depth of true essence were far above that of Lin Ming and Dragon Fang. Could it be that his potential was inferior to theirs, thus they equalized each other and all three were able to maintain a similar speed?

“Can my potential truly be inferior to those two?”

Nether Limitless found this hard to accept.

In the way he viewed the world, he could accept it if an Empyrean descendant was superior to him. After all, someone that came from a Great World King Holy Land background simply couldn’t compare to the talent, inheritance, and resources of an Empyrean Heavenly Palace.

But, for small influences, even if they were dark horses that rushed out from the endless masses, he could not accept that they were on par with him!

It had to be known that in Nether Limitless’s nearly 40 year years of life, he had consumed a massive amount of resources. With all these resources gathered together, their value was no longer estimated in violet sun stones, but nine sun jades.

Nine sun jades were refined by half-step Empyreans and above by combining violet sun crystals with nine different types of yang energies. A single nine sun jade was equal to nearly 100 million violet sun crystals, or a trillion violet sun stones.

Nether Limitless had used so many resources and also practiced a transcendent divine might. Even so, he wasn’t much superior to two common martial artists. How could Nether Limitless accept this? It made him feel as if all those resources used on him had been wasted, as if they had been used on a dog.

“It’s impossible that they are better than me. I will not believe this. They must have some special arcane skill capable of resisting soul pressure, or their own soul force is astoundingly formidable, thus they are able to reach this speed…”

Nether Limitless speculated. In truth, his guesses were half right.

Lin Ming and Dragon Fang both had an extremely strong resistance to soul pressure. One cultivated the soul and the other had a special variation soul body.

An hour later, Dragon Fang was the first one to reach the 31st step of the Divine Seal Altar.

And behind Dragon Fang, just after 20 breaths of time, Nether Limitless arrived at nearly the same time as Lin Ming.

At this time, Dragon Fang’s pupils had returned to normal. His face was a bit paler than before, and he seemed extremely fragile. It was hard to imagine that a terrifying strength slumbered within him.

“These two people haven’t exhausted themselves too much… they must have some special technique to resist soul pressure.” As Nether Limitless saw Lin Ming and Dragon Fang’s appearance, he was increasingly sure of his own speculations. “If that’s the case, I will simply use my absolute strength to defeat all of you!”

After another quarter hour passed, Bloodless Sword finally crawled up the cliff of the 31st step with great difficulty.

The four of them had all successfully climbed up. Without a doubt, besides the four of them, there wouldn’t be another person that could make it up this high.

A decisive battle would soon erupt between these four people!

“This is too intense! The four of them are all peak masters; who will battle who?”

“I feel that Bloodless Sword is the weakest, Lin Ming and Dragon Fang are both similar, and Nether Limitless is the strongest!”

Based on their performance since the 21st step, Bloodless Sword was a bit worse and the other three were the same. But in the eyes of the audience, Nether Limitless was at the late Divine Sea, thus his cultivation and true essence were the deepest of the four. Lin Ming and Dragon Fang should surpass him in potential, but if they truly fought, Nether Limitless was likely stronger.

“This Lin Ming is truly a freak. He’s only at the peak of the early Divine Sea realm, yet he’s this strong. I really have no idea just how he has trained.”

…………..

At this time, several hundred miles away from the Divine Seal Altar, a spirit ship floated high in the skies.

In the spirit ship, a tall man in black robes was sitting in a grand black stone throne, looking through a window at the far off Divine Seal Altar. Even though he was this far away, he was able to clearly see everything happening on the Divine Seal Altar in crystal clear detail.

“Of those four people, two of them registered to enter the First Martial Meeting at my True Martial Word. But, the truth is that they aren’t from my True Martial World, nor do they belong to my True Martial Holy Lands. One is a wandering cultivator that just happened to be passing by, and the identity of his master is a mystery. As for the other, he is a disciple of a mere peak Holy Land. Even so, the two of them are able to stand on the 31st step! But, the disciple that I carefully raised up for all this time was actually eliminated on the 27th step! I used my portion of the income from Starbind Bank and the Imperial Auction House as the foundation for your resources, and even gave you an incomplete transcendent divine might as an inheritance. Even though I did all of this, this is the trash result that you gave me!”

This black-robed man was fuming with anger. He was the Great World King of True Martial World. In truth, True Martial World was only a sect from a second-order world, so it was normal that they wouldn’t have any disciples able to reach the 30th step. But now, four people had appeared that were able to step on the 31st step, and although two of them had even registered at the True Martial World, they actually weren’t from there. This was truly a matter that made one lose all face.

As the black-robed man spoke, the martial artists in front of him were all kneeling on the floor, trembling in fear. No one dared to speak up.

The black-robed man heaved a heavy sigh. “It has been over a million years and I have used up countless resources, and yet… if another million years pass and my True Martial Holy Lands still aren’t able to raise another World King, then that is simply the hand of fate. There will be nothing else I can do…”

The black-robed man shook his head, no longer speaking. He alone was the pillar that propped up the entire True Martial Holy Lands, but he would be unable to do so forever…

At this time on the Divine Seal Altar, the four participants still hadn’t fought. Rather, they rested for a moment. This brief period of rest was most beneficial to Bloodless Sword because he had exhausted the most energy of the four.

The pressure on the 31st step was extremely suppressive. Even though it was completely flat ground, Bloodless Sword still felt his own strength suppressed to no more than 40%.

“These damned fellows have actually climbed up faster than me. This weird Divine Seal Altar simply doesn’t allow me to display my sword skills to their full potential. In terms of total combat strength, with my sword in hand, I don’t believe that I will lose to an early Divine Sea or middle Divine Sea brat!”

The truth was that a Great World King Holy Land would deliberately train core disciples to participate in the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting. To guarantee the greatest chance of victory, they would make sure all disciples that entered were at the late Divine Sea realm. By entering a time enchantment it was easy to accomplish this.

Thus, Crimson Wishjade, Wu Finalcloud, Nether Limitless, Bloodless Sword, and the rest were all late Divine Sea martial artists.

If one wasn’t at the late Divine Sea realm, it was easy to suffer a great loss. Only those scattered smaller sects would send a group of early or middle Divine Sea realm disciples to participate as cannon fodder. In any case, for them, attaining any kind of good result was impossible to begin with.

“Choose your opponent!” Xiao Daochild indifferently said, his face like a 10,000 year glacier. No matter how amazing the participants on the Divine Seal Altar were, he didn’t have any expression at all, as if everything that happened was natural. To Xiao Daochild, the 31st step wasn’t anything at all!

As Xiao Daochild spoke these words, the billions of people in the audience held their breath.

And on the 31st step of the Divine Seal Altar, Lin Ming, Nether Limitless, Dragon Fang, and Bloodless Sword all glanced at each other, a fierce and vivid fighting spirit blazing in their eyes, nearly causing the air to burn.

“The two of you have quite wonderful soul support arcane skills, hm? To think that you would do something so cheap as using them to climb up here.” Nether Limitless was the first to speak.

“Oh? What are you trying to say?” Lin Ming asked, an eyebrow arching up.

“Even if you don’t want to admit it, you cannot hide from my eyes. But from now, it will be a battle of strength, something that will depend on your true ability. Do you want to choose first, or shall I choose first?” Nether Limitless had an extremely confident expression, as if he were the top master of the four people here.

Dragon Fang was silent, but Lin Ming grinned and then laughed. “Since you let me choose first, then I won’t be rude. I choose… you!”

Lin Ming pointed his spear towards Nether Limitless!

This movement caused a great commotion!

Of the four martial artists, no matter how one looked at it, Bloodless Sword should be the weakest. Thus, if one was allowed to choose first, choosing Bloodless Sword was the most appropriate choice. But, Lin Ming had actually chosen the supposed strongest Nether Limitless!

“This Lin Ming is too crazy!”

“What a badass!”

As Nether Limitless saw Lin Ming’s icy spear pointed towards him, a thick killing intent flashed in his eyes, “You’ve got guts!”

Chapter 1253 – Comprehending the Concepts

“Dragon Fang!”

“Dragon Fang!”

“Lin Ming!”

“Lin Ming!”

Billions of people crazily shouted out. At this time, no one was divided any longer by divisions of great worlds. The Ancient Phoenix Clan cheered out, the Crimson Light Great World’s people cheered out, the True Martial Great World’s people cheered, and even Demondawn Great World’s people cheered.

The scene was filled with an incomparable craziness. Everyone was hoping that these two people on the altar could create a miracle, a miracle that belonged to all martial artists!

In particular, everyone’s attention was focused Dragon Fang, the strongest martial artist from the 100 great worlds that had gathered at Gravemoon Star. It was extremely likely he would break apart the legends left behind at an Empyrean Heavenly Palace.

At this time, on the Divine Seal Altar, Lin Ming and Dragon Fang had already climbed up a tenth of the 32nd step; that was also 10,000 feet!

In the last several Divine Realm First Martial Meetings in which the Divine Seal Altar had been used, no one had been able to climb up to the 32nd step. One could see just how difficult it was from this alone!

….

“This is really a grand occasion of Gravemoon Star’s competition area. It’s something that wouldn’t be seen in even a million years!”

In the arena filled with billions of people, the highest class reserved area was a place specially prepared for the certain guests. This area formed its own separate minor dimension, and all those that sat here were old people, each and every one of them an important character of the 100 great worlds.

Among them, most were peak Holy Lords and there were even some half-step World Kings. However, there were no true World Kings.

World King powerhouses, especially Great Worlds Kings with high status like Tian Mingzi, could gather at Empyrean Heavenly Palaces and personally watch the competition with Empyrean disciples through massive crystal mirrors. Worlds Kings with slightly lower statuses, such as the True Martial Great World King, could ride their spirit ship and watch the competition from the skies. This was a privilege that only World Kings had. No one else was allowed to fly in the skies, otherwise the skies above the semifinals field would have already been filled with people.

Besides World Kings, the high level figures of the great worlds could only sit in the arena and watch from private reserved seats.

These characters were all haughty existences, rulers of their own domains. But now, as they saw Dragon Fang and Lin Ming, they were all filled with a deep emotion. The tides of time would eventually wash out the old and bring in the new; every new generation would succeed and surpass the last. The future achievements of these two youths were hard to imagine.

“Unbelievable. These two are definitely proud elites of their generation. I wonder just which one is better!”

“Mm, Dragon Fang is great, but Lin Ming is also outstanding. With his early Divine Sea cultivation, he was actually able to follow Dragon Fang this far. That isn’t simple at all!”

Everyone thought that Lin Ming was being slowly left behind by Dragon Fang. But, Lin Ming continued to climb up 10,000 feet, not falling a single bit behind Dragon Fang.

…………….

Wind howled.

The cheers were deafening.

The 3.3 million feet Divine Sea Altar stood proud and tall in the world. Climbing it, Lin Ming and Dragon Fang seemed extremely common and humble. But in actuality, in the future… they would be pillars that supported the entire Divine Realm!

10,000 feet…

20,000 feet…

30,000 feet…

Lin Ming climbed higher and higher, keeping pace with Dragon Fang!

The higher they climbed, the fiercer and more suppressive the pressure became!

“What a marvelous Divine Seal Altar. Every trace on the stone contained the aura of the Great Dao Laws.”

Lin Ming caught his breath. Every breath he took was long and deep. He inhaled like a snake and exhaled like an arrow, every breath equal to a hundred breaths of an ordinary person.

Moreover, an ordinary person inhaled air, but what Lin Ming breathed in was heaven and earth origin energy.

Pressure flooded down like a waterfall. It wasn’t just the Empyrean pressure, but Lin Ming also felt that his surroundings were filled with the power of chaotic Laws.

This power of Laws was not uniform and without rules; it was even different from the Laws that Lin Ming had comprehended.

If he didn’t revolve his own Laws to resist them, this chaotic power would have torn him down.

Every step he took up was filled with difficulties.

On one step, Lin Ming felt as if he had stepped onto the precipice of a falling cliff. On another step, he felt as if he had fallen into mud. On the next step, he felt as if he was being drowned in water.

Sometimes, a sudden swell of immense gravity would rush towards him, making it feel as if his arms would be ripped off. If it weren’t Lin Ming but some ordinary martial artist that didn’t possess his powerful mortal body and thick true essence, these gravitational waves would have pulled him off the cliff.

And sometimes, there would be a sudden impact of chaotic energy that directly attacked Lin Ming’s true essence. This chaotic energy was no less than the all-out attack of a late Divine Sea powerhouse. If this were usual times, then Lin Ming would have shrugged off the attack of an ordinary late Divine Sea powerhouse. But now, as he climbed the Divine Seal Altar and with him having consumed a great deal of strength, he found it difficult to withstand these strikes.

Hu – !

Lin Ming let out a long breath. He had only climbed up 30 thousand some feet; there was still 60 thousand some feet awaiting him!

According to this trend, Lin Ming sensed that it wouldn’t be a problem at all to reach the 32nd step. But, just the 32nd step was not Lin Ming’s ultimate goal!

He wanted to reach the 33rd step. But now, with his current ability, he would only be able to crawl several thousand feet up the 33rd step before being pushed off!

The Divine Seal Altar was known as a test where a Divine Sea realm martial artist could reach the summit. Empyrean Vast Universe had created this Divine Seal Altar so many years ago and yet he hadn’t had a single disciple that had ever managed to crawl up to the top during the Divine Sea realm. This was naturally not fake boastful talk.

Moreover, when the disciples of Empyrean Vast Universe had tried to climb up, nearly all of them had been at the late Divine Sea realm during their attempt. As for Lin Ming, he was only at the early Divine Sea realm.

Lin Ming didn’t expect to reach the top of the 33rd step. Want he wanted to do was to climb the 33rd step as far as he could, digging out all of his potential and pushing his limits to their extreme!

Lin Ming turned to look at Dragon Fang. Dragon Fang wasn’t too far away from Lin Ming; they were both climbing at around the same speed.

At this time, Dragon Fang’s pupils had turned into needle-like dots, with countless mysterious and profound patterns surrounding them.

“Those pupils…”

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. This wasn’t the first time he had seen Dragon Fang’s strange pupils.

Although he didn’t understand what mysteries were behind it, what he was certain about was that Dragon Fang had a higher awareness of the surrounding chaotic Laws because of these pupils. Thus, the amount of chaotic power Dragon Fang had to withstand was less than what Lin Ming had to withstand.

Dragon Fang sensed Lin Ming’s gaze and turned towards him. His variation pupils were incomparably sharp, as if they could see through one’s heart.

Dragon Fang smiled and continued to climb.

But at this time, Lin Ming actually slowed down. He took a deep breath and concentrated his thoughts.

Eyes closed in meditation!

From the very moment that Lin Ming touched the Divine Seal Altar, he had felt a vague Concept from it – the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens!

This Concept filled every nook and corner of the Divine Seal Altar. Others could not sense it, but Lin Ming could clearly feel it.

Just what were the 33 Layered Heavens?

Lin Ming was unable to clearly say what it was, but he knew it wasn’t just myths and empty talk.

Because Lin Ming had crossed a 33 Layered Heavens Ninefall which contained the Laws of the Great Dao.

“Lin Ming isn’t moving!”

Everyone in the audience saw Lin Ming suddenly stop moving. Lin Ming had been able to follow Dragon Fang’s speed, but now that he remained motionless, he had been cast off by Dragon Fang.

“Is he resting because he exhausted his strength?”

On the Divine Seal Altar, martial artists were not allowed to fly, nor could they. In this situation, they were like mortals climbing a cliff. Sometimes they would stop on a ledge to restore their strength.

“Taking a rest is a good idea, otherwise he’ll exhaust his true essence and be swept off the Divine Seal Altar.”

“It looks like Dragon Fang will be able to smoothly mount the 32nd step. Lin Ming might find it difficult to reach that far though. But, even if he was swept away now, that would also be very good. Don’t forget that he is only at the early Divine Sea realm!”

Lin Ming was currently 35,000 feet high on the 32nd step. At this height, even if he were to be immediately defeated, no one would ever look down on him, because none of them would have the qualifications to do so!

In the past, when the Divine Seal Altar was used in the semifinals of the First Martial Meeting, there were countless unrivalled late Divine Sea geniuses that were all swept down before mounting the 32nd step.

“He’s done well. At the early Divine Sea he defeated Nether Limitless and also climbed 35,000 feet up the Divine Seal Altar’s 32nd step. If he can rest here and then climb up a few tens of thousands of feet more, he can take pride in his accomplishments!”

At this time, Dragon Fang had already climbed 45,000 feet up the 32nd step. As for Lin Ming, he was stuck at 35,000 feet up.

On the 32nd step, even Dragon Fang had to slowly climb up. It took him nearly half an hour to climb up these 10,000 feet.

Lin Ming had been lost in meditation for this half hour.

“Is he still resting? Even if he doesn’t move on the cliff, he still has to withstand the pressure. Can he not move his arms?”

“Could he have already lost consciousness, and is relying on his final breath to hold on…?”

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin, hold on!”

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin, don’t give up!”

All of the young Ancient Phoenix Clan disciples were crying and cheering for Lin Ming.

As they shouted, there was a loud explosive sound as the chaotic power broke through, causing Lin Ming’s protective true essence to burst apart. Even so, Lin Ming remained completely unaware of all this.

His forehead was matted with blood.

Even though Lin Ming had opened the Gate of View and fused with the supreme dragon bone, causing his bodily defensive power to reach incredible degrees, this was still a situation where he had consumed a great deal of his energy and also didn’t stimulate the true essence and dragon bone power within his body. In this meditative state, even a late Divine Sea powerhouse would be injured.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin!”

The disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan were horrified. After Lin Ming’s protective true essence shattered, he didn’t summon any new protective true essence!

“Senior-apprentice Brother Lin, be careful!”

The martial artists of the Ancient Phoenix Clan all cried out. But, despite their shouts, that chaotic energy still hurtled towards Lin Ming’s back!

Without any protective true essence, he would have to directly withstand the impact of this energy!

Peng!

Lin Ming’s body suddenly shook. The clothes on his back tore apart and his skin was torn, dripping blood.

“Brother Lin!”

Qin Xingxuan cried out in alarm and fear as she saw this.

From the start, whether it was Lin Ming or Dragon Fang, both of them had fully galvanized their protective true essence to block the chaotic energy the 32nd step. The shockwaves afterwards were withstood by their bodies or flexible armor.

But now, Lin Ming’s protective true essence had been shattered and he would withstand this chaotic energy with his body alone. If an ordinary martial artist were to be struck by this, their body would be torn apart.

“Lin Ming is really unconscious!”

“There must be a mistake. How could he be so fierce if he’s unconscious? He withstood two hits and didn’t fall down?”

In the eyes of the audience, if Lin Ming was really unconscious, he should have instantly tumbled down once struck.

Chapter 1256 – Climbing to the 33rd Step

“The great calamity approaches…” Empyrean Divine Dream said to herself, as if she were immersed in the rivers of endless history.

Of course, even if one were to say that this great calamity of the Heavenly Dao was approaching soon, that could mean tens of thousands or even millions of years.

In truth, no one could say just when it would happen.

During this tumultuous period, old Empyreans would fall and new Empyreans would rise.

At this time, Empyrean Vast Universe’s thoughts stirred and he looked towards the Divine Seal Altar.

“Dragon Fang has also begun to display his strength… the Three Lives Pupils truly lives up to its name!”

Empyrean Vast Universe was more confident in Dragon Fang because his Three Lives Pupils was a complete transcendent divine might. It was also known as a heaven-defying physical state, one that could peer through all Laws. Even among all transcendent divine mights, it was still considered an outstanding example!

Even with transcendent divine mights, there were great disparities between them.

At this time, on the Divine Seal Altar’s 32nd step, Lin Ming had already climbed up to the 50,000 foot mark. His speed still didn’t slow down, as if there was nothing that could stop his advance.

However, at the time Lin Ming started moving again, Dragon Fang had already climbed up 80,000 feet.

Dragon Fang lowered his head and looked at Lin Ming. In his eyes, where his pupils were surrounded by numerous complex and wonderful patterns, it was impossible to make out what shined there.

“He has comprehended the special Laws on the Divine Seal Altar?” Dragon Fang suddenly thought. He couldn’t perceive the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens, but he knew that there was some special Law that permeated the entire Divine Seal Altar.

“With an hour, he actually managed to perceive the special Laws of the Divine Seal Altar while clinging onto the cliff. This is truly amazing! I can also understand some things about the Divine Seal Altar, but that is all depending on the Three Lives Pupils, something that Lin Ming does not possess.”

Dragon Fang had heartfelt admiration towards Lin Ming. In truth, the further Dragon Fang climbed up the Divine Seal Altar’s 32nd step, the easier it became for him. Just what sort of genius was he? He wasn’t the type to use brute force to resist the impact from the power of divinity that contained 33 different energies of the Heavenly Dao. Rather, as he climbed up, he would also ponder the rules of the power of divinity.

Of course, it was impossible for Dragon Fang to perceive the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens like Lin Ming did. After all, he did not cross a 33 Layered Heavens Ninefall. Even so, Dragon Fang had a special trump card in his hands, the Three Lives Pupils that were known to see through all Laws!

In front of the Three Lives Pupils, there were no Laws that could hide!

The reason that Dragon Fang could comprehend the fifth level Concept of the Space Laws at a mere 36 years of age was all due to the Three Lives Pupils.

Originally, Dragon Fang’s Space Laws had been stranded at the fourth level Concept. But, after he opened the Three Lives Pupils, in the short three months he spent on the spirit ship travelling to Gravemoon Star, his Space Laws had stepped into the fifth level. After several more months, his Time Laws would also break into the fifth level. This was the heaven-defying power of the Three Lives Pupils!

By relying on the Three Lives Pupils, Dragon Fang was able to see the movement path of the power of divinity. Although he couldn’t directly absorb the power of divinity like Lin Ming, he could still slowly make out the paths that it would move along. By following these rules and adjusting the route he climbed up, he could avoid the powerful impact areas of the power of divinity, and instead climb up the areas where the power of divinity was at its weakest point.

In this way, Lin Ming rapidly climbed up the Divine Seal Altar because he was going in a straight line. As for Dragon Fang, his trajectory would suddenly twist. He would move about, turning left before switching back to the right!

The surges of the power of divinity passed by Dragon Fang like waves, simply not touching his body at all. Thus, Dragon Fang only had to withstand a very small impact, causing his speed to rise significantly!

From the start, he had merely moved left and right as he climbed up. But later, on the cliffs of the Divine Seal Altar, he simply jumped upwards. Every time he jumped up he would dodge seven or eight strikes of the power of divinity!

“Look how fast Dragon Fang is climbing!”

“Heavens! What sort of route is he taking?”

The current Dragon Fang was like a spirit monkey, constantly jumping about. He began to climb up faster and faster.

“Too fierce! Although I don’t know what Dragon Fang has comprehended, there is definitely a special meaning to the way he is climbing up. He must have figured out how to conform to the Laws of the Divine Seal Altar!”

“A chosen pride of heaven! Truly a chosen pride of heaven! Lin Ming is already a monstrous genius, but Dragon Fang can still suppress him this time. Lin Ming has comprehended the Laws of the Divine Seal Altar, and Dragon Fang has also done the same! But, Dragon Fang comprehended these Laws in a much more relaxed manner! Lin Ming had to stop and pay a great price in injuries become becoming aware of these Laws, but Dragon Fang was able to do so as he climbed up.”

How could the spectators on Gravemoon Star understand the essential difference in how Lin Ming and Dragon Fang understood the Laws of the Divine Seal Altar? They didn’t know that Lin Ming had truly comprehended the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens and was absorbing a tenth of the power of divinity to use for himself.

As for Dragon Fang, he merely used the Three Lives Pupils to understand the movement path of the power of divinity and was jumping through the weakest points. This could be considered a trick he was using.

However, in their opinion, Dragon Fang’s climb up seemed extremely relaxed, as if he were doing flips and jumps on the cliff!

As for Lin Ming, he was much calmer. He climbed in a straight line upwards without making any big motions at all.

Half an hour later, Lin Ming crawled 60,000 feet high, but Dragon Fang had already mounted the flat plains of the Divine Seal Altar’s 32nd step!

Dragon Fang was the first to mount the 32nd step!

“Dragon Fang!”

“Dragon Fang!”

“Amazing!”

“King!!”

The entire audience cheered like a surging tidal wave. Even the disciples of the Ancient Phoenix Clan cheered for Dragon Fang.

This level of talent was truly impressive.

Normally, when a genius fought Lin Ming, that opponent would suffer a defeat once he revealed his advantages and the hidden cards in his hands. Or, at least they would begin to gradually be worn down.

While Lin Ming was breaking through his own limits, only someone like Dragon Fang could similarly erupt with his own potential, obtaining new comprehensions and rising to even greater heights!

This was the difference between an ordinary genius and an unrivalled talent!

Thus, for those watching, Dragon Fang had never been suppressed by Lin Ming. On the contrary, he had been the one to faintly suppress Lin Ming.

After several quarter hours of time passed, Lin Ming also reached the top of the 32nd step without any further problems.

The two peerless geniuses both met on the 32nd step!

It had to be known that in the last several Divine Realm First Martial Meetings in which the Divine Seal Altar had been used, there had not been a single person to reach the 32nd step. But now, there were two people all of a sudden!

This was a battle of kings!

The audience issued deafening cheers. Everyone was looking forward to this explosive moment, crazy with anticipation.

And on the Divine Seal Altar, Lin Ming and Dragon Fang were standing 500 feet apart. The two were of similar height and build. However, Lin Ming was more handsome with sharp and distinct facial features, a healthy outstanding young man in the prime of his youth. As for Dragon Fang, he looked more delicate, with pale white skin.

“Lin Ming, you are indeed a rival that I appreciate.” Dragon Fang said. The faint movements of his body seemed relaxed, as if he could easily withstand the pressure on the 32nd step without needing to worry about the impact from the power of divinity.

“You too. In all these years that I have practiced martial arts, you are the most talented contemporary that I have seen. Most of the time it is others that underestimate me, but when I thought I could defeat you, you still managed to make another breakthrough!”

As Lin Ming spoke, he traced his spatial ring. According to the rules of this competition, in order to earn the qualifications to climb up the next step, they had to defeat an opponent on the current step. And, the only two people on the 32nd step were the two of them! That meant that their opponents were each other!

Dragon Fang looked at Lin Ming’s movements. “Are you planning to fight me now?”

“Those are the rules.” Lin Ming said. In truth, he didn’t want to fight Dragon Fang at this time. In all fairness, he had to admit that he didn’t have any confidence in facing Dragon Fang. He didn’t know just where Dragon Fang’s limits were.

Dragon Fang smiled. “Rules are only rules. I also don’t wish to fight with you now. The reason for this is simple. Although I have the confidence to win, I will not be able to do so with any degree of ease. I know I will be severely wounded and will use up at least 80-90% of my true essence. In this situation, even if I were to rest on the 32nd step for a long period of time, I wouldn’t be able to restore myself. My wish of mounting the 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar would become nothing more than a hopeless impossibility. What do you think?”

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. In truth, he was also well aware of this point. Once he fought with Dragon Fang, he would no longer have the strength to climb up the Divine Seal Altar.

And Lin Ming very much wanted to climb up the 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar. Although this Divine Seal Altar was only a replica Empyrean spirit treasure created by Empyrean Vast Universe, and in no ways the true ancient Divine Seal Altar, it still truly contained the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. If he were able to comprehend this Concept more, that would be an immense benefit to Lin Ming. He definitely didn’t wish to miss out on this lucky chance.

Lin Ming looked towards Dragon Fang and let go of his spatial ring.

Dragon Fang faintly smiled, returning Lin Ming’s soft gaze.

Following this, the two of them looked towards Xiao Daochild – the one who presided over the First Martial Meeting semifinals on Gravemoon Star.

Whether or not they could skip this battle and climb directly to the 33rd step all depended on him.

Xiao Daochild chuckled. “Good. You two have the ambition and boldness to climb up the 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar; that is something I appreciate very much! The 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar is a legend. It is said that no one below the Divine Transformation realm could ever hope to reach it. Of course, those are only legends, and these legends are in truth limited to Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. This is because besides those moments when the Divine Seal Altar is moved out to be used in the semifinals of the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, it has only been placed at Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, so that the disciples there could gain experience from it! The other Empyrean disciples each have their own methods of tempering themselves and gaining experience, thus they do not climb up the Divine Seal Altar.

“When my Honorable Master was 8.6 million years of age, he created this Divine Seal Altar. Up until now, over 2 million years have passed. For all those underneath the Divine Transformation realm, even if they are direct disciples of Honorable Master, none of them have been able to reach the summit! There has been a disciple that reached 70,000 feet up the 33rd step, but even at that distance, there is still 30,000 feet remaining! And, at that time, the disciple had a late Divine Sea realm cultivation!

“Today, of the two of you, one has a middle Divine Sea cultivation and the other has an early Divine Sea cultivation. You can both be more than proud that you have reached this step. You no longer need to fight, but can directly continue climbing up the Divine Seal Altar!”

As those in the arena heard Xiao Daochild’s announcement, most of them were crestfallen. They had wanted to see the epic showdown between these two kings of their generation.

But at the same time, they could also witness Lin Ming and Dragon Fang climb up the 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar when both were at their peak condition. This was truly an eternally grand event!

“This is too exciting!”

“These are kings of the younger generation. I wonder just how high they can climb? Perhaps they can even reach the top!”

“Reach the top? Haha, you are far too naïve. Mounting the summit is impossible, but crawling several tens of thousands of feet is no problem at all. Dragon Fang might even reach the record set by that senior disciple from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. As for Lin Ming, he should be a bit worse. He should be able to climb 30,000-40,000 feet high!”

Chapter 1259 – Absolute Slaughter Thunder Sources

Kacha!

The bolt of purple thunder came crashing down, winding about like a swimming dragon!

This divine thunder was dozens of feet thick. It struck the Divine Seal Altar with unstoppable momentum, randomly crawling around and turning the entire upper 33,000 feet height of the Divine Seal Altar into a purple sea.

Even though the audience was extremely far away, they were still panic-stricken as they saw this. Without a doubt, if any of the outstanding young elites in the audience were to be placed in that purple sea, they would all be fried into ash!

“That is heavenly tribulation! Heavens, those are tribulation clouds!”

“Heavenly tribulation has covered the last 30,000 some feet. In climbing up the last section of the Divine Seal Altar, one actually has to withstand heavenly tribulation!? This difficulty is far too ridiculous! No wonder for the last 2 million years of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, even though there were dozens or hundreds of chosen prides of heaven, not a single one of them has been able to mount the summit of the Divine Seal Altar!”

“Even for Dragon Fang it is impossible to create a miracle. Wanting to withstand this heavenly tribulation like he’s been doing so far is an act of futility. If I’m not wrong, the heavenly tribulation will become fierce the further up one goes. Perhaps Dragon Fang will be stopped at 70,000 feet!”

Out of the billions of people watching, very few of them believed in Dragon Fang. Heavenly tribulation was not a trifling joke. Even if Dragon Fang was on flat ground and also in his most flourishing condition, he would still have to carefully prepare himself to have just a small chance of passing this. But now, he was currently climbing up the Divine Seal Altar and he had exhausted a great deal of his strength in coming up so far.

“Heavenly tribulation…”

Dragon Fang’s eyes burned with purple flames. He placed the Dragon Fang Blade between his lips, the shark blade edge reflecting his snow white teeth, cold and sharp.

“In the past, Honorable Master once listed seven divine artifacts to me, and the ancient Divine Seal was listed third amongst them. But, that has already disappeared for an extremely long time by now. The Divine Seal Altar that Empyrean Vast Universe created was refined by drawing support from a wisp of the ancient Divine Seal Altar’s artifact spirit. Even so, Honorable Master said that this replica Divine Seal Altar is not something I can climb all the way. Now that heavenly tribulation has arrived, let me see just what step my Three Lives Pupils will help me reach!”

In the face of this endless roiling purple sea, the average person would have lost all their courage to continue. But for Dragon Fang, this challenge caused his fighting spirit to boil over!

He bit down on the Dragon Fang Blade and slowly climbed up towards that purple sea!

From 50,000 feet to the purple thunder dominion, there was still 17,000 feet. For Dragon Fang to climb this distance still took some time. By the time he climbed up to 65,000 feet, Dragon Fang’s entire body was dripping with sweat and blue veins were popping out on his forehead!

Maintaining the state of All Existence to Void created a tremendous burden on his body!

At 65,000 feet, he was still 2000 feet from reaching that turbulent purple sea. But even so, at this time, the purple strip of thunder left that purple sea and shot downwards!

Kacha!

A terrifying explosion rang out like the roar of gods! Dragon Fang’s body shook and the spatial enchantment around him began to shatter like a broken eggshell!

“The spatial enchantment is breaking!”

As the audience saw this, all of them held their breath. In that brief instant there simply wasn’t enough time to respond. The purple thunder burst apart that spatial enchantment and thrust down at Dragon Fang.

But at this moment, another spatial enchantment flashed into existence around Dragon Fang, blocking this thunder.

“Double layered spatial enchantment!?”

No one thought that after the first level spatial enchantment shattered, there would also be a second one that wrapped around Dragon Fang. This second layer enchantment had blocked the thunder attack!

And Dragon Fang had escaped this without a single wound!

“He blocked it! Wonderful!”

“He’s comprehended the Space Laws enough to create a multi-layered spatial enchantment. To reach this degree at 36 years of age is unbelievable!”

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Beams of savage thunder crashed down, crashing onto the spatial enchantments around Dragon Fang.

As a ray of thunder chopped apart a spatial enchantment, another new layer would appear around Dragon Fang’s body forming a completely balanced system.

Like this, Dragon Fang shouldered the arcs of thunder and climbed up towards the purple thunder dominion!

67,000 feet high was still 33,000 feet away from the summit of the Divine Seal Altar!

Here was where the thunder dominion was.

At this point, Dragon Fang could feel the terrifying energy contained with that purple thunder dominion.

“He’s entering the thunder dominion!”

“67,000 feet, he’s only 3000 feet away from the 70,000 foot record left behind by Empyrean Vast Universe’s disciple. In other words, any one of Empyrean Vast Universe’s disciples would be instantly defeated as soon as they entered the Thunder Dominion!”

The audience watched with unblinking eyes. Dragon Fang grit his teeth and broke into the thunder dominion!

As soon as he entered the thunder dominion, the power of thunder rushed towards him like an endless stream of time, seeming to pierce through space itself! Within this vast purple sea, any martial artist was nothing but a dinky boat drifting in the swelling waves, incomparably small, able to overturn at any moment!

Purple light filled every inch of space. The rolling thunderclaps were deafening, endless. The double layered spatial enchantments around Dragon Fang rapidly melted away like ice underneath the noon sun!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Like the apocalypse, everything in the world seemed as if it were being destroyed.

Dragon Fang’s entire body was wreathed in flickering purple flames. As the baptism of thunder crashed onto him, it was impossible to imagine what kind of tribulation he was experiencing.

The spatial enchantments around him constantly shattered and reformed. Although Dragon Fang’s restorative ability was inferior to Lin Ming’s, it was still extremely amazing. Even though he was consuming energy at a rapid pace, he was still able to continue on.

68,000 feet! 69,000 feet!

He was only a thousand feet away from reaching the record left behind by Vast Void!

At this time, Dragon Fang’s entire body was bulging with blue veins and all the blood vessels beneath his skin were visible in clear detail. It was no longer possible to see his eyes; one could only see brilliantly combusting purple flames!

“He’s going to break the record!”

“Dragon Fang, you can do it!”

“Dragon Fang!”

“Dragon Fang!”

Many people cheered out for Dragon Fang. There were many young girls that screamed out his name!

The record was right in front of him. The Divine Seal Altar was a comprehensive test of one’s cultivation and potential. But, in a situation where one’s cultivation wasn’t high enough to resist the heavenly tribulation, then that only left… one’s potential!

As long as Dragon Fang could draw with this record, it would prove that his potential easily swept away every single disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.

If Dragon Fang, a middle Divine Sea realm martial artist, could climb up 70,000 feet on the 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar, then he would create a legend!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The heavenly tribulation became increasingly wild. Dragon Fang’s skin began to crack as blood poured down from these wounds. There was even blood dripping from the corners of his lips!

However, he still steadily climbed up as before.

Finally, he had passed a 70,000 foot height and had broken Vast Void’s record!

In that instant, the entire arena, the billions of spectators there, were all cheering out as loudly as they could!

This was a miracle wrought by Dragon Fang!

After reaching 70,000 feet, there was suddenly a drastic change in the thunder dominion. Within the thunder dominion, the endless thunder gathered together, forming savage vicious beasts!

Of these beasts, some seemed like massive pythons, some were enormous lizards, some were tigers, and there were even some like flood dragons. All of them clawed their way towards Dragon Fang!

“Heavens! What is that!?”

“Those are spirit bodies formed by the power of thunder, Thunder Souls! No… no, those are Thunder Sources!”

Thunder Sources were energy life forms created by the essence of thunder. The Purple Lion Thunder Source that Lin Ming absorbed was also a Thunder Source.

In order for a Thunder Source to be born, it had to be at the center of countless coincidences for tens of millions or even hundreds of millions of years.

And now, on the 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar, there were suddenly over 20 Thunder Sources!

All of these Thunder Sources hurtled towards Dragon Fang!

Each Thunder Source had the ability to kill an early Divine Sea powerhouse!

An ordinary Divine Sea martial artist would be instantly killed. Even a master would find them extremely difficult to deal with, much less in these endless purple thunder dominion.

Dragon Fang took out the Dragon Fang Blade from his mouth. Space rippled around the blade as he slashed out!

“Tremble, space!”

With this slash, all of the space around the Dragon Fang Blade began to vibrate at high speeds! A weapon that was vibrating at high speed was much sharper than normal. Moreover, what Dragon Fang did was cause space to tremble and not his weapon. Space was known as the sharpest weapon in the world!

Peng peng peng peng!

Four Thunder Sources were blocked by Dragon Fang!

But, the other Thunder Sources followed right after, Dragon Fang didn’t have time to redraw his sword!

As Dragon Fang saw those numerous Thunder Sources rush towards him, in this critical moment, he shouted out –

“Mirror Image Avatar!”

Woosh woosh woosh woosh woosh woosh woosh!

Seven figures flashed out from Dragon Fang. These spatial mirror image projections were what Dragon Fang used to defeat Bloodless Sword. It was able to allow him to divide into eight!

These seven mirror images all attacked, each one blocking three Thunder Sources, instantly stopping 21 of them. However, two final Thunder Sources evaded Dragon Fang’s defenses, rapidly rushing towards his body!

Rumble rumble rumble!

One Thunder Source shattered Dragon Fang’s spatial enchantment, and the second Thunder Source solidly smashed into Dragon Fang’s protective true essence.

An energy life form created by the power of thunder, just how terrifyingly strong were they? It was far more formidable than any previous thunderbolt!

Dragon Fang’s protective true essence instantly exploded and the savage power of thunder crashed into his body!

The audience cried out in alarm. Some young girls that had a secret crush on Dragon Fang closed their eyes, too afraid to look.

But at this time, brilliant purple flames suddenly erupted, gushing out from Dragon Fang’s body. These purple flames intertwined with the thunder light, casting the entire surrounding area in endless deep purple, shining and radiant, blinding to the eye!

Everyone subconsciously looked away before turning back.

“What happened!?”

“He crossed it!”

“He crossed it… but, his eye…”

“Dragon Fang overdrew his strength and received heavy damage to his eye. If this continues then he’ll crawl at most to 80,000 feet or so.”

At this time, on the Divine Seal Altar, the corner of Dragon Fang’s right eye had torn open. The blood vessels had been ripped apart and blood was flowing out.

The purple flames in the right eye had nearly been extinguished.

Practicing the Three Lives Pupils gave one greatly increased self-recovery abilities of the eyes. If the eyes were wounded, they could quickly restore give enough time. But now, this injured eye meant that Dragon Fang wouldn’t be able to continue for much longer.

“This is too horrifying. This is a killing formation of 27 Thunder Sources, and yet Dragon Fang was able to cross it. But, the price he paid was one of his eyes. He’s already 77,000 feet high up; he has high hopes of reaching 80,000 feet.”

In the skies above the Divine Seal Altar, Xiao Daochild was full of praise. He was well aware of just how terrifying the 27 Thunder Source killing formation was. At this time, Xiao Daochild’s thoughts moved and he looked downwards. He saw that 10,000 feet behind Dragon Fang, Lin Ming had also climbed into the purple thunder dominion.

“Mm, Lin Ming has also climbed up to the level of heavenly tribulation. Great!”

Chapter 1260 – Dragon Fang, Defeated

On the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step, Dragon Fang could be said as having grabbed the attention from the entire world. As for Lin Ming, he climbed up much slower so there were far less people paying attention to him. In this situation, people would usually be looking towards the first place person.

Now, Lin Ming also neared the purple thunder dominion, causing many people to turn back to him.

“Lin Ming can actually crawl up this high!”

“Fierce! I thought that 50,000 feet was his limit, but I never imagined he would also reach the 67,000 foot height. I wonder just how long Lin Ming can withstand the 33,000 feet of the thunder dominion?”

“The 33,000 foot thunder dominion? Hehe, Lin Ming is only at the early Divine Sea realm; he might fall before he can fully climb into the thunder dominion. Don’t forget, he has to withstand the attacks of heavenly tribulation as he approaches the thunder dominion.”

“Lin Ming is definitely inferior to Dragon Fang. His talent is already heaven-defying if he can truly climb into the thunder dominion. But, it is impossible for him to go any further than that, let alone cross the 27 Thunder Source killing formation at 70,000 feet.”

People didn’t place many expectations on Lin Ming. After all, Lin Ming’s cultivation was inferior to Dragon Fang’s.

As the people were discussing, there was a sparkling explosive sound as a snake-like beam of thunder separated from the purple sea and hurtled towards Lin Ming.

“It’s here! The first bolt of thunder!”

“Dragon Fang relied on his double layered spatial enchantment to block this. I wonder just how Lin Ming will defend against it this time! If he cannot block these arcs of thunder then he won’t be able to enter into the 33,000 foot thunder dominion!”

Everyone’s eyes widened, waiting to see what technique Lin Ming would use to deal with this onslaught! On the Divine Seal Altar, one’s body had to withstand the Empyrean pressure so they were unable to fly. Wanting to avoid the attack of thunder was impossible, they could only defend against it!

But, wanting to defend against this crazy and maniacal thunder was easier said than done. In the audience, none of the young elites sitting there had the confidence to do so.

Lin Ming looked up. At this time, the bolt of thunder had separated from the purple sea, and that incomparably wild and violent energy was hurtling towards him!

Lin Ming’s eyes sharpened. He opened the Gate of View that functioned in defense and also revolved the power of the supreme dragon bone. At that same time, he revolved his true essence to the limit and allowed that purple thunder to crash into his body!

At this moment, the entire audience was dumbfounded!

“He’s forcefully resisting the thunder tribulation!?”

“He’s too crazy! How can he withstand that and still live!?”

Lin Ming wasn’t Dragon Fang, who had spatial barriers set up around him to protect his body. Just the spatial enchantments were enough to block the majority of the attacks aimed at Dragon Fang. But Lin Ming used his protective true essence to do so, so the impact he had to withstand was countless times greater.

Bang!

As thunder washed over his body, Lin Ming suddenly shook. His protective true essence withstood half of the power of thunder before directly bursting apart. The power of thunder flushed into Lin Ming’s meridians where 90% of it was absorbed by the Heretical God Seedling.

As for the remaining power of thunder, it fizzled away within Lin Ming’s meridians. Lin Ming’s meridians had been tempered with the power of thunder multiple times in his life; this power of thunder simply couldn’t affect his body at all.

His body only trembled for the briefest moment before he continued climbing upwards.

“This is… am I seeing things?!”

“It’s over like that? Did that bolt of thunder really hit Lin Ming or did it veer away?”

Many martial artists glanced at each other in confusion, a bit bewildered. How could Lin Ming possibly resist this thunder tribulation in such a relaxed manner? After being struck by the thunder tribulation, his body only shook for a brief moment before he continued to climb upwards as if nothing had happened at all! This was far too abnormal!

They all suspected that they were seeing something, but as more bolts of thunder struck Lin Ming, his body shook several times before he continued upwards, still unaffected as before.

“The hell!?”

“This is too forceful!”

The entire audience was shocked. At this point in time, although they didn’t think that Lin Ming had completely exhausted himself like a lamp without oil, he should also have been nearing his limit. None of them thought he would be able to resist this thunder tribulation so easily.

But, what they didn’t know was that within Lin Ming’s inner world, the Heretical God Seedling there had crossed Ninefall and absorbed the power of heavenly tribulation.

That had been true heavenly tribulation – a tribulation of metal, wood, water, fire, earth, thunder, wind, yin, and yang. Nine different tribulations gathered as one, representing nine different source energies of the universe, uniting together to represent the Heavenly Dao!

Disregarding the annihilating strength of heavenly tribulation, just in terms of quality, the heavenly tribulation that Lin Ming crossed during his Ninefall was on a much higher level than this thunder dominion thunder tribulation on the Divine Seal Altar. After all, this Divine Seal Altar was only a replica created by Empyrean Vast Universe relying on a fragment of the ancient Divine Seal Altar’s artifact spirit. The inherent Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens within was extremely pale and incomplete.

“What method did Lin Ming use? It’s really unbelievable. All of these geniuses have endless amounts of methods that can leave one startled.”

“He might be using some rare treasure. I don’t believe that an early Divine Sea martial artist can use his body alone to resist thunder tribulation. He definitely has some tricky method that he is using. After this he will have to enter the purple sea and we’ll see whether or not he can reach 70,000 feet. Once he reaches that height, he will have to withstand the combined attacks of 27 Thunder sources. At that time, any tricks he uses will be meaningless.”

As everyone was speaking, Lin Ming officially entered the 33,000 foot thunder dominion!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The sound of thunder shook the heavens, piercing through the ears!

Within this world, there was nothing but boundless purple all around. Lin Ming was completely submerged within this purple thunder dominion!

“Thunder dominion… this is similar to the skies above the Sea of Miracles’ 8000 Miles Black Swamp. I wonder just what this heavenly tribulation is. If it’s simply limited to thunder tribulation, then that is nothing at all to me.”

A blazing thunder light filled the field of his vision. But, Lin Ming ignored all of this and continued climbing straight up the cliffs!

Chi chi chi!

An endless waterfall of thunder baptized Lin Ming’s body. Within Lin Ming’s inner world, within his meridians, everything was flooded with thunder!

“This brat, how is he doing this? Does have a thunder spirit body? Or perhaps he has a Thunder Laws-based transcendent divine might?”

Within Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, Empyrean Vast Universe had a startled expression. Lin Ming’s performance so far had exceeded his expectations.

However, he immediately shot down these guesses.

“No, that’s wrong. The power of thunder tribulation represents the will of the Heavenly Dao. It is fundamentally different from ordinary elemental lightning. No matter how wonderful a thunder-attribute cultivation method he practiced, it is impossible for him to absorb thunder tribulation to use for himself. That completely violates all common sense.”

Empyrean Vast Universe muttered. No matter how he thought about it, he couldn’t see just how Lin Ming accomplished what he did.

Even Empyrean Vast Universe was unable to think that Lin Ming had crossed heavenly tribulation. Moreover, the thunder tribulation from a 33 Layered Heavens Ninefall was beyond rare, ever since the most ancient of times.

Empyrean Vast Universe hadn’t crossed a 33 Layered Heavens Ninefall, thus he simply didn’t know what sort of change would happen in a Ninefall of that level.

And at this time, Dragon Fang had already climbed 80,000 feet up the Divine Seal Altar. He had broken past the boundary of 80,000 feet!

Just how exaggerated a result was climbing up 80,000 feet on the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step. Even Empyrean Vast Universe had to praise such an achievement.

“The successor of Three Lives Old Man is truly fierce. He is far more formidable and talented than all the disciples I have received in my millions of years of life! In terms of potential alone, I fear that even if he can’t compare with Frost Dream, he isn’t too far off.”

Empyrean Vast Universe looked at Empyrean Divine Dream. From the meaning of his words, it was clear he believed that Dragon Fang’s talent was worse than Frost Dream’s!

Frost Dream was the successor to Empyrean Divine Dream and also the current Saintess of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace. In the future there was an extremely high chance she would become an Empyrean!

Three Lives Old Man and Empyrean Divine Dream were characters of two completely different eras. When Empyrean Divine Dream’s strength grew and she arrived at the peak of the Divine Realm, Three Lives Old Man was already far too old. Thus, the two of them had never dueled to decide who was stronger and who was weaker.

But in Empyrean Vast Universe’s eyes, Empyrean Divine Dream was an unfathomable existence. He even suspected that she was far more formidable than Three Lives Old Man had been in his prime.

And Empyrean Divine Dream’s disciple, Fairy Maiden Frost Dream, was also immeasurably deep!

As Empyrean Vast Universe was thinking, at this moment, 80,000 feet up on the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step, countless Law runes began to shimmer into existence around Dragon Fang.

These multi-colored runes were different from the Laws that currently existed in the Divine Realm. No one was able to discern what they meant. After these Law runes appeared, they gathered together, forming stone tablets!

“These are… tablets condensed from the Laws!”

Everyone watched with shock and amazement as 80,000 feet up, the Law runes gathered together, forming 33 Law stone tablets!

Since ancient times, countless supreme elders of the Divine Realm, before their death, would spend a great deal of time and energy to carve their life’s comprehension of Law Concepts onto these stone tablets, forming totem tablets for their descendants to meditate on.

And now, the Great Dao in the heavens had gathered into 33 Dao tablets. This left everyone panic-stricken. If the world Laws formed Dao tablets, then wouldn’t these be tablets on the same level as chaos stones?

After climbing this far up the Divine Altar’s 33rd step, it was no longer only thunder tribulation, but Law tablets formed from runes of the heavens and earth. One would be directly bombarded by these tablets!

On the Divine Seal Altar, Dragon Fang watched as these 33 Dao tablets formed. He extracted the Dragon Fang Blade once more. His right hand was already stained red with blood, and trickles of blood flowed down the edge of the Dragon Fang Blade. The icy cold reflection and the crimson shine were gorgeous beyond compare!

He had lost vision in his right eye. But, his left eye still blazed with purple flames as brightly as before!

“33 Dao tablets! Even if I must be stopped here, I will fight with everything I have!”

At this time, Dragon Fang had already consumed over 60% of his true essence, but his fighting spirit had not dimmed in the least!

Woosh!

The first Dao tablet shot towards Dragon Fang!

This was a blood red Dao tablet. Dragon Fang thrust out his sword, “Space-time Vorpal Vibration Sword!”

Fusing the vibrating power of space into his sword, Dragon Fang’s sword pierced through the tablet, causing the tablet to explode. Dragon Fang’s body shook, his hand cracking even as he spat out a mouthful of blood!

“So strong!”

All of the blood vitality within Dragon Fang’s body tumbled over. In that strike just now, he had managed to block it but he still received an internal injury.

And at this time, the other 32 Dao tablets began to rush at him.

Dragon Fang’s pupils shrank. “Mirror Image Avatar!”

Dragon Fang divided into eight: one true self, seven avatars. Every avatar attacked a Dao tablet, crashing into them and being annihilated together!

However, there were still over 20 Dao tablets left!

“A Sword to Shatter the Void!”

Dragon Fang grit his teeth and slashed out with his sword once more. At once, three Dao tablets were cut in half. But, he was unable to resist the remaining Dao tablets. They all struck his body!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The Dao tablets exploded. Dragon Fang’s protective true essence exploded, his chest collapsed, and he wildly vomited blood.

In that final moment, the gray-clothed old man watching from deep within the Divine Seal Altar finally moved, rescuing the nearly unconscious Dragon Fang.

Thus, Dragon Fang was defeated!

Chapter 1262 – Slaughter of the Dao Tablets

To use heavenly tribulation to temper the body, that was simply unimaginable!

Heavenly tribulation was originally the power of heavenly retribution, able to annihilate all of existence. Even using various means to block it wouldn’t be enough, much less directly withstanding it with the body.

For instance, take Dragon Fang. Dragon Fang was already a genius at the limits of potential. But, let alone tempering his body with heavenly tribulation, just three or four explosive strikes by the Thunder Sources would have shattered his spatial enchantments.

It was also because of this reason that many people thought it was impossible for Lin Ming to be so abnormal. Moreover, the performance that Dragon Fang had displayed so far had surpassed Lin Ming’s. Taking a step back, even if Dragon Fang was inferior to Lin Ming, the difference couldn’t be that great.

So, how could one direct the heavenly tribulation to temper their body whilst the other was beaten up so ruthlessly?

“I don’t think this is Lin Ming’s own ability. Dragon Fang climbed up higher than Lin Ming, and he also climbed up in a much calmer fashion. But, upon entering the 33,000 foot thunder dominion and then encountering the Thunder Sources, Dragon Fang was suddenly inferior to Lin Ming. I think this is because Lin Ming must have some special type of shield or rare treasure that can absorb thunder!”

In the crowd, many people agreed with this view.

The timeless history of the Divine Realm was untraceable. Since ancient times, there were countless heaven-defying characters that had refined powerful treasures. It was possible that there were those capable of shielding against the thunder tribulation atop the Divine Seal Altar.

“Yes, that’s also what I am suspecting. Lin Ming resisted those 27 Thunder Sources far too easily, as if his body wasn’t attacked by thunder at all. Moreover, he cultivated the Thunder and Fire Laws from the start, so it wouldn’t be strange if he had some rare thunder-attribute treasure.”

“Treasure is a part of one’s strength but it is still an external force. If Lin Ming were to arrive at this step using a treasure, then even though that’s wonderful of him, it cannot be considered a miracle.”

“If it’s like that then it’s only Lin Ming’s luck that is better. The Divine Seal Altar’s test just happens to suit him.”

“Heh, luck is also part of one’s strength. Dragon Fang’s luck is just far too poor.”

As everyone was speaking, this opinion soon spread through the arena. Everyone could find this more acceptable if Lin Ming had some amazing treasure.

And at this time, Lin Ming had already crawled up another 1000 feet, nearing the 80,000 foot mark!

From 70,000 to 80,000 feet, the purple sea became even wilder and more violent. Thick arcs of thunder howled through the world like purple dragons. Thunder split the skies, revealing an endless and dangerous energy.

At this time, Lin Ming’s entire body was wrapped in thunder. From his head to his toes, he displayed the endless glory of thunder!

Lin Ming’s state seemed to confirm everyone’s guesses. Otherwise, how could he turn a blind eye to so much thunder?

“This boy! Just how many secrets does he have on him?”

In Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, Empyrean Vast Universe was muttering to himself. Upon discovering that Lin Ming was able to perceive the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens, Empyrean Vast Universe was sure that there was some secret on Lin Ming’s body, otherwise it was impossible for him to comprehend this sort of Concept.

And now, Lin Ming had broken through the 27 Thunder Source killing formation with an unstoppable momentum, even absorbing a portion of those Thunder Sources’ strength to use for himself. That had left Empyrean Vast Universe completely speechless. The power of heavenly tribulation was completely different from the power of ordinary elemental thunder, so how could Lin Ming refine it?

Suddenly, from his side, Empyrean Divine Dream quietly spoke. “Vast Universe, you seem to believe that Lin Ming had found some heaven-defying treasure, or perhaps he stumbled into some lucky chance, relying on some external force to advance to this point.”

“Didn’t he?” Empyrean Vast Universe turned to look at the white-clothed woman beside him. He didn’t think that a Divine Sea martial artist could rely on their strength alone to reach such a boundary.

As for strange treasures, there were all kinds. The Divine Realm was too broad and boundless and had existed for far too long. It was normal for there to be treasures that Empyrean Vast Universe wouldn’t be able to sense. Just speaking of the Magic Cube alone, there were only several people in the entire Divine Realm that knew of it. The Ancient Elysium Seal’s artifact spirit also knew of it, but the only reason that it had discovered the Magic Cube within Lin Ming’s body was because Lin Ming had displayed it when the artifact spirit was trying to destroy him.

The white-clothed woman faintly smiled. “Lucky chances, treasures, these are things that Lin Ming has in abundance. And as you think, they are definitely heaven-shaking. But, the reason he can absorb the power of heavenly tribulation and use it for himself isn’t necessarily because he is relying on some external force, but due to his own abilities…”

“Own abilities?” Empyrean Vast Universe knit his eyebrows together. “A thunder-attribute cultivation method on the level of a transcendent divine might can only stand on par with thunder tribulation in terms of the Laws, so even that can’t truly utilize thunder tribulation. Lin Ming is only at the early Divine Sea realm, but you think he used his own strength to refine that heavenly tribulation?”

Empyrean Vast Universe couldn’t think of any way this was possible. But then Empyrean Divine Dream said, “If Lin Ming were to have experienced heavenly tribulation himself… then from that basis, Lin Ming would be considered as having surpassed the Heavenly Dao Laws. If that is true, then if this were to be coordinated with a supernatural power of the thunder attribute, then there might be that possibility…”

As Empyrean Divine Dream spoke, Empyrean Vast Universe was shocked.

“Experienced heavenly tribulation!? You think he somehow managed to galvanize heavenly tribulation at the Divine Sea realm? How is that even possible?”

Heavenly tribulation was the punishment of the Heavenly Dao. When there was something that tried to surpass the constraints of the Heavenly Dao, the Heavenly Dao would summon heavenly tribulation against that existence in order to exterminate it.

Up to this point, Empyrean Vast Universe had withstood three heavenly tribulations.

The first time was when he had become an Empyrean. His first time experiencing heavenly tribulation had also been the most terrifying time.

The second and third times had been brought down when Empyrean Vast Universe created an Empyrean spirit treasure. The treasure itself had to withstand heavenly tribulation, not Empyrean Vast Universe.

For the first of the two treasure heavenly tribulations, because the quality of that treasure was insufficient, it had been destroyed and failed to come to completion. The second time the treasure was successfully refined, and the finished product of that had been the current Divine Seal Altar replica.

Besides creating an Empyrean spirit treasure, composing a transcendent divine might would also summon heavenly tribulation. Empyrean Vast Universe’s transcendent divine might was only half complete, thus it wasn’t yet able to summon heavenly tribulation.

As the saying went, the heavens would never seal off all roads. Heavenly tribulation always allowed a chance for survival, no matter how slim it was. Once one crossed heavenly tribulation, the benefits were tremendous!

There were many martial arts geniuses whose strength far surpassed those at their level, many with a Holy Lord or World King cultivation, who thought to arouse heavenly tribulation to temper their bodies and use this method to surpass the Heavenly Dao. But, they did not have the ability to offend the Heavenly Dao. So how could Lin Ming, who was only at the early Divine Sea realm, possibly accomplish something like that?

Empyrean Vast Universe felt that this was unimaginable. Even a child God Beast, equal to a human with a Divine Sea cultivation, would not be able to quicken heavenly tribulation.

Empyrean Divine Dream didn’t speak further. Instead, she silently watched as Lin Ming continued climbing up the Divine Seal Altar.

Empyrean Vast Universe also remained silent. He was well aware that if Divine Dream were to say something, she naturally had faith in her own words.

If all of this was true, then that youth known as Lin Ming was far too terrifying. His potential would be far superior to Dragon Fang’s, someone who had successfully cultivated the Three Lives Pupils.

At this time, the unconscious Dragon Fang finally woke up. He had been directly sent into a spirit ship from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. Through the spirit ship’s portholes, he had a direct view of the competition. Moreover, because he had a superior position and view, he could see everything much more clearly than the audience did.

He immediately spotted Lin Ming.

“This height is…”

Dragon Fang took a deep breath. He original believed that with his own strength, if he were to fight Lin Ming, there was an extremely high chance that he would win. But now, Lin Ming had actually crawled 77,000 feet up the 33rd step, only 3000 feet from his record.

And by the time Dragon Fang had reached that height, he had consumed over half his true essence and his bodily condition had been at its worst.

In contrast, Lin Ming’s entire body sparkled with sheets of thunder, as if his body had become liquid lightning. His blood vitality soared to the heavens, far stronger than his own.

“How is he doing this?”

Dragon Fang was confused and consternated. Lin Ming’s strength should be less than his own, and he also didn’t have the Three Lives Pupils.

When Lin Ming climbed up the Divine Seal Altar, the method he used was far more difficult than the method Dragon Fang had used. He climbed with far less ease than Dragon Fang.

And now, by the time Lin Ming climbed where he was, he was in his greatest state and had nearly reached the area where Dragon Fang had failed.

Dragon Fang, no matter how hard he thought, couldn’t figure out just what was happening.

“I wasn’t able to clearly see how you crossed that Thunder Source tribulation at 70,000 feet, but once you encounter the tribulation of Dao tablets at 80,000 feet, I will take a good look at just how you cross that.”

With things having arrived at this point, Dragon Fang believed that Lin Ming could reach 80,000 feet.

Time slowly passed. Lin Ming’s body roared, explosive crackling sounds coming from every joint in his body. Even his soul was flooded with an endless power of thunder.

And at this time, Lin Ming finally reached the 80,000 foot height. Once he crossed this height, he would have to resist the bombardment of 33 Dao tablets!

The 33 tablets were no longer just the power of thunder, but formed from the world Laws. They represented the will of the Heavenly Dao and were far more formidable than those Thunder Sources from before.

When Dragon Fang formed his spatial mirror images, each one was able to cut down three Thunder Sources. But against these Dao tablets, his spatial mirror images were only able to cut down one. The disparity between them could be imagined.

The audience watched everything with bated breath.

“80,000 feet! He finally reached 80,000 feet!”

“Hehe, I’ve been waiting for this moment. Lin Ming will soon have to withstand the tribulation of those 33 Dao tablets. Before, I suspected that Lin Ming was using some sort of special thunder-attribute treasure to block those Thunder Sources. If this is so, then now that he is facing these 33 tablets he will have to reveal his true strength.”

“It’s suspicious but the truth. Besides that, there is no other possible explanation. Lin Ming is strong, but his strength absolutely cannot reach such a degree. Now, the 33 Dao tablet tribulation he must withstand is different from the power of thunder. These Dao tablets are truly formed from the Laws themselves. If Lin Ming has any treasure, that treasure will be useless from now on. It will be impossible for him to pull any more tricks.”

As everyone spoke, at this time, countless Law runes began to appear around Lin Ming. These Law runes had multi-hued colors, each color representing different Laws. Moreover, the strangest thing was that these Laws were immensely different from the Laws currently existing in the Divine Realm.

Lin Ming looked at those ever-changing Law runes around him, a thoughtful look on his face. “These Law runes, they each represent the Laws of the 33 Layered Heavens. Among these are Laws of the essence gathering system, Laws from the body transformation technique, and even Laws from the Divine Dream Law… this could be called all-encompassing!”

Lin Ming still didn’t understand what the 33 Layered Heavens were. But now, he had an extremely faint idea. The 33 Layered Heavens represented every single energy system in the universe, and also the fusion of every martial path’s Great Dao!

If so, then only by perceiving the 33 Layered Heavens would he be able to walk down his road of martial arts and reach the peak!

Chapter 1268 – Empyrean Phantom

Was the ancient calamity a great war that swept through the entire Divine Realm?

This thought instantly passed through Lin Ming’s mind. The scale of this war must have reached unimaginable proportions; even the Heavenly Dao Laws had been changed.

Just what sort of terrifying war was this, that it could even alter the Heavenly Dao Laws?

At this time, Lin Ming saw a massive purple gold divine altar appear in the void. A tall and dashing man stood atop this divine altar, wearing pure white robes.

His right hand grasped a golden scepter and his left hand grasped an ancient and solemn-looking seal. At this moment, standing atop this altar, he seemed to be the only existence in the world.

Standing alone, he faced the army comprised of over 200 Empyreans and several million Holy Lords.

“That is Empyrean Divine Seal?”

Lin Ming immediately thought.

Empyrean Divine Seal was the leader of the Divine Realm 3.6 billion years ago!

Although he was extremely far away, in the instant that Lin Ming saw Empyrean Divine Seal, his mind shook. Facing such an existence, it was like he was facing the universe and all the ancient stars within.

Afterwards, the terrifying pressure crashed down upon him like a waterfall. Endless killing intent poured past him. Caught within this pressure, Lin Ming felt like a leaf in the water, about to be swallowed up at any time.

“Is this an Empyrean will? The memories of the Divine Seal Altar?”

Lin Ming was panic-stricken. Without a doubt, he could now confirm that the ancient Divine Seal Altar was Empyrean Divine Seal’s divine tool. And, the great seal in that Empyrean Divine Seal’s hand was the Ancient Elysium Seal.

3.6 billion years ago, Empyrean Divine Seal had led the masters of the ancient Divine Realm to withstand the great tribulation. He stood atop the Divine Seal Altar, leading all the troops!

After the great tribulation passed, the ancient Divine Seal Altar went missing. In truth, it might have even been struck by some immeasurable force and been extremely damaged, otherwise it was impossible for Empyrean Vast Universe to have obtained a wisp of the ancient Divine Seal Altar’s artifact spirit to refine the Divine Seal Altar replica.

As for the Ancient Elysium Seal, it was used by Empyrean Divine Seal to suppress some unknown existence. This suppression had continued for 3.6 billion years. It was hard to imagine just what was suppressed beneath the Ancient Elysium Seal that could survive for such a long time!

Lin Ming had all these suspicions but no time to ponder on them. The pressure atop the Divine Seal Altar was too terrifying. The surging pressure ruthlessly crashed into Lin Ming. His body, soul, and inner world all simultaneously withstood the baptism of this horrifying pressure.

His divine sense seemed as if it would tear apart and his inner world was on the verge of collapse. This was the pressure that Empyrean Divine Seal left behind in the past when he once stood atop the Divine Seal Altar.

This was a pressure created by the martial arts will and thoughts of hundreds of Empyreans and millions of Holy Lord and World King powerhouses, controlling all of existence!

Even though 3.6 billion years had passed, even though this was only a dream of a wisp from the ancient Divine Seal Altar’s artifact spirit that Empyrean Divine Seal had created, Lin Ming still found this nearly impossible to withstand!

Under this pressure, Lin Ming’s entire forehead was dripping with sweat and the veins on his arm bulged up like worms.

Within Empyrean Divine Seal’s hand, that solemn and thick Ancient Elysium Seal slowly floated into the air. From that seal, 100,000 foot beams of silver radiance spread out, recklessly flying through the air. A divine might spread out, passing through the universe.

Millions of Divine Realm masters gathered, all of them solemn and grim. None of them made a single sound. Strong astral winds roared through the air, sweeping through everything. At this time, their thoughts gathered into a terrifying vortex, breaking through space itself!

Space and time collapsed, all living beings trembled!

Lin Ming struggled to continue onwards. Nearly all the blood vessels in his body were crushed but he still pressed forwards, a step at a time.

This was incomparably strenuous. Underneath this pressure, his will seemed as if it were being hammered down by a divine hammer.

“What is Lin Ming experiencing?”

“What is it? I can’t see!”

Many people discovered something strange with Lin Ming; it was apparent he was withstanding some great tribulation. In the tribulations of 70,000 feet, 80,000 feet, and 90,000 feet, they had been able to clearly see what was happening. But now, none of them were aware of just what Lin Ming was experiencing.

“In the final 10,000 feet of the Divine Seal Altar, everyone experiences something different. But since ancient times, there has never been a Divine Sea powerhouse that has managed to climb up this last 10,000 feet. It is hard to predict what Lin Ming could possibly be experiencing right now.”

“Although we can’t see, for it to be this hard for Lin Ming, it should be some sort of tribulation that we cannot hope to imagine!”

Let alone the ordinary spectators, even the high level figures in the reserved area, and even the World King Xiao Daochild himself didn’t know what Lin Ming was experiencing at this time.

Time seemed to slow down to a near standstill. Lin Ming saw a great war sweep across the heavens and earth. He saw countless trillions of lives perish. He saw ancient stars explode into nothing and worlds collapse to pieces. He saw phoenixes rise from nirvana, he saw the corpses of Azure Dragons litter the ground, and he even saw the blood of God Beasts form rivers of blood flowing to the ends of the world. Even Empyreans fell from the sky here. As for Holy Lords, their lives were as frail as dust, vanishing at every turn.

Such a scene was boundless, vigorous, bleak, tragic!

Although he was faintly aware of all these scenes, he couldn’t see it clearly happening. But, that terrifying killing intent, that gathered will, still attacked Lin Ming’s mind, nearly causing his divine sense to collapse!

“Grandmist battle spirit!”

Lin Ming shouted out loud. He displayed his grandmist battle spirit, using his sword of will to open a path in his mind!

The dark gold sword of will struck that sea of killing intent!

Peng!

As that normally unstoppable sword of will struck the sea of killing intent, Lin Ming felt his spiritual sea violently shake. A soul-tearing pain ripped through him. However, he didn’t give up. He endured this torturous pain, continuing to open a path outwards with his sword of will. Otherwise, underneath this pressure, it would be impossible for him to climb up.

Time slowly passed. A quarter hour, one hour, two hours, four hours…

Lin Ming forcefully relied on his solid unyielding will to crawl to 99,000 feet up the last step of the Divine Seal Altar!

At this time, his face was paper white and his entire body was soaked with sweat. He had overdrawn his true essence and his sword of will had dimmed to almost nothing at all. It was hard to imagine just what sort of tribulation he had experienced on his journey here.

Even though Lin Ming’s foundation was extremely deep, he had finally reached his limit. He was relying on his will alone to reach this far and continue struggling upwards.

His fingers were worn away, and he had bitten his lips so hard they were bleeding. Sweat blurred his eyes, and all sounds faded away from Lin Ming’s ears. He simply clenched his teeth, continuing forwards, unstoppable!

99,500 feet…

99,600 feet…

He would soon reach the top!

At this moment, the entire audience was roused into a frenzy.

“Is Lin Ming really going to reach the top!?”

“It’s hard to say. At the final moment he might even experience an even more terrifying tribulation! Just like the tribulations at 70,000 feet, 80,000 feet, and 90,000 feet!”

“I have no idea just what a tribulation at 100,000 feet would be like. No one can tell whether or not Lin Ming can cross that.”

Although no one knew just what Lin Ming had experienced, they could all see that he was relying on his dogged and stubborn will to climb up this far. He had already long surpassed his limits!

If he were to experience another tribulation at 100,000 feet, it would likely be even more terrifying than the one at 90,000 feet. For Lin Ming in his current state, it would be impossible for him to cross it.

At 90,000 feet, Lin Ming had relied on breaking through to the middle Divine Sea to create a miracle. Now, Lin Ming’s only hope was to break through to the late Divine Sea realm, otherwise there was nothing left for him but defeat.

But after just breaking through to the middle Divine Sea realm, it was clearly impossible for him to break through to the late Divine Sea realm right after.

“99,900 feet!”

“This is the final stretch!”

Everyone held their breath.

And at this time, the heaven and earth origin energy around the Divine Seal Altar suddenly began to swell up in chaos. A terrifying eruption of energy broke out. The massive Divine Seal Altar trembled, as if a True Dragon were awakening from deep within.

“Is there really another tribulation?”

“If there is, just who can withstand it?”

Everyone was feeling sorry for Lin Ming at this time. If there really was a tribulation at 100,000 feet, then this Divine Seal Altar was simply too abnormal. It was impossible for a human to climb up it.

“What is that!?”

Someone suddenly pointed to the highest precipice of the Divine Seal Altar.

“On the edge of the 33rd step, there’s a figure there!”

Everyone was incomparably shocked and horrified. At the highest peak of the Divine Seal Altar, there was the phantom of a tall man in white clothes. He held his hands together, as if he were standing alone in the endless flow of time, looking at the future and the past, becoming one with the boundless world.

Although this was only a phantom, the moment that he appeared, the world seemed to fall under his control, the master of the heavens and the earth, the ruler of existence. The billions of people present all had a deep impulse to fall to their knees in prostration, worshipping him.

Even Xiao Daochild, floating in the skies, was sucked in by this power, unable to continue flying!

Xiao Daochild was shocked. He rapidly formed some seals, dropping down hundreds of thousands of feet before stabilizing himself. He slowly fell down and finally landed on the ground.

Flying was prohibited above the Divine Seal Altar. But, that was only for young disciples. Xiao Daochild was a World King, thus he had the ability to fly. Yet in front of this phantom, he couldn’t even fly at all. How could he not be shocked!?

“This person is…”

Xiao Daochild’s mind raced. Even though this was only a phantom, his aura and his momentum were far more formidable than the average Empyrean’s! Xiao Daochild could not imagine just who would have such divine might!

This was also an inevitable matter. This ancient Empyrean was a figure from 3.6 billion years ago. Let alone Xiao Daochild, not even Empyrean Vast Universe knew who it was. If it weren’t for Lin Ming finding the Ancient Elysium Seal deep underneath Immemorial Imperial City, then he would never have known of the name of Empyrean Divine Seal.

“Who is he? What a terrifying and alarming aura! Facing him is like facing the endless ancient stars!”

“Just a phantom is like this. What would his true self be like?”

“I have no idea! Is this Empyrean Vast Universe?”

“It absolutely isn’t Empyrean Vast Universe. I wonder just which ancient king this is!”

As everyone was discussing, on the Divine Seal Altar, the nearly unconscious Lin Ming also saw this phantom.

Others might not know, but Lin Ming was well aware of who this was – Empyrean Divine Seal!

Empyrean Divine Seal’s phantom stood right in front of him. There was only a 100 foot distance separating them!

“Em…pyrean….Di…vine….Seal….”

Lin Ming’s lips moved, but no sound came out. At this time, he could only look at Empyrean Divine Seal, the corners of his mouth overflowing with blood.

The white-clothed phantom slowly walked forwards to the edge of the Divine Seal Altar. Lin Ming looked up but couldn’t clearly make out his appearance. All he could feel was that this phantom exuded a vast and ancient aura, as if he had stepped through the solemn and endless flow of time, bridging the gap of 3.6 billion years between then and now!

The phantom of Empyrean Divine Seal lowered his head to look down at Lin Ming. His eyes were as deep and profound as the void, impossible to see through.

Although Lin Ming didn’t understand Empyrean Divine Seal, he still felt sincere admiration towards him. This was because he shouldered the history of the Divine Realm 3.6 billion years ago!

Lin Ming wanted to open his mouth and respectfully call out senior, but he couldn’t make a single sound.

Then, at this time, Empyrean Divine Seal indifferently raised a hand and began to slowly draw something in the void…

Chapter 1269 – The Summit

Empyrean Divine Seal’s finger cut through the void, leaving behind a purple golden path of shimmering light. These lights gathered together, forming a strange golden purple rune.

Lin Ming froze for a moment. This purple golden rune seemed to exude some strange magical charm, making him fall into it.

This is…

His heart wildly shook!

Empyrean Divine Seal’s finger did not stop. After drawing up the first rune, he continued to draw up a second, a third, a fourth…

Every time he drew a new rune he did so slowly. The path of light he carved into the air was simple and profound, as if it contained the highest truths of this world.

The entire process was soundless, without a single word spoken.

At this time, the world had faded away from around Lin Ming’s eyes, leaving nothing behind but these mysterious runes.

In truth, he didn’t understand just what Empyrean Divine Seal was drawing. But, he could faintly feel that these runes he drew were incomparably precious treasures, containing the mysteries of the Great Dao within them!

Lin Ming entered a complete ethereal state. Besides Empyrean Divine Seal, everyone lost all meaning.

In the audience, the billions of spectators also saw this scene.

“Who is that phantom? What is he doing?”

“That could be a divine soul mark that an ancient supreme elder once left behind in the Divine Seal Altar. After hundreds of millions and even billions of years it still remains in existence, continuing onwards in perpetuity! What is disturbed because of Lin Ming? Heavens, that is unbelievable!”

“It is said that when an unrivalled genius climbs up the final stretch of the Divine Seal Altar, they will arouse a world phenomenon. Vast Universe Heavenly Palace’s Vast Cosmos climbed up the last 10,000 feet of the Divine Seal Altar during the Divine Transformation realm and also triggered the appearance of a phenomenon. This ancient phantom is likely the world phenomenon Lin Ming caused by climbing up the Divine Seal Altar!”

“Inconceivable. He has actually alarmed an ancient supreme elder! And he seems to be writing something in the air!”

“He is indeed writing something, but I can’t see what it is. It’s like my vision has been blocked by some strange power!”

Although the audience couldn’t clearly see these runes being drawn, they could see that the phantom was drawing them. But, in the process of drawing them, distortions appeared in the surrounding power of the Heavenly Dao Laws, causing all of them to be unable to clearly see what was happening.

“Are those words? Runes? Can anyone see what is being written?”

Many people widened their eyes as best they could, deploying any mystical sight skill in their arsenal to see just what this Empyrean phantom was writing. But, the more they tried to look, the dimmer their vision became, until they couldn’t even see the finger of that Empyrean phantom.

“What a pity!”

“I can’t see!”

Everyone was able to guess that this Empyrean phantom was likely some outstanding existence amongst all Empyreans. Otherwise, it was impossible for a phantom to leave behind such a terrifying pressure.

The words, the runes he carved might contain the truths of the Great Dao. If they could remember them then their benefits would be endless!

“If we can’t see, can Lin Ming see them?”

“That phantom seems to be deliberately drawing these characters. Is it doing so for Lin Ming to see?”

As everyone was discussing, their hearts were beating with fear and also envy.

A purple gold divine light came shrouding down like tens of thousands of fluttering silk ribbons. Lin Ming and that Empyrean phantom were covered within this light, and no one could clearly see what was happening on the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step.

And within this brilliant blazing light, Lin Ming felt his entire body become weightless. He was only able to watch blankly as these mysterious runes flew into his body. Some buried themselves into his flesh and blood, some fell into his soul force, and some flew into his inner world.

“What is this? Laws? Information? Or both?”

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath.

In that moment, the light vanished and the phantom of Empyrean Divine Seal also disappeared along with it. There was nothing left but a dim shimmering purple gold light that quietly scattered away like endless flower petals…

In that final moment, Lin Ming felt a strong will from this fading light, unyielding and indomitable…

Empyrean Divine Seal…

Lin Ming’s thoughts were extremely complex. When Empyrean Divine Seal vanished, the overwhelming pressure from the sky completely disappeared and everyone was restored to tranquility.

“What happened just now?”

“The ancient supreme elder’s phantom has disappeared, and the runes he carved have vanished also.”

No one had been able to see those purple gold runes submerge into Lin Ming’s body, thus no one knew what happened. The final 10,000 feet of the Divine Seal Altar was completely different from their expectations.

They thought that Lin Ming would have to withstand some terrifying heavenly tribulation, and perhaps he would even be defeated, but they never thought this would be the result.

Lin Ming breathed in, grabbing the extremely rough walls of the Divine Seal Altar once more, then began to climb upwards, one step at a time!

100 feet… 90 feet… 80 feet… 70 feet… 60 feet… 50 feet…

Lin Ming was only a few moments away. But, he did not hurry himself. Every step he took was as stable and steady as the rivers and mountains.

The billions of spectators all held their breath, each and every one of them with their eyes glued onto Lin Ming.

At this final moment, time seemed to slow to molasses.

Lin Ming firmly reached out his right hand and grasped the precipice of the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step.

Pulling his right hand, he seemed to conjure up every last shred of strength in his body as he slowly pulled himself up.

His arms were the first to reach flat ground. Then his chest, his waist, and then his legs. Lin Ming half knelt on top of the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step before slowly standing up.

The Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step – he had made it!

In that moment, Lin Ming felt as if his entire life had been baptized. He stood 3.3 million feet in the air, overlooking the endless rolling lands, peering into the vast galaxy!

At this time, his body, his soul, his inner world, everything seemed to transform, becoming purer, slowly fusing together.

“He did it, he finally reached the top!”

“It’s a miracle!”

The billions of spectators didn’t cheer at the start. They were all still lost in their shock, unable to utter a single word

But after a silence that lasted for several breaths of time, the entire area burst out with deafening cheers!

“He mounted the Divine Seal Altar! This is like a dream! Lin Ming is the peerless proud son of heaven of the Divine Realm that only appears once every million years!”

“His talent and potential are incalculable. In the future there are high hopes he will become an Empyrean.”

“He surpasses an Empyrean descendant!”

When the numerous spectators said that Lin Ming surpassed an Empyrean descendant, they referred to his potential. When Lin Ming climbed up the Divine Seal Altar to reach the top, the truth was that it wasn’t because of his strength, but because he alone had crossed a 33 Layered Heavens Ninefall and experienced a nine by nine heavenly tribulation. Otherwise, it would have been impossible for him to mount the summit of the Divine Seal Altar.

In Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, Empyrean Vast Universe looked down at Lin Ming as he stood on the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step. He blinked several times, opening his mouth but finally not saying anything.

After several dozen breaths of time in silence, he then slowly said, “Divine Dream, that final phantom… was that Empyrean Divine Seal?”

Empyrean Divine Dream nodded. She said in a soft voice, “I have never seen him before, but I could feel his aura. I shouldn’t be mistaken.”

“Mm. I could also feel it a little. Really, that was quite shocking. I used a fragment of the ancient Divine Seal Altar, as well as countless timeless god stones, in order to refine the current Divine Seal Altar. Even so, for the Divine Seal Altar to be able to project Senior Divine Seal’s phantom, his strength must have reached an unfathomable boundary. Perhaps the word Empyrean alone is insufficient to describe his strength. I wonder what Senior Divine Seal finally wrote in the air?”

Empyrean Vast Universe sighed with deep emotion. Although they were both called Empyreans, the truth was that he couldn’t compare in the slightest with Empyrean Divine Seal. In truth, Empyrean Divine Seal already surpassed the limits of an Empyrean.

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “I only saw a tiny portion of Senior Divine Seal’s handwriting. It should be the highest Laws of the 33 Layered Heavens and possibly some information too, describing the great war that happened 3.6 billion years ago.”

3.6 billion years ago was an incomparably glorious era from ages past. Although there were Empyreans that could live for 100 million years, there were still many things that were lost in the endless river of history.

This was just like a mortal that could live for a hundred years. How could they know what happened 36,000 years ago? Moreover, after that great calamity, many masters perished from the skies, and even the martial arts world had been struck back down to its fundamentals. Many things had to be redeveloped from the beginning.

Some secrets would have disappeared in the infinite flow of time, and only some peak characters of the Divine Realm would know of them.

As Empyrean Divine Dream mentioned the 33 Layered Heavens, Empyrean Vast Universe frowned and said, “I am still not sure just what lucky chance Lin Ming encountered that allowed him to access the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. Because the Heavenly Dao Laws changed long ago, that is something that should have been cut off from the Divine Realm. These Laws are almost impossible to comprehend now.”

Empyrean Vast Universe realized that Lin Ming had come into contact with the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens before he had climbed up the Divine Seal Altar. Otherwise, it would have been impossible for him to become aware of it.

Empyrean Divine Dream spookily said, “Lin Ming indeed must have comprehended the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens before he started climbing the Divine Seal Altar. But, that is not necessarily because of some lucky chance, but perhaps because he himself was thoroughly enlightened about it.”

Empyrean Vast Universe was shocked. “He thoroughly enlightened himself on it? How could that be possible? Underneath the limits of the Divine Realm’s Heavenly Dao Laws, it is impossible to access the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens.”

“There is always a possibility. For instance… if Lin Ming were to break through a 33 Layered Heavens Ninefall and withstand a baptism of the Heavenly Dao Laws, he would come into contact with the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. At that time, he might have even withstood the power of heavenly tribulation. If that is true, then it can also be explained how Lin Ming was able to use heavenly tribulation…”

As one of the leaders of all Empyreans within the Divine Realm, Empyrean Divine Dream’s understandings of a 33 Layered Heavens Ninefall were far greater than Empyrean Vast Universe’s.

After Empyrean Vast Universe listened to this, he looked at her with amazement. “33 Layered Heavens… Ninefall!?”

When Empyrean Vast Universe crossed Ninefall himself, he had stopped at a 30 Layered Heavens Ninefall, a 90 mile origin energy cloud.

Thus, he was not clear on what it meant to cross a 33 Layered Heavens Ninefall.

If it were really as Empyrean Divine Dream said, then Lin Ming’s future achievements would be hard to imagine!

Of course, Lin Ming still fell far short of being on the same level as those ancient supreme elders. After all, the achievements of these characters were not based on just how many Layered Heavens they crossed during Ninefall.

This was because Ninefall was merely the beginning of a martial cultivator’s road. There were many boundaries afterwards, and in order to take a solid step forwards within these boundaries, one needed to pile up countless lucky chances and resources before they could hope to be successful.

Since ancient times, for the birth of an Empyrean, talent, destiny, resources, and inheritances were all indispensable.

“Since Lin Ming disturbed the phantom of Empyrean Divine Seal, then in a sense he obtained the recognition of Empyrean Divine Seal. If I’m not wrong, that must be because of the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. If this were 3.6 billion years ago, Lin Ming might have even be received as a disciple of Empyrean Divine Seal.” Empyrean Divine Dream suddenly said.

Empyrean Divine Seal was a peak existence who cultivated essence, energy, and divine.

Chapter 1270 – Bustling Like A City

In reaching the summit of the Divine Seal Altar, this had been the most exhausting battle Lin Ming had gone through so far. From start to finish, it had taken him seven days and seven nights.

In these seven days and seven nights, besides a pill that he had taken, he had completely relied upon his own natural restorative abilities.

After exhausting himself over seven days, at the final moment he was like a lamp without oil. At the last 100,000 foot pass, if it were any casual test and not the phantom of Empyrean Divine Seal, then Lin Ming would have lost.

Lin Ming didn’t remember how or when he came down from the Divine Seal Altar. All he knew was that he slumped over and instantly fell into a state of deep sleep.

And outside, billions of people were wildly screaming! News about this competition on the Divine Seal Altar spread like a snowstorm throughout the entire Divine Realm.

The billions of spectators present had come from 100 great worlds as well as countless small worlds and hidden worlds. They were all high level figures, either sect Elders, reclusive sages, or outstanding young elites.

Their ability to spread news far surpassed the ordinary person’s. For a time, the name of Lin Ming and Dragon Fang were extremely dazzling. In particular Lin Ming; his fame resounded through the world!

Of course, to many people, they had no idea just what sort of concept mounting the summit of the Divine Seal Altar was. This was because the Divine Seal Altar wasn’t very famous to begin with.

An Empyrean was synonymous with mystery. People didn’t know all the Empyreans in existence, moreover there was quite a large number of Empyrean Heavenly Palaces in the Divine Realm. In terms of Heavenly Palaces alone, there were 100-200 that were well known by most, not including those Empyreans living in deep seclusion like Three Lives Old Man.

With so many Empyreans, how many people would know about a random Empyrean spirit treasure?

Although the Divine Seal Altar had been revealed to the public before, that was 100,000 years ago, or even several hundred thousand years ago. People had already forgotten about such a distant matter.

Let alone the disciples of ordinary Holy Lands, even Nether Limitless didn’t know how difficult it was to reach the top of the Divine Seal Altar.

Many people only knew that Lin Ming was the top participant from the semifinals at Gravemoon Star. As for what degree he had reached, it was hard for them to imagine.

……

Far away, there was an independent greater dimension. This dimension was a great world that was forcefully opened up by an extreme character using their titanic supernatural powers. It was billions of miles long and wide, far larger than the Sky Spill Continent and Holy Demon Continent combined!

It was already astounding for a martial artist to open up their own dimensional realm, much less a greater dimension.

In this separate world, there was a palace built from white jade. This palace was filled with flowers and trees as if the inside was endless grasslands. Immortal cranes flew above lotuses and white monkeys danced among the fruit trees. Beautiful spirit springs sprung up all over. These springs were not formed from ordinary water, but wine nectar. If a mortal were to drink this, they would be able to extend their lifespan by several times.

In this heavenly fairyland, there was a group of lightly dressed women. Amidst enchanting music, they gracefully danced. Each one had alluring looks and perfectly built bodies made for obsession.

These women all had a cultivation at the Divine Sea realm. Moreover, their talent was very good. However, they were just singing and dancing maids, serving the guests of their master, who were a dozen or so young men and women.

These dozen plus people all had extraordinary auras; they were clearly outstanding individuals.

“I hear that the semifinals are finally over.” A red-haired youth smiled, carrying a wine cup in his hands.

“Oh? How is it? Are there any interesting opponents?” Beside the red-haired youth, a man in silver battle armor lazily asked as he ate some grapes.

To dare speak with this sort of tone, to refer to the martial artists of the Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds who had been selected through trial after trial as ‘interesting’, their status was easily guessed – they were Empyrean descendants!

Empyrean descendants were all divided between high and low. There were strong and weak Empyreans, just like the difference between ordinary World Kings and Great Worlds Kings. In addition, even between the disciples of Empyreans, there were number one ranked disciples and also last ranked disciples.

According to the customs of the First Martial Meeting, when a new number one disciple was about to appear to an Empyrean, that Empyrean would also step forwards to hold the First Martial Meeting. Of these Empyreans that held the First Martial Meeting, their strength on average was extremely high. Even the weakest among them would be at the same level as Empyrean Vast Universe.

The weaker Empyreans would not hold the First Martial Meeting. Rather, their descendants would join the First Martial Meeting held by other Empyreans.

These dozen plus people were mostly in this situation. As Empyrean descendants, they didn’t need to undergo the preliminaries and semifinals, and could go straight to the finals.

“There are indeed some interesting matches that have appeared. On Whitelight Star’s martial field, the first ranked participant – Blood Carnage. On Yellow Net Star’s martial field, the first and second ranked participants – Hong Yu and Chao Guang. And of course, the ones with the greatest limelight so far are the first and second ranked participants of Gravemoon Star’s martial field – Lin Ming and Dragon Fang. Especially that Lin Ming. It’s said that he even surpasses us Empyrean descendants.”

“Surpasses us?”

Many of those present chuckled. “It’s just the ramblings of people who have never seen the wider world. They haven’t even seen the side of a Heavenly Palace and yet they dare to do something so ridiculous like comparing someone to us Empyrean descendants. How laughable!”

“There’s no need to care about those common mortals. In the Divine Realm First Martial Meetings, it has always been Empyrean descendants that have ruled the rankings. The so-called geniuses of the great worlds can struggle as much as they want for the Earth Proclamation, but there is no room for them to stand on the Heaven Proclamation.”

Empyrean descendants were all proud and lofty individuals. They naturally wouldn’t be willing to believe that some common person was able to surpass them.

However, the youth who spoke up before added again, “It’s different this time. That Lin Ming is extremely fierce. I heard that he climbed up to the 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar and created a miracle.”

As this youth finished speaking, another person who was sitting amongst the group nearly spat out the wine he was drinking.

“Shore Feather, what do you think?”

“Is the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step really that exaggerated?”

“That’s right, the Divine Seal Altar is Empyrean Vast Universe’s spirit treasure, right? Aren’t you from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace?”

The young man called Shore Feather opened his mouth, his complexion pale. If one didn’t come from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, even if they knew that it was difficult to climb up the Divine Seal Altar, they wouldn’t truly understand until they witnessed it with their own eyes. But as a disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, Shore Feather was profoundly aware of just how ridiculously abnormal it was for a Divine Sea realm martial artist to climb up the Divine Seal Altar!

“Ex-exaggerated? It’s more than exaggerated!” Shore Feather shouted out in his heart. Since Lin Ming had joined the First Martial Meeting, then he definitely was at the Divine Sea realm!

He grit his teeth and said, “You can all continue eating. I’ll be returning first.”

Shore Feather’s reaction was to put down his wine cup and return. He wanted to confirm whether this matter was true or false.

As for the others, they glanced at each other, puzzlement in their eyes. Wasn’t Shore Feather’s response just blown out of proportion?

“This Lin Ming can have him respond in such a ridiculous manner?”

“About the Divine Seal Altar, I have heard some things. The Divine Seal Altar is mainly a test of one’s potential. Can this Lin Ming’s potential surpass our own?”

“As if I’d believe that. In any case, the finals will soon begin. I’ll see for myself just what sort of freak this Lin Ming is.”

“That’s right. We’ll know sooner or later. Come, let us continue drinking.”

………..

Crimson Light World, Ancient Phoenix Clan Headquarters.

The Ancient Phoenix Clan was originally a highly ranked influence based on the Crimson Light World. The Ancient Phoenix Clan Headquarters were usually bustling with people. The skies would be flooded with powerful mounts, glorious spirit boats, divine carriages, and countless Divine Lords and even Holy Lords.

But in these past days, over a hundred times more martial artists had come to visit the Ancient Phoenix Clan!

The entire sky was occupied by various mounts and spirit boats.

And the martial artists that came all had an above average strength.

Originally, it was mostly Divine Lords and some Holy Lords. But now, it was mostly Holy Lords, half-step World Kings, and even World King level powerhouses!

There were even some weaker Holy Lords that were ashamed to enter the gates as they saw all these peak Holy Lord powerhouses and even World King Holy Land spirit ships shuttling through the skies.

Without a doubt, all of these people had come for Lin Ming.

Most of the Holy Lord level characters had simply come to befriend and establish connections with the Ancient Phoenix Clan. They were also well aware of their status. What sort of character was Lin Ming now that they could easily see him?

And amidst this crowd, there was a small group of extremely low cultivation individuals, with the strongest amongst them being at the late Divine Lord realm. Even so, these people still had a place to stand in the Ancient Phoenix Clan and they were also treated courteously.

These were people from the Good Fortune Great World’s Unbroken Cult.

“Aiya, thanks to the blessings of those two female disciples, we’ve become honored guests here.”

The black-clothed man leading the group commented. He was the Founder of the Unbroken Cult. Normally, he would be considered someone with some degree of status, but here in the current Ancient Phoenix Clan he wasn’t even worth a fart. Each of these other visitors were more amazing than the last. Let alone these people’s subordinates, the Unbroken Cult Founder couldn’t even contend with their followers.

However, these great people couldn’t even see Lin Ming; they might not even have the chance to see the high level figures of the Ancient Phoenix Clan! They could only greet the Internal Affairs Envoy, the Disciplinary Elder, the Merit Elder, and so forth.

“Truly, this scene is a bit too ridiculous.”

“We really are the frogs in a well. This time can be regarded as us gaining a great deal of experience.”

Several Elders sighed with emotion. And beside them, Yu Youming was also silent, his mood extremely complex. Not too long ago, he was considered a chosen pride of heaven. From birth until adulthood, he had been shrouded in the halo of being called a genius. He had enjoyed the worship of countless others, but now, he was just a joke compared to Lin Ming.

“I must practice as hard as I can. Although I might not reach his level, one day, I too will have the Unbroken Cult be so lively because of me!”

Yu Youming gripped his fists together, setting down this vow in his heart. However, the truth was that in the Divine Realm there were countless young martial artists that made similar pledges. But, only an extremely small proportion of them were able to succeed in their dreams. Many of them perished, their wishes and hopes unfulfilled.

The road of martial arts was incomparably brutal.

The Ancient Phoenix Clan could be considered as being at the height of their glory at this moment. Several Highest Elders, including even the current Patriarch, were growing tired from greeting the endless stream of guests. Although they were only here to curry favor with the Ancient Phoenix Clan, each and every one of them was a powerful figure, thus they naturally couldn’t be treated coldly.

However, as they greeted these guests, they were also a bit worried, because since Lin Ming returned he still hadn’t awoken.

Up until now, over 10 days had passed.

Huo Violentstone was especially worried. Lin Ming had slept for too long and the reason for it was also unknown.

In these days he had been investigating the reason for Lin Ming’s sleep, but nothing came of it.

Even Xiao Daochild made a trip here, but he couldn’t figure out the reason either. If the reason was fatigue, that would be easy to understand. But with Lin Ming’s recovery abilities, that was simply impossible.

Chapter 1275 – Law Test

Vast Universe World was an independent world opened up by an extreme powerhouse using their tremendous supernatural powers.

Here, there existed a massive arena. This arena was completely formed from thundercrush steel as well as timeless god stones. It was so tough that even a Divine Lord master couldn’t leave the shallowest of marks.

All around this arena, there were massive stands able to hold hundreds of millions of people. Just these stands alone extended 10 miles into the skies. But, these stands were still much smaller than the temporary stands created by Xiao Daochild at Gravemoon Star. This was also one of the reasons why the admission tickets were so rare.

A hundred miles away from this arena, there were groups of palaces. Each palace stretched out for an extremely long distance, and each one was the epitome of luxury and grace, with fine carvings and beautiful finishings. This was also where the geniuses of the 3000 great worlds would be located.

After a month and a half and several great void shifts, Lin Ming finally arrived at Vast Universe World, where the finals would be held.

“This is Vast Universe World!”

Lin Ming flew down from the spirit ship and discovered that the heaven and earth origin energy on Vast Universe World was much more chaotic and strong than the heaven and earth origin energy on Atlas World or True Martial World!

For a genius like Lin Ming, having a special training area wouldn’t have too great of an effect right now. But, there were some more basic martial artists that could only train outside, and thus they were greatly influenced by their surroundings.

If one was to cultivate in Vast Universe World, wanting to control the circulation of origin energy was much more difficult. But, if one continued to train here, their achievements would also be greater.

Before Huo Violentstone arrived here, he had already contacted one of the organizers from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace to determine where their temporary residence would be; it was the 52nd palace.

According to the arrangements of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, the first 30 palaces were for Empyrean descendants to prepare themselves. In other words, the direct disciples of Empyreans.

Follow that, palace 31 to palace 60 were for the first place contestants of the various semifinals areas.

From palace 61 to palace 1000, they were for various disciples of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. These people weren’t Empyrean descendants but core disciples as well as the disciples of the older Empyrean descendants. As for the other participants and core disciples, they were housed in even lower ranked palaces.

Many Empyrean descendants were millions of years old or even 10 million years old. Among them, the weakest were comparable to ordinary World Kings and many of them were stronger than Great World Kings. There were even some that were half-step Empyreans!

There were a great number of these people, and their top disciple was often more talented than the top disciple of a Great World King Holy Land.

An Empyrean Heavenly Palace had a truly terrifying population. An Empyrean had their descendants, and these Empyrean descendants had their own disciples, and then these disciples also had their disciples. The population would grow over the years at an exponential rate, and the total number of people easily broke past a trillion. Of course, most of these people were staff and they simply didn’t possess the qualifications to contact the core of the Empyrean Heavenly Palace.

With 30 semifinals areas and each area screening out for 300 people, there were a total of 9000 participants. In addition to the 970 Heavenly Palace core disciples and the 30 Empyrean direct disciples, that was just about 10,000 individuals.

“Lin Ming, in front is the residential area for the contestants. We can’t enter there, so we’ll separate here for now. There are still around 10 days until the finals of the First Martial Meeting begins. You shouldn’t spend this time training; it’s fine as long as you adjust your mentality and prepare yourself. You should relax and also get to know the geniuses from the other great worlds.”

Lin Ming’s current strength had reached a bottleneck. It was impossible for him to make any significant changes in just 10 days of time. If he wanted to steadily break into the late Divine Sea realm, it would take at least several years.

“Okay.”

Lin Ming also wanted to get to know the geniuses of other great worlds more.

After Huo Violentstone and the others left, Lin Ming went into the residential area by himself. He discovered that there was an enormous square in the center of this palace, with all sorts of buildings. There were restaurants, martial fields, pill shops, and weapon stores.

Upon casually entering a store, everything inside was extremely expensive, but the items were all of high quality. The worst weapons from the weapon stores were spirit artifacts. Although these spirit artifacts didn’t have much potential for growth, they were still equal to dozens or hundreds of top grade saint artifacts.

This was also a reasonable matter. The 10,000 martial artists that were able to come here were famous individuals with strength ranked in the top three of their great world. Besides those few scattered wandering martial artists, the ones with the worst background still came from Great World King Holy Lands. How could they care about a normal top grade saint artifact?

Numerous heroic young elites walked back and forth on the streets. Even a character like Bloodless Sword seemed ordinary here.

Lin Ming glanced over them, sighing. It truly was a spectacular sight to see all the Divine Sea geniuses of the Divine Realm gathered here. These people were all monstrous freaks, but even so, most of these people weren’t worth Lin Ming paying attention to. The ones Lin Ming saw to be a real threat were only several people. For instance, Dragon Fang, but also Frost Dream…

“Lin Ming!”

Lin Ming suddenly stopped as he heard someone call out to him. He turned around to see a martial artist in purple clothes running towards him. He had some impressions of this fellow: he was the martial artist known as Purple Blade in the semifinals at Gravemoon Star. He had finally lost when he failed to climb up the 31st step of the Divine Seal Altar. His strength had been ranked fifth at Gravemoon Star’s semifinals, inferior to Nether Limitless and Bloodless Sword.

“Purple Blade!”

“Right, haha, Brother Lin has arrived really early, but I came even earlier, about a month ago.  Brother Lin, it seems you’ve been training quite well these days. I have to say that I envy your strength.”

Purple Blade was already at the peak of the late Divine Sea realm. The next step for him was to enter the Divine Transformation realm. Thus, there was no way for him to increase his strength by raising his cultivation, so he could only enlighten himself on the Laws. But in just a few months’ time, how much could he possibly perceive?

“Brother Lin just arrived, so you’re probably not familiar with this place yet. Come, I’ll bring you to some interesting places. There are some ruthless individuals that haunt those places. I imagine Brother Lin would be like to take a look, as only those geniuses can be Brother Lin’s competition.”

Purple Blade had been arrogant and proud since birth, but after witnessing Lin Ming mounting the Divine Seal Altar, he felt nothing but a deep sense of admiration towards him, and wanted to be friends with him. In the future, Purple Blade would be the leader of a great influence. There would be no harm and only gain if he were to befriend a top master.

“Alright.” Lin Ming readily agreed. He was also interested in this.

Purple Blade brought Lin Ming through several streets and past a group of palaces. Finally, he came to a large square where many people had gathered.

This square had several hundred elites in it, with both men and women. In the center, there was a massive crystal platform, and this platform shined with a variety of colors.

“What is that?”

“It is used to test one’s Laws. I’ve also seen these at my World King Palace, and they test the degree to which a trial challenger can comprehend the Laws. But, this one is several times greater than any I’ve seen before.”

Purple Blade explained. This was clearly one of the interesting locations he had mentioned.

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. There were magic tools that could test one’s comprehension of Laws?

“Come on, let’s go take a look.”

Lin Ming followed Purple Blade forwards. The crystal platform was divided into nine colored layers: red, orange, yellow, green, cyan, blue, violet, black, and white, each color corresponding to a different set of Law Concepts.

As Lin Ming walked forwards, he saw a martial artist just coming down from the crystal platform. The first four levels of the crystal platform had lit up with a blazing light, but the fifth only dimly shined for an instant before dying down.

“The fourth level Laws are his limit, and he’s just barely managed to become aware of the fifth level Concept. Not bad.”

Many of those present had already practiced the fourth level Laws to the peak. The difference was whether or not they had comprehended the fifth level Concept and just how deep their awareness was.

Above the fifth level, every little bit of progress was extraordinary.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Song is great. Haha, your results are no worse than those of that Heavenly Palace core disciple who just stepped up!”

“Are you saying that we’re worse than them? Their master is a Great World King, but so is ours! Just thinking about how the palaces are ranked by position angers me. The Empyrean descendants are arranged in the top 30 palaces, the top master of each semifinals location is arranged in the 31st to 60th palace, and then that is followed by the Empyrean Heavenly Palace core disciples and finally us. It’s like they think we are all worthless.”

“Yah! It’s not like those Empyrean Heavenly Palace core disciples are Empyrean descendants. They are only disciples of Empyrean direct disciples, so how come they are arranged in front of us!”

“We’ll see how they do in the finals. Just because of their empty status as a Heavenly Palace disciple, they don’t place us in their eyes at all! In truth, they can’t even see the Empyreans. They are nothing but foxes pretending to be tigers.”

At the edges of the crowd, Lin Ming heard such discussions going on.

Geniuses were all extremely arrogant. From the way that Vast Universe Heavenly Palace had arranged the residences of the participants, it could be seen just how they viewed the difference between Empyrean disciples and the disciples from ordinary influences.

It was originally difficult for the disciples of Empyrean Heavenly Palaces and the disciples of World King Holy Lands to live peacefully together. This was because the disciples from Empyrean Heavenly Palaces always had a sense of superiority, and the disciples of the Great World King Holy Lands would naturally envy them. Now, because of how the palace living arrangements were done, this had aroused the bitterness and criticism of others.

“Heh… talk about a crowd of country bumpkins that have yet to see the greater world. Just because you managed to stumble into some good results you’re all so overly pleased with yourselves. What a bunch of idiots.”

In the crowd, a cold voice suddenly spoke up, attracting everyone’s angry glares. As everyone looked over, they saw a white-clothed youth speaking. He had the emblem of a starry sky embroidered on the chest of his robes. This was the symbol of a disciple from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.

“Vast Universe Heavenly Palace disciple!”

“Core disciple? Direct disciple?”

These geniuses who were originally mocking and cursing those Empyrean Palace disciples were all extremely angry. But in the face of this Vast Universe Heavenly Palace disciple, they actually felt lacking in courage and energy. This was because this fellow’s aura was simply too strong, and all of them felt as if they couldn’t begin to compare with him.

“What are you being so arrogant about? If you have the ability then go up and test yourself. Don’t just stand here and talk big!” A World King Holy Land disciple shouted, not too convincingly.

“Haha, I already knew that you would have doubts. Since that’s the case, let me broaden your horizons.”

As that disciple spoke, he walked into the middle of the crowd and lazily brought up a hand. Then, with a simple gesture, he thrust his palm out. Faint fluctuations of the Space Laws appeared in the air, and the first four levels of the crystal platform immediately lit up. The fifth level also dimly shined, continuing for several breaths of time before dying down.

This was proof that his comprehension of Concepts was not just being faintly aware, but truly touching upon the fifth level threshold. Compared to Nether Limitless, he was about the same!

And Nether Limitless was himself a peak master of a great world. If it weren’t for the monstrous freaks known as Lin Ming and Dragon Fang, he would have been first in the semifinals at Gravemoon Star. He was stronger than 99% of those present!

Chapter 1276 – Frost Dream, Xiao Moxian

Any casual disciple from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, even if they weren’t an Empyrean direct disciple, still nearly reached the standard of a first ranked master from a semifinals area. This caused many of the young elites present to be left speechless.

“Who… who is he?”

The several Holy Land disciples speaking before felt their faces flush red with embarrassment.

They weren’t able to ascertain his status before they saw that person switch hands. This time, a golden red light covered his hand as he slapped his palm onto the crystal platform.

The last time was the Space Laws, but now it was the Metal Laws!

The crystal platform shimmered with a dazzling light once more. Without needing to mention the first four levels, even the fifth level blazed for one to two breaths of time. Although his Metal Laws were slightly worse than his Space Laws, he could still be considered as having touched upon the threshold of the fifth level Concept.

He cultivated two different Laws and yet he had reached perfection of the fourth level Concept and was soon to break through the boundary of the fifth level Concept. This disparity was obvious to all present, and it caused many of them to lose all the bluster they had before.

That disciple from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace swept his eyes through the entire audience and tipped his head upwards in victory. As for the person that had challenged him, his face had gone deep red as he was left speechless. Under the gaze of everyone present, he had disgracefully shamed himself.

These people were all geniuses of their various great worlds. When they came to the First Martial Meeting, although they didn’t imagine they would be able to shock the world with a brilliant feat of talent, they believed they could at least shine in glory. But now, before the finals had even begun, they had been brutally attacked.

“I am Zhao Ji and my Honorable Master is Vast Cosmos. Remember that.”

The Vast Universe Heavenly Palace disciple said with a smug smile on his face. Vast Cosmos was the chief disciple of Empyrean Vast Universe, and also had a half-step Empyrean cultivation. Not just that, but with the support of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace’s resources, the strength of the disciples he taught could be imagined. To be able to touch upon the fifth level Concepts of two different Laws wasn’t strange at all.

Many people clenched their jaws, but they were pressured so badly they couldn’t even lift their heads. The already couldn’t compare with Empyrean direct disciples, but now these Heavenly Palace core disciples were pushing them down.

“Hehe, to tell the truth, having the number one ranked participants of the semifinals be arranged in front of us is already doing you a favor; you should be content with what you have!” Zhao Ji sneered.

Purple Blade frowned. “Brother Lin, this cocky fellow really thinks his tail reaches the skies. He’s even mocking you.”

Lin Ming was the first ranked participant of the Gravemoon Star semifinals and was arranged in the first 60 palaces. As Zhao Ji spoke, his words naturally disparaged Lin Ming.

Lin Ming said, “Let him do as he pleases. There’s no reason to quarrel over something like this. No matter how great his results are on that platform, it won’t affect the overall result of the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting. Moreover, a genuine master wouldn’t do something so ridiculous.”

Lin Ming was well aware that there were many martial artists in this First Martial Meeting, as well as Empyrean descendants, that had thoroughly comprehended the fifth level Concept. That was something that wasn’t as simple as touching upon the threshold!

But these people actually hadn’t moved.

Lin Ming and Purple Blade’s conversation wasn’t hidden, thus Zhao Ji naturally heard them. He sneered and said, “You talk like you’re so amazing. How about you come on stage and give it a try, so we can see just how much weight you have. You really are a shameless boaster!”

Zhao Ji provokingly said. Everyone immediately turned to Lin Ming. Out of the hundreds of people present, there were naturally some from Gravemoon Star’s semifinals, thus they recognized Lin Ming.

“Isn’t that Lin Ming?”

“Yes, that’s Lin Ming. He’s the first ranked participant of Gravemoon Star!”

“The first ranked participant was Lin Ming and the second ranked participant was Dragon Fang! Both are extreme geniuses!”

Many disciples from the Gravemoon Star semifinals started to call out Lin Ming’s name after seeing him.

As for the people from other semifinal areas, they didn’t think much of Lin Ming. To them, there were far too many first ranked participants from the different semifinal areas.

“First ranked of Gravemoon Star? That’s him?”

“I guess he’s around the same as our semifinals’ first ranked participant, Blood Carnage.”

As everyone was speaking, near the crystal platform, Zhao Ji stiffened, his face red, the exact same as the disciple from the World King Holy Land that he had embarrassed.

“You… you are… Lin Ming?”

Zhao Ji gulped, his words coming out a bit slurred.

If one wasn’t a disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, it would be hard to imagine just how difficult it was to climb up the Divine Seal Altar’s 33 steps.

When the disciples from other semifinal areas heard that Lin Ming had mounted the peak of the Divine Seal Altar, they only knew that he was fierce. As for how fierce he was, they weren’t sure. But, as a disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, Zhao Ji had personally witnessed an incomparably powerful direct disciple of Empyrean Vast Universe climb up the Divine Seal Altar in the past. However, that disciple hadn’t even been able to climb 10,000 feet up the 33rd step. In this situation, if Lin Ming could reach the top, just how strong was he?

At the beginning, when Zhao Ji first heard this news, he simply couldn’t believe it. But, after verifying this with his master, he had learnt beyond a shadow of a doubt that this news was true, despairingly so.

Even if Lin Ming were using some tricks, shortcuts, or had some treasure to climb up, there was no doubting his potential. Zhao Ji knew that he absolutely couldn’t compare to such a person, because he himself couldn’t even climb up to the 32nd step.

The great disparity between them could be imagined!

“Yes, he is Lin Ming.” Purple Blade said, his lips curving upwards. He already guessed that the name of Lin Ming had some significant mental impact to this disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.

“Lin Ming…” Zhao Ji’s complexion was very uncomfortable. In front of Lin Ming, he didn’t have any confidence at all. But even so, he couldn’t back down and lose like this here. “My senior-apprentice brother has wanted to challenge you. Your results in climbing up the Divine Seal Altar were truly heaven-defying, but you did so using nothing but tricks!”

Lin Ming faintly smiled. “The Divine Seal Altar is a test of your comprehension of Laws. Whether or not you can find tricks to climb up all depends on your own ability. The methods are already there. Whether you can find them is your own problem.”

Zhao Ji was left speechless by Ling Ming’s words.

He was well aware that no matter how Lin Ming climbed up the Divine Seal Altar’s 33 steps, him trying to challenge Lin Ming was only bringing about his own destruction.

So he simply walked down the crystal platform. He had spoken too arrogantly just now and had ended up slapping his own face. Zhao Ji didn’t even have the shame to lift his own face up.

At this time, a pall of silence fell over the entire square.

Some people began to look towards one direction. As for others, they seemed to feel something special and also looked over.

They saw a 15-16 year old-looking young girl. She wore a long black skirt and as she walked over she resembled a devilish nocturnal temptress.

Her long hair was jet black, hanging down to her waist like a waterfall of ink. Her eyes were as wide as a baby’s, incomparably bright.

Even with several hundred people present, it was possible to hear the sound of a pin drop.

“Xiao Moxian!”

“Direct disciple of Demondawn Heavenly Palace and also a direct bloodline descendant of Empyrean Demondawn – Xiao Moxian!”

And what was most breathtaking was that beside Xiao Moxian was a young woman in a long pure white dress. Her figure was tall and outstanding, and her entire body exuded a sacred and sacrosanct atmosphere, making anyone near her feel inferior.

She appeared together with Xiao Moxian and she herself was a perfect and formidable young woman. Her name was heart-stopping; she was Fairy Frost Dream!

Chapter 1277 – Child of the Dark Phoenix

Xiao Moxian and Frost Dream were two peerless women. Standing side by side, they were two women that made all surrounding martial artists feel less than dirt. These two women, whether it be in status or strength, made everyone feel incomparably distant. Even that World King Holy Land disciple who was criticizing the arrangement of the palace residences didn’t complain that the Empyrean direct disciples were placed in the first 30 palaces. This was because the disparity was far too obvious.

There was no need to mention Frost Dream; it was said she was the disciple that Empyrean Divine Dream was most proud and satisfied of for these last 10 million years.

Empyrean Divine Dream was already one of the few peak characters of the entire Divine Realm. The strength of her most outstanding disciple could be imagined.

However, Fairy Frost Dream was an extremely low-key and subdued individual. The techniques she used, the Laws she cultivated, all of that was a mystery.

As for Xiao Moxian, her character was widely known as a naughty trickster that loved to play all the time. Even so, her strength was also a mystery.

During the preliminaries, Xiao Moxian’s terrifying strength had struck fear into the hearts of everyone. In the Divine Dream World’s 3000 great worlds, Xiao Moxian had swept through all opponents, unstoppable.

But even that was not her full strength. It was hard to imagine where the limits of her strength lay.

“They are Xiao Moxian and Frost Dream…”

Lin Ming looked at these two women, his eyes extremely sharp.

Xiao Moxian was actually only at the middle Divine Sea realm, the same as himself.

As for Fairy Frost Dream, Lin Ming couldn’t clearly see through her cultivation.

Her inner world was covered in a dense layer of fog, blurry. Let alone her inner world, even her facial features seemed to be shrouded in a dream-like layer of illusions, making all unable to clearly see her.

Beside Lin Ming, Purple Blade said to him, “Brother Lin, Fairy Frost Dream is an extremely mysterious character. Whenever she appears in public she is always concealed with the Divine Dream Laws. It’s impossible for anyone to get a clear look at her.

“As for Xiao Moxian, I’ve heard a bit of her situation. Although it isn’t some secret, not everyone knows of it… after I learned this information, I lost all confidence to face her… her talent has truly reached a boundary that mortals like us cannot imagine.”

As Purple Blade spoke, he saw Lin Ming’s not too concerned expression and continued to say, “Brother Lin, I’m not trying to scare you. In my opinion, your talent is already heaven-defying amongst all heaven-defying geniuses. But, if compared to Xiao Moxian, I’m afraid that even you are far inferior…”

“Oh?” Lin Ming looked at Purple Blade with amazement in his eyes. In Purple Blade’s opinion, Xiao Moxian’s talent was far greater than his own?

The Divine Seal Altar was mainly a test of one’s potential. When Lin Ming climbed up the Divine Seal Altar, although he had relied on some shortcuts, the undeniable truth was that his potential swept away the dozens of Empyrean disciples of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace for the last 2 million years.

Because Purple Blade didn’t understand him, Lin Ming wouldn’t think it was strange that Purple Blade thought he was worse than Xiao Moxian. But, Purple Blade had said that Lin Ming was far worse than Xiao Moxian.

This surprised Lin Ming. It was clear that Xiao Moxian was quite special.

“Let’s hear it.”

Purple Blade said, “Brother Lin, I know that you are hiding some secrets and also have many other cards you have yet to reveal. Your future achievements are something I cannot imagine, but even so, I fear that you are too far off from Xiao Moxian. She is truly a monster amongst all monstrous geniuses. Let me say this first: Xiao Moxian is younger than you. She is only 26 years old right now.”

“26 years old!?”

As Lin Ming heard this age he was truly horrified. A 26 year old middle Divine Sea realm master!? This age combined with this cultivation was ridiculously shocking!

An extreme genius, even if they didn’t cultivate the Laws, ignoring their foundation and cultivation methods, merely seeking to increase their strength, even if they ignored all consequences to take all sorts of medicines, they still might not be able to reach the middle Divine Sea realm at 26 years of age.

And Xiao Moxian was clearly not in this situation. There was no mistaking her strength. Whether it was in comprehension of Laws or foundation, she far surpassed all her peers!

Lin Ming couldn’t begin to imagine just how she did so much in so little time.

Purple Blade was already expecting this response from Lin Ming. He said, “The reason Xiao Moxian has her current achievements is because she has a special bloodline. Her mother is not a human…”

As Purple Blade said this, Lin Ming was stunned. “Her mother isn’t a human? Is she from the demon race?”

In the Divine Realm, besides humans, there were a small number of other races. For instance, the demon races’ ogre race and imp race. Even so, all of them combined together were only a small number. Their population was nothing in comparison to the humans’.

In Lin Ming’s impressions, since Empyrean Demondawn was known as Demondawn, the Dawn of all Demons, then it wouldn’t be strange if Xiao Moxian’s mother was also from the demon race.

Purple Blade shook his head, “It isn’t the demons but the monsters. If I say this it might scare you a bit, but the rumors say that Xiao Moxian’s mother is a Dark Phoenix…”

As Purple Blade said this, Lin Ming was truly scared silly. “Dark Phoenix? A God Beast!?”

According to what Lin Ming knew, the most common phoenix was a Fire Phoenix, with a small number being Ice Phoenixes. As for Dark Phoenixes, Lin Ming had once seen one in Empyrean Divine Seal’s dream-like memories. But now, in the current Divine Realm, these types of phoenixes had disappeared long ago.

However, that was not the most critical point. A human Empyrean was originally an existence comparable to a God Beast, and their strength might even surpass a God Beast. In Empyrean Demondawn’s Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming wouldn’t be startled if there was a God Beast there, or even a primordial God Beast. No, what Lin Ming thought was inconceivable was that even though a God Beast could change into human form, no matter how much sex they had with a human it should be impossible for a child to be born from them!

Let alone a God Beast with a human, even a God Beast mating with another God Beast would find having a child incomparably difficult. The more powerful a species was, the more difficult it was to bear descendants. This was part of the laws of nature that balanced the universe. Otherwise, there would be hundreds of millions of God Beasts and it would be beyond simple for them to sweep through and rule the Divine Realm.

In this sort of situation, how could there be a child between a God Beast and a human?

Lin Ming finally knew why Purple Blade thought that his talent was far inferior to Xiao Moxian’s.

A God Beast was originally the beloved darling of the world Laws. Their entire body was a treasure and their bones and organs and flesh were all engraved with the most mystical and profound Law runes. When a God Beast was born, they would not need any training at all to possess strength only inferior to that of an Empyrean after growing up.

Of course, correspondingly, there were many shortcomings. This was that the Laws they possessed were more or less finalized at their birth. No matter how much they trained, this wouldn’t change much. Also, their ability to learn was far worse than humans’.

But, if a God Beast and a human could mate together, the child they produced would inherit the learning capabilities of a human but also the heaven-defying talent of a God Beast. It was hard to imagine just how terrifying such an existence would be!

Moreover, since this Xiao Moxian was the direct bloodline descendant of Empyrean Demondawn, then her father must naturally also be an extreme character. Otherwise, how could he possibly obtain the favor and lust of a God Beast taken human shape?

Her father was an extreme character, her mother was a God Beast, and her grandfather was an outstanding Empyrean!

This sort of background was high to the point that it couldn’t be any higher!

It wouldn’t be an exaggeration to say that Xiao Moxian was the proudest daughter of heaven within the entire Divine Realm!

“Ancient Phoenix Clan… in front of Xiao Moxian, there simply isn’t any comparison at all…”

Lin Ming sighed with emotion. The Ancient Phoenix Clan, no matter how much Ancient Phoenix blood they transplanted, could not compare with Xiao Moxian. Xiao Moxian had the true body of a phoenix child. Every drop of her blood, every bone, every muscle, and even her soul was marked with the characteristics of a God Beast.

“No wonder that Xiao Moxian can reach the middle Divine Sea realm at 26 years of age but also comprehend the Laws to this level. That is because those Laws have already been engraved within her body from her birth…”

Lin Ming felt a bit relieved. Xiao Moxian didn’t need to do as other geniuses did and assiduously perceive the Laws. She already had the Laws within her body and merely needed to slowly digest them. Such a disparity was truly frustrating.

“Yes. When the resources and inheritances of Demondawn Heavenly Palace are added on top, we truly can’t compare.”

Purple Blade spoke with sincere envy. In front of Xiao Moxian, he really was nothing more than an ant. The difference between them was too great.

“Big Sister, there are so many people here, it’s really lively!” Xiao Moxian giggled as she saw all the people gathered around the crystal platform. As she smiled, she revealed a pair of sharp canines.

“They are testing their comprehension of Laws.” Fairy Frost Dream said. Her voice was similar to immortal tunes flowing down a 100,000 foot tall snow-capped mountain.

“Eh, is there something so fun?” Xiao Moxian had just arrived at Vast Universe World so she had yet to take a walk around. “I also want to play a bit. Would Big Sister Frost Dream like to try it too?”

Xiao Moxian casually asked. Frost Dream faintly smiled and said in a soft voice, “No need.”

“Then I’ll give it a try.”

Xiao Moxian walked into the crowd and everyone spontaneously drew away from her.

Although Xiao Moxian seemed extremely casual as if she were just playing around, everyone else’s eyes widened. They held their breath, waiting to see Xiao Moxian’s performance.

Among the young generation, she was someone who truly stood at the peak!

Standing before the crystal platform, Xiao Moxian simply didn’t ready anything at all. She just lightly thrust out her palm, and in that moment a black flame burnt in Xiao Moxian’s palm. Although this black flame appeared inconspicuous, the moment it lit up, the entire crystal platform began to light up. The first five levels blazed with a shining light and even the sixth level began to glimmer with a bright light!

She had reached perfection in the fifth level Laws, and even touched upon the sixth level Concept!

As everyone saw this they were shocked speechless, panic-stricken. A normal genius was already considered amazing if they could touch upon the fifth level Concept, but Xiao Moxian had already touched upon the sixth level Concept. Her comprehension of Laws was truly monstrous.

“Too strong!” Purple Blade sighed from beside Lin Ming. In terms of the comprehension of Laws, Xiao Moxian had flung him impossibly far away. He had only reached large success in the fifth level Concept.

“Xiao Moxian is only playing around and yet she’s managed to reach such a level. She’s definitely not trying her best. In terms of Laws, I am truly far inferior to her.” Lin Ming shook his head. His comprehension of Laws was already considered outstanding, but it was far too difficult for him to compare with Xiao Moxian, who had the Laws engraved into her body as a true God Beast did.

Xiao Moxian didn’t have any reaction to her result. She simply chuckled and said, “Big Sister Frost Dream, are you sure you don’t want to try?”

She looked completely like a young girl who only came to play about and have some fun. To other geniuses, they were here in a ruthless battle to decide superiority and gain glory. But to Xiao Moxian, this was only an amusing toy.

Frost Dream smiled, shaking her head again and saying, “No.”

“Okay. Big Sister Frost Dream you are just too boring. Let’s leave this place and go shopping over there.”

Chapter 1278 – The Finals Begin

“Junior-apprentice Sister Xiao Moxian is fierce, truly fierce! Wonderful! I’m filled with admiration!”

As Xiao Moxian was about to leave, Vast Cosmos’s disciple, Zhao Ji, walked towards her with a face full of smiles. “I am Zhao Ji. Junior-apprentice Sister, it is truly my lucky chance to meet you here.”

“Who are you?”

Xiao Moxian glanced over at Zhao Ji, clearly not interested in bothering with him.

“I am a disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace’s Vast Cosmos.”

Zhao Ji put forth his master’s name, but his status wasn’t able to arouse any interest from Xiao Moxian. Xiao Moxian singly gave a light, “Oh,” before pulling Fairy Frost Dream’s arm and leading her away from the crystal platform.

Zhao Ji was left behind by himself, his hands cupped against his chest. This caused him to feel extremely awkward.

In truth, from start to finish, Xiao Moxian hadn’t even bothered to glance at the surrounding martial artists. From this, Lin Ming could faintly feel that even though Xiao Moxian had a lively and childlike innocent demeanor, her playfulness only extended to those she was familiar with. Strangers, and in particular those strangers that were ordinary in talent, were treated the exact opposite. After all, arrogance was something bred into her bones.

Xiao Moxian had tested herself just now because she thought it was amusing. She didn’t do so to demonstrate her ability like the other martial artists here, because doing so had no significance. This was just like how a human felt superior to a pack of ants. They weren’t even on the same playing field.

“Let’s go.”

Lin Ming said to Purple Blade. As they were about to leave, he suddenly saw a black-clothed martial artist with a strangely curved sword on his back, walking towards the crystal platform. This person was Dragon Fang.

“Dragon Fang, he also wants to test himself?”

Lin Ming just had this thought when he saw Dragon Pang’s palm thrust out. This palm actually had the feeling as if the flow of time were shifted around it. Suddenly, the crystal platform lit up. The first four levels shined with a dazzling light and even the fifth level shimmered, shining for several dozen breaths of time before slowly dying down.

“That’s Dragon Fang! For him to have the fifth level of the crystal platform shine for so long, his Laws must have reached the fifth level Concept!”

“Compared to Xiao Moxian, his result is far worse, but that’s still amazing.”

“This person came in second place at the Gravemoon Star semifinals, only inferior to Lin Ming! Rather, it should be said that his potential is worse than Lin Ming’s. As for his strength, no one knows.”

Those that could recognize Dragon Fang also came from Gravemoon Star’s contest arena. Although Dragon Fang had been completely beaten by Lin Ming, he had still left a profound impression on everyone.

To be more accurate, Dragon Fang and Lin Ming were already on a completely different level.

“Large success of a fifth level Law; I fear that is the strongest result you’ll find under the Empyrean descendants!”

“There are even some weaker Empyrean descendants that are weaker than him! How come those from the Gravemoon Star semifinals are so strong. Isn’t there still Lin Ming, who is even stronger?”

The participants of the other contest areas discussed. As those from Gravemoon Star heard about this, they felt a certain sense of pride. They already knew that Lin Ming and Dragon Fang were fierce, and now those that had suspected them had actually seen them with their own eyes.

Several hundred feet away, Lin Ming witnessed the entire scene.

“Dragon Fang… he actually used the Time Laws on that crystal platform.”

Lin Ming took a deep breath. Before now, he only knew that Dragon Fang’s most outstanding ability was his mastery of the Space Laws. Nether Limitless had been able to create four spatial mirror images, but Dragon Fang had been able to use eight of them. The disparity between someone who just touched upon the fifth level Concept and someone who steadily entered the fifth level Concept could be seen from this.

And now, Dragon Fang’s Time Laws had already reached the fifth level. It was unknown just what boundary his Space Laws had reached!

The Time Laws and Space Laws were two of the most difficult Laws to comprehend. Correspondingly, they were also two of the strongest Laws. Of these two, the Time Laws were far more abstract and elusive, and faintly superior to the Space Laws.

“Dragon Fang… he’s a terrifying opponent! In these past months his comprehension of the Laws has reached an even higher level and his cultivation has entered into the late Divine Sea realm. I still have no idea what cards he’s holding back. In terms of comprehending the Laws, I can’t compare with him at all.”

In terms of Laws, Lin Ming was indeed inferior to Dragon Fang and far more inferior to Xiao Moxian. But, true combat didn’t depend on just one’s comprehension of the Laws; there were many other aspects that influenced one’s comprehensive combat strength.

……….

10 days passed in the blink of an eye. Besides the unfathomably deep Frost Dream and Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming saw several strong Empyrean descendants.

As the sun rose on the 11th day, Lin Ming was sitting in meditation in his palace. He suddenly heard a voice spread through his mind.

“All participants of the finals, gather in the square. The finals of the First Martial Meeting shall begin today!”

A solemn voice spread through every palace. Lin Ming opened his eyes. Today, the beginning of the finals had come at last.

The entire martial field was filled with 10,000 young elites. All of them had come from their respective palaces and were gathered at the central square.

Here, dozens of World King powerhouses had gathered. They were all the presiders of the various semifinal contest areas, and even Xiao Daochild was included amongst them. With several dozen World King powerhouses gathered together, the might of their aura could be imagined!

10,000 geniuses stood quietly, waiting for the finals to arrive.

“Everyone!”

After everyone had gathered, a strong and tall man in white robes descended from the skies. His figure was tremendous and his aura was pressuring. His entire body emitted a breathtaking pressure.

“I am Empyrean Vast Universe’s direct chief disciple, Vast Cosmos. I represent Vast Universe Heavenly Palace in welcoming you all here. You are all truly outstanding!”

“Vast Cosmos?”

“He is Vast Cosmos? If we can enter the top 10 ranks of the Earth Proclamation we can enter Vast Universe Heavenly Palace and also obtain his tutelage?”

“Senior Vast Cosmos has a half-step Empyrean cultivation. He is more than qualified to guide us. Even the Great World King of a first-order world has to pay deep respects to Senior Vast Cosmos.”

The young geniuses present secretly discussed with true essence sound transmissions. For many of them, Vast Cosmos was the fiercest character they had yet to see in their lives.

“Now, I shall announce the rules. The lot of you have already been divided into groups for elimination.”

As Vast Cosmos spoke, he flourished his hands and a massive curtain of light appeared in front of everyone. This curtain of light was 1000 feet wide and had 10,000 names displayed on it. Each name had a number following it – these were the palace numbers that everyone had lived at.

Of 10,000 people, they were divided into 10 groups with 1000 people each.

“1000 people? How do we fight? Could it be an elimination trial like the Divine Seal Altar?”

Lin Ming immediately thought. If they carried out a round-robin tournament to ensure absolute fairness, then everyone would have to fight 999 other people. This seemed too troublesome.

But at this time, he also discovered that each group of 1000 people was also divided into two parts. The first part had 30 people written in red, and the second part had 970 people written in white.

Lin Ming’s name was red, and many of the Heavenly Palace core disciples were white.

In the skies, Vast Cosmos said, “Every great group is divided into two smaller groups depending on your results in the semifinals as well as the strength you’ve displayed so far. The first group has 30 people and the second group has 970 people. For those in the second group, they have three chances to challenge someone from the first group. If they can win in any single one of these battles, they may swap positions with their opponent. Otherwise, if you are defeated in all three challenges then you will be directly eliminated! As for those that are defeated and replaced in the first group, they also have three chances to challenge someone from the first group again. If they lose all three challenges, they too will be eliminated! This will continue until all those from the second group have lost their qualifications!”

Upon hearing these rules, those that were selected to enter the second group felt uncomfortable. To put it in other words, Vast Universe Heavenly Palace did not believe those from the second group had any chances of winning and wanted to directly eliminate them from the tournament. This round of eliminations was developed as their final chance.

“They really think we’re useless trash.”

“Although we can’t enter the top 10 of the Earth Proclamation, we still shouldn’t be directly placed in the elimination group!”

Out of the 10,000 participants, there were only 300 people in the first group. 200 of them were Empyrean descendants and Heavenly Palace core disciples, and the other 100 were the young elites chosen from the 30 semifinal contest areas.

This caused many of the third and fourth ranked participants of the semifinals to be placed in the second group.

There were even some contest areas with bad luck that had their second ranked participant placed into the second group.

This caused them all to immediately fume with anger.

“What is the meaning of this? I came in second in my semifinals contest area, so why am I in the second group? There are some people that were ranked fifth in their contest area that are still in the first group!”

“These grouping rules are too random!”

These people were referring to Gravemoon Star’s contest area. The fifth placed Purple Blade was placed in the first group, much less Lin Ming and Dragon Fang.

Chapter 1280 – Unchallenged

After Dragon Fang and Lin Ming mounted the city gates, many others followed.

Even the Empyrean descendants no longer bothered posturing.

“That is White King! Empyrean Vast Universe’s direct disciple!”

White King had a very low-key personality. Although he had joined the preliminaries, he didn’t reveal his true abilities and he rarely came out to the contestant area, so many people didn’t know about him.

Without any problem, White King easily defeated the blood hands and stepped onto the city gates.

After White King, Xiao Moxian also flew up. She even engaged the blood hands in a little tussle before scattering them. The other martial artists were afraid of the blood hands and vigorously tried to avoid their attacks, but this was actually amusing to Xiao Moxian.

Then, it was time for Fairy Frost Dream.

Frost Dream gently lifted her hand, covering her entire body with a shroud of scattered light. This dream-like scattered light slowly revolved around Frost Dream, seeming like countless gorgeous flower petals that fell around her. Then, she simply vanished.

In the next moment she appeared above the city gates. A hazy halo of light appeared, shining with dazzling colors like spring cherry blossoms. Frost Dream appeared within these flower petals, proud and tall, like a goddess fallen down from the highest heavens. Her entire body exuded a holy and sanctified aura. Even though she had entered Slaughter City, she wasn’t stained with even the tiniest scent of blood.

Like this, Frost Dream had inexplicably appeared within Slaughter City, as if those flower petals had led her there. From start to finish, no one had been able see how she moved or what Laws she utilized.

“Is that teleportation?”

“Impossible! The power of space around Slaughter City is extremely solid and there is also that resentful energy that is hindering us all. It’s already difficult for us to fly, so how could she possibly teleport?”

“Too horrifying. I don’t know what Laws she used to accomplish what she just did. Who could possibly be her match?”

Everyone looked at Fairy Frost Dream with awe in their eyes. Xiao Moxian was a heaven-gifted eternally rare genius, but she was still only 26 years old. Being so young, her strength would naturally lag behind her senior.

Moreover, after understanding Xiao Moxian’s information, although one still couldn’t hold a candle to her, at least one could clearly see her strength. She wasn’t like Fairy Frost Dream, who had always been a mystery. Even now, no one had the faintest clue about her.

“These aren’t the Space Laws. This Frost Dream is too terrifying…”

Dragon Fang thought to himself. As someone with an extreme understanding of the Space Laws and who also touched upon the sixth level Concept, he could easily distinguish whether or not Fairy Frost Dream had used the Space Laws just now.

There was no limit in this universe. There was always a higher mountain and a stronger person!

Many martial artists sighed with emotion. Frost Dream was already so horrifying and yet no one knew where the limits of her strength lay.

After Frost Dream, the other remaining participants were all overshadowed. Even if they could defeat the blood hands, that wasn’t anything special at all.

Soon, all 10,000 people had tried to enter Slaughter City, with only 890 succeeding!

“10,000 people and now 90% were suddenly eliminated!”

“This is just too abnormal. I thought that after entering the finals I would be able to earn a ranking, but I never imagined there would be so many people that wouldn’t even have the chance to enter the arena!”

“There are too many geniuses. This competition is the definition of brutal!”

Even those that successfully entered Slaughter City thought this.

As for those martial artists that were overly confident in themselves, they also restrained the contempt and envy in their hearts. The difference was laid out in front of them. Many of them had managed to barely bypass those hands to enter Slaughter City, whilst some easily defeated the blood hands to enter. There was even someone like Fairy Frost Dream who had entered using some inconceivable means.

“Let the battle begin!”

One of the World Kings managing the tournament suddenly announced.

In the 10 great divisions, those that were eliminated were in the second group. Everyone in the first group would be considered has having passed.

Lin Ming was in the third division. In his division, there were 62 individuals remaining in the second group. They had to challenge those 30 martial artists in the first group.

“Dragon Fang?”

Lin Ming was surprised. He hadn’t noticed before, but he and Dragon Fang were placed in the same division. In addition, Purple Blade was also here.

“Choose your opponent. Each of you has three chances.”

The one managing this division was a thin old man. He wore blue clothes and had an extraordinary and ethereal-like temperament to him.

The 62 individuals chose their opponents. Neither Lin Ming nor Dragon Fang was selected.

This was also a reasonable matter. As one of the few people in their division capable of defeating those blood hands, wasn’t challenging someone as strong as they were just asking to die?

Beside Lin Ming, several other people weren’t chosen either. These were Empyrean descendants, Heavenly Palace core disciples, or the original first ranked martial artists of their contest areas.

Everyone else had three or four opponents. There were even some with poor performances as they entered Slaughter City, like Purple Blade, who were simultaneously chosen by seven or eight people.

“So that’s how it is. The elimination round in entering Slaughter City helps to reduce the number of participants but it is also to help those in the second group have an approximate understanding of the strength of the others. They can learn who is weak and who is strong so they don’t randomly waste their time.”

As Lin Ming was thinking, he suddenly felt someone’s eyes fall onto his body. He saw a white-clothed youth looking at him. This youth was shaved bald with a nine ringed scar on his head. He wore straw sandals and a loose robe, the very image of a solemn monk.

“Monk…”

Lin Ming’s eyebrows arched up.

“Benefactor Lin, I’m blessed to meet you. I am a disciple of Mount Potala, Hang Chi.”

“Mount Potala…” Lin Ming was startled. He had never heard the name of Mount Potala before.

As Lin Ming was trying to recall anything about Mount Potala, Purple Blade’s true essence sound transmission suddenly rang in his hears.

“Brother Lin, Mount Potala is an Empyrean Heavenly Palace level influence. They have an incomparably low profile most of the time, but they are one of the longest-lived sects with the most glorious history, and it is even rumored that they have two Empyreans in their sect!”

“Two Empyreans?” Lin Ming asked, startled. A sect with two Empyreans!

“There are extremely few double Empyrean influences. In the future, Divine Dream Heavenly Palace and Demondawn Heavenly Palace will be the same. Fairy Frost Dream and Xiao Moxian could be called young Empyreans. But, whether it is Divine Dream Heavenly Palace or Demondawn Heavenly Palace, they cannot compare with Mount Potala. This is the difference in background. I heard that Mount Potala has already existed for 3.6 billion years…”

“3.6 billion years!”

Lin Ming sucked in a breath of cold air. For an influence to survive for 3.6 billion years, that was a truly terrifying number!

“In these 3.6 billion years of history, would there always be an Empyrean standing guard within their ranks? Wouldn’t that mean they had several dozen Empyreans born from their sect?”

“I am not too clear about that. Mount Potala is extremely mysterious. The only reason I understand a little about them is because I was investigating information about everyone who is participating in the First Martial Meeting finals.”

Lin Ming deeply looked at Hang Chi. This monk exuded an aura as deep as the sea. He was clearly an extreme master.

“There are really too many masters here. This is a den of crouching tigers and hidden dragons!” Lin Ming thought to himself again. He cupped his hands and greeted Hang Chi in return.

“It’s fortunate to meet you too.”

Since this fellow was polite, Lin Ming naturally had to return the politeness.

And at this time, the fierce battling of the elimination series began. Every large division had several battles continuing on at the same time. In nearly all of them, the participants from the second group were defeated.

After battles and more battles, there would be someone eliminated every now and then. But this intense combat had no influence on Lin Ming at all. When the sun set and the elimination round was over, out of the 10,000 people at the start, only 300 people were remaining, with each division having 30 people.

Purple Blade was unlucky; he had been eliminated.

There wasn’t much he could do about this. He was someone who just barely managed to enter into the first group. On Gravemoon Star’s side, there was only Lin Ming, Dragon Fang, Nether Limitless, and Bloodless Sword left.

To a martial artist, there was no difference whether they fought in the morning or night. After several hours of rest, the group matches would begin.

And at this time, it was still around midnight.

“Things are happening so fast!”

Lin Ming thought to himself. There wasn’t even time for a day’s rest!

Lin Ming glanced over the name list. In each group of 30 people, every person only needed to fight 15 times. Lin Ming’s matches were mostly against Heavenly Palace core disciples or top three ranked participants from their contest areas. He wouldn’t be running into true Empyrean descendants or Dragon Fang yet. It seemed that everyone who was considered an extreme master was seeded into different groups to stagger them apart from each other.

“First martial field! Lin Ming against Cang Liang! Dragon Fang against Wuju! Hang Chi against Heng Yin!”

In the individual martial fields of the divisions, a referee loudly announced that the first one to go on stage was Lin Ming. This was also reasonable. Lin Ming hadn’t even fought in the elimination series so he naturally had to fight first.

His opponent, Cang Liang, was a Heavenly Palace core disciple, and he stayed at Palace 90. From this number, his strength could be imagined to a certain extent.

Chapter 1281 – Difference in Strength

The Cang Liang who walked on the martial stage was a silver-haired martial artist who used a black spear, the same weapon type as Lin Ming.

Lin Ming also silently took out his Phoenix Blood Spear from his spatial ring.

“Spear? How interesting!”

Cang Liang faintly smiled. “I have some impressions of you. You were the first ranked participant from Gravemoon Star, and many people know of you. They believe you can easily enter the top three of the Earth Proclamation, and perhaps even bloom in splendor during this First Martial Meeting and reach the top 10 ranks of the Heaven Proclamation.”

According to the rules of the First Martial Meeting, the Empyrean direct disciples and Heavenly Palace core disciples were considered within the Heaven Proclamation, but the Earth Proclamation removed all of them. Basically, those that would rule the Earth Proclamation would be disciples of Great World King Holy Lands.

In the past First Martial Meetings, the top three placed participants on the Earth Proclamation would only have an average ranking on the Heaven Proclamation. Without mentioning Empyrean descendants, many Heavenly Palace core disciples, which were also in the second group, were often better than disciples of Great World King Holy Lands.

This was because these Heavenly Palace core disciples often had half-step Empyrean masters, and their inheritances and resources were often much better. Many times they were even able to study transcendent divine mights. It was extremely difficult for disciples of Great World King Holy Lands to compare with them.

Cang Liang was this type of Heavenly Palace core disciple. As a Heavenly Palace core disciple, he was naturally arrogant. But no matter how arrogant Cang Liang was, he didn’t think for half a second that he could enter the top 10 rankings of the Heaven Proclamation. This was because the momentum and grandeur of this First Martial Meeting was far too vast. As the First Martial Meeting was held, more and more Empyrean direct disciples began to join in. At the start there were less than 10, but now as the finals were about to begin, there were already 30 of them.

This was an extremely rare situation, even when considering all the past First Martial Meetings. For instance, the last First Martial Meeting only had seven Empyrean descendants participating. Looking even further back, it was rare to find a First Martial Meeting that had more than 10 Empyrean descendants.

This caused the minimum ability required to enter the top 10 rankings of the Heaven Proclamation to be very high. If one wished to enter the top 10 they would have to engage in an absolutely blood-drenched round of combat!

The 30 Empyrean descendants came from over 20 Heavenly Palaces, and each one was an unbelievably monstrous genius. Moreover, nearly every one of them had a late Divine Sea cultivation. Facing any single one of them, Cang Liang didn’t have any confidence at all. Even so, in this situation, there were still many people that believed Lin Ming, a mere middle Divine Sea martial artist, had a chance of entering the top 10 of the Heaven Proclamation. Didn’t this mean that Lin Ming could easily defeat him?

Cang Liang certainly wasn’t convinced of this.

“Lin Ming has an extremely high chance of entering the top 10 of the Heaven Proclamation? Who said that?”

All around the arena stage, many of the viewers were also participants. This was the first time they had heard that Lin Ming had high hopes of entering the top 10 of the Heaven Proclamation.

“No idea. I only heard that he was the first ranked participant from Gravemoon Star’s contest area, and his potential even exceeds that of Dragon Fang. His comprehensive strength isn’t bad either. And that Dragon Fang is also a peak master.”

“Dragon Fang? Isn’t he just a common mortal martial artist…?” A Heavenly Palace disciple mindlessly commented. His eyes drifted towards another arena, where Dragon Fang was to face off against Wuju. Wuju was also a Heavenly Palace disciple in the second group. His palace number was 130, just slightly worse than Cang Liang.

After Lin Ming heard Cang Liang’s words, he faintly smiled. “Do I have a chance of entering the Heaven Proclamation’s top 10? That’s probably an appraisal given to me by the disciples of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.”

All the disciples of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace believed that Lin Ming had used some trick to mount the Divine Seal Altar. Even so, that was still far too amazing. From that alone they believed that Lin Ming’s potential was limitless. It was only a pity that Lin Ming was far too young. He was five or six years younger than most of the other Empyrean descendants, thus they believed that Lin Ming would only rank in the top 10 of the Heaven Proclamation. This appraisal already directly overshadowed most other Empyrean descendants and implied they would be defeated by a genius five or six years younger than them. To the Empyrean descendants, this was absolutely a great shame. Just thinking about what sort of strength Lin Ming could achieve in five or six years, one could imagine what sort of disparity these five or six years were.

“I am a disciple of Empyrean Ash Moon’s chief disciple, Moonchild. I’ve stepped on this stage because I want to use this battle to teach you something. I will teach you just how great the disparity is between the Heaven Proclamation and the Earth Proclamation. Even if we are not Empyrean direct disciples, we still have transcendent divine mights that we can cultivate!”

Cang Liang didn’t say that he would defeat Lin Ming. He didn’t believe that all rumors were baseless, but he also didn’t believe that Lin Ming could tear his way through so many powerful enemies to reach the top 10.

“This Cang Liang is really stupid.”

Underneath the arena stage, Zhao Ji was gloating in pleasure. In a stroke of fate, he was also placed into the same division as Lin Ming. And, as a disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Place, he was well aware of just how horrific Lin Ming was. Cang Liang could only blame his own bad luck.

“Lucky for him he didn’t say that he could defeat Lin Ming, otherwise his face would be swollen with shame later.” Another Vast Universe Heavenly Palace disciple said from beside Zhao Ji. Even if their Vast Universe Heavenly Palace disciples were inferior to Lin Ming, they were still glad to see the disciples of other Heavenly Palaces eat dirt.

As Cang Liang was about to say several more words, he suddenly heard a loud muffled sound from behind him, as if someone had forcefully struck the protective light barrier around the arenas.

He turned around and was immediately surprised. In another arena where Wuju was facing Dragon Fang, Wuju’s protective true essence had completely shattered. He spat out a mouthful of blood as he slumped to the ground. As for Dragon Fang, he stood in the center of the arena, casually grasping his curved sword as if he hadn’t expended any energy at all.

This fight was over in just a few breaths of time!

“This… what happened?”

Cang Liang’s eyes widened. He was somewhat familiar with Wuji. Although Wuju was inferior to himself, he still had the strength to compete for the top 100 rankings of the Heaven Proclamation, and yet he was quickly defeated by Dragon Fang!

“Fierce! He used a double spatial mirror image to defeat him in one move!”

“A double spatial mirror image isn’t considered too skillful at all. Dragon Fang’s limit surely continues past two images. I wonder just what boundary he has achieved!”

“No wonder some people said that Dragon Fang has a chance of entering the top 10 of the Heaven Proclamation. Now, it seems that these rumors might have been a bit exaggerated, but not necessarily inaccurate.”

All around Dragon Fang’s arena, many people had been watching that match just now. In just a spark of light the outcome had been decided!

Cang Liang’s face became immeasurably grim. In Gravemoon Star’s contest area, Dragon Fang had only come in second. Lin Ming had come in first place!

“And you were saying? Let’s start now, that side has already finished fighting.”

Lin Ming’s expression was very casual, but his words were grating on Cang Liang’s ears. Lin Ming simply didn’t consider him a decent opponent, and his words implied that this battle would be over soon.

“What a hateful man. Ash Moon in the Skies!”

Cang Liang shouted out loud and a watery lunar halo enveloped him. Behind Cang Liang, a brilliant moon appeared, slowly rising. This round moon gave off a magnificent and ancient atmosphere, making it hard for one to look directly at it.

As everyone saw this scene, their eyes began to light up.

“This is a transcendent divine might, the transcendent divine might of Ash Moon Heavenly Palace – Ancient Ash Moon!”

In truth, Ancient Ash Moon was not a complete transcendent divine might. Many Empyreans used their entire life’s energy to create a transcendent divine might. They might have to spend tens of millions of years to complete only half, and they might even die before they finished. This was the reason there were so many incomplete transcendent divine mights.

Ancient Ash Moon was one of these transcendent divine mights.

“A starving camel is still bigger than a horse. Even if a Heavenly Palace Core disciple is weak, they still have a supernatural divine might backing them. Just now, Wuju underestimated his enemy and didn’t even use his transcendent divine might. Cang Liang learnt from that lesson and now he’s immediately starting with everything he has.”

“Cang Liang might be able to create some trouble for Lin Ming. After all, he is stronger than Wuju.”

In this situation, even if Cang Liang were to show his transcendent divine might, very few people thought that he could defeat Lin Ming. If Lin Ming was on the same level as Dragon Fang, then the disparity between him and Cang Liang would be too great.

But, if he relied on his transcendent divine might to engage in a prolonged battle, he should be able to use up some of Lin Ming’s energy.

“Transcendent divine might? What a pity, you’ve only scratched the surface.”

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and swept outwards. With a flash of spear light, that ancient ash moon spear light in front of Cang Liang was pierced through. Although it didn’t shatter, the light dimmed down to almost nothing.

‘Mm? This attack contains the Concept of Timelessness? No wonder this ability gives off such an ancient and boundless feeling. Really, any kind of transcendent divine might isn’t simple at all! Unfortunately, Cang Liang’s comprehension of it is too shallow. Although an Empyrean Heavenly Palace often has more than one transcendent divine might as an inheritance, there are far too many people that wish to study them. The amount of time that a disciple is able to study it for is limited. If one wishes to study it in detail, they would need to be at least an Empyrean descendant.’

Lin Ming’s spear light twisted and an endless flood of thunder surged out, directly breaking apart that round ancient ash moon.

“He broke it so easily?”

That was a transcendent divine might. Even if Cang Liang wasn’t able to study it in detail, it still shouldn’t have been so easily broken.

Lin Ming began to walk towards Cang Liang, one step at a time.

“You’ve gone too far! You’ve forced my hand!” Cang Liang shouted, “Ancient Ash Moon second style – Moon Shimmering Through the Heavens and Earth!”

As Cang Liang attacked for a second type, true essence erupted to the limit. All the veins in his body bulged out as he clearly overdrew his own strength.

However, facing Cang Liang’s desperate attack, Lin Ming simply thrust his spear out. Flame and thunder flashed out and the ancient ash moon strike was directly split in half by Lin Ming’s spear.

Peng!

Cang Liang’s protective true essence shattered. He flew backwards and crashed down onto the arena stage.

Lin Ming easily achieved victory. The gap was far larger than everyone else imagined.

“I already knew it would be like this. Cang Liang and Lin Ming simply aren’t on the same level at all. We already said that Lin Ming would be able to advance into the top 10, but not many people believed us.” Underneath the arena stage, a Vast Universe Heavenly Palace disciple spoke with sneering disdain. Was their Vast Universe Heavenly Palace’s Divine Seal Altar so easy to climb? Even if one resorted to tricks, it definitely wasn’t easy to climb. Even with any amount of shortcuts, it was as difficult as reaching the heavens.

“There’s nothing that can be done. People only believe their own eyes, not the rumors they hear with their ears. Moreover, there were too many First Martial Meeting semifinal areas, and many of those that were first ranked in their areas were blown out of proportion.” Zhao Ji said. Although he wasn’t too happy with Lin Ming, he couldn’t help but acknowledge his strength.

“After this, Lin Ming might not need to fight again. Many people will simply admit defeat instead of having to face him in battle. In each group, everyone will have to fight 15 people after all. If they admit defeat they can save their strength for the next fight.”

The disciples of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace had guessed correctly. After Cang Liang was defeated, Lin Ming’s second opponent simply admitted defeat.

The third, fourth, and fifth matches were also the same.

Lin Ming easily obtained a five match winning streak, and Dragon Fang was also the same. In the eyes of everyone else, a genius like Lin Ming was simply sparring in this brief interlude. Their real strength would be revealed in the true finals.

Chapter 1282 – Easily Passing Qualification

In the group stage, because the masters were seeded into different groups, Lin Ming was victorious all the way to 10 wins without a single hiccup.

Dragon Fang also had a 10 win winning streak. Not just that, but Hang Chi and two other Empyrean direct disciples easily obtained a 10 win winning streak.

Although these were group matches, one could see many things. There were always interested parties that soon summarized the top 50 people of all the divisions. Lin Ming and Dragon Fang were arranged within these rankings. The 30 Empyrean direct disciples were naturally included too, as there wasn’t a weak Empyrean direct disciple. After all, the weak did not possess the qualifications to become Empyrean descendants.

Another matter worth mentioning was Divine Dream Heavenly Palace. Besides the Heavenly Palace Saintess, Fairy Frost Dream, there were also three core disciples. None of these core disciples were weak, and they were all placed into this list of 50 names.

The three of them were collectively referred to as the Three Fairies of the Divine Dream. Their names were – Frost Charm, Frost Cloud, and Frost Moon.

In Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, all disciples of Frost Dream’s generation had the surname Frost, but, only the top disciple had the qualifications to be called ‘Dream’.

This was where Frost Dream’s name originated from.

“Divine Dream Heavenly Palace… is truly formidable.” In the group that the three fairies were located in, Lin Ming silently watched them fight.

The one on the arena stage was Frost Moon. She simply stared at her opponent, and without a single move, victory and defeated had already been decided.

Her opponent slumped to his knees, all strength fleeing his body.

And this person was a second ranked genius from his semifinals area. A genius that was ranked second out of 100 great worlds actually had no ability to resist in front of Frost Moon!

“Frost Moon wins!”

The World King managing this arena area announced without expression. This result was something he already expected.

Although the three fairies were formidable, there were actually very few that forfeited when they fought them. This was because as disciples of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, their statuses were special. They were mysterious and mystical, the definition of perfection. Even if the other geniuses knew they couldn’t defeat them, they still fought. At least, when they left the First Martial Meeting, they would be able to boast that they fought with the fairies of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace. Even if they were horribly defeated they could still speak with pride about this.

Losing to one of the fairies from Divine Dream Heavenly Palace was not a shameful matter. Rather, it was something to show off to others.

“Divine Dream Heavenly Palace is truly a strange and mystical influence. The other Heavenly Palaces often have trillions of disciples, but Divine Dream Heavenly Palace only has several hundred. Each one of them must be an outstanding individual amongst all outstanding elites!” Lin Ming thought. But at this time, a voice suddenly echoed out in his mind. He was startled and then happily said, “Miss Mo, you’ve finished your seclusion?”

Within the Magic Cube space, even an Empyrean didn’t have the ability to sense Mo Eversnow. Of course, it wouldn’t matter even if they did.

“Mm, I’ve also realized something from that incomplete bone shard. I’ve been verifying it with the Celestial Tyrant Manual, one truth at a time, and now I’ve understood things that I didn’t before. The Celestial Tyrant Manual’s Hundred Layered Waves can go another step further.”

“How is Fishy?”

Lin Ming hadn’t looked into the Magic Cube space for some time now, and Mo Eversnow and Fishy had lived inside as they pleased.

“Fishy has been sleeping more and more these days. Although she has eaten up a great number of violet sun crystals, there still hasn’t been any change within her body.”

Mo Eversnow shook her head. She guessed that Fishy had some special background and was certainly unique in some way, but up until now she still hadn’t seen just how this specialness manifested within Fishy’s body.

Moreover, Fishy’s growth was much slower than that of other little girls. Through these years, she still retained the appearance of an 11-12 year old little girl.

Of the 50 people, besides the Three Fairies of the Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, another person also caught Lin Ming’s attention.

He called himself Jun Bluemoon and he was dressed all in white. From his head to his toes, he emitted the aura of a sad and melancholic scholar. A pot of wine hung from his waist and he used a long sword. What was strange was that this sword seemed rusty. From all appearances it looked like a common mortal sword that was stained with blood and rust.

“This weapon is…”

As Lin Ming saw this sword, he felt something indescribable in his heart. This was absolutely not an ordinary sword. The sword blade emitted a light pressure and Lin Ming still wasn’t able to see what rank weapon it was. He wasn’t able to judge whether it was a spirit artifact or not.

“This is…”

Lin Ming deeply looked at that sword. If it was truly an unrivalled treasure sword, why would it be rusted? Those were clearly true rust stains that covered the blade and not some deliberate camouflage.

“I also cannot see the mysteries behind that sword.” Mo Eversnow said from within the Magic Cube, shaking her head. She could not see through that weapon at all. “It could be Jun Bluemoon’s lucky chance, just like your Magic Cube.”

“Maybe.” Lin Ming sighed. In the 3000 great worlds of the Divine Realm and the quadrillion trillion lives that existed within it, there were bound to be far too many people that came across a heaven-defying lucky chance. There was the dual body and energy cultivator Shiku, Dragon Fang with his Three Lives Pupils, and now this Jun Bluemoon. All of these people unveiled an unfathomable feeling.

Time passed quickly. It was the second day, with evening soon approaching. At this point, the continuous battles had gone on for two days and one night.

Some matches were extremely bitter and intense, and some matches revealed an absolute disparity in strength.

At his final 15th match, Lin Ming finally met an opponent that fought him with everything they had. This person came from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.

“You are strong, but I won’t give up just because of this. I want to know just how you climbed up the Divine Seal Altar!”

As a disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, the Divine Seal Altar was a legend to them. And, the one who broke this legend was not a disciple of their Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, but Lin Ming. This caused some disciples to be unable to let this go. They hoped to fight Lin Ming to confirm just what sort of strength he had.

As soon as this martial artist faced Lin Ming, his entire body shook as his joints crackled and popped. He stayed at Palace 72 and out of the 14 matches so far, he had only lost a single one, which was against the disciple from Mount Potala, Hang Chi. This was also a reasonable defeat. Hang Chi was an Empyrean descendant. Moreover, he came from the Heavenly Palace with the deepest background in the entire Divine Realm. It was simply impossible for this martial artist to defeat him.

“Take my move! Savage Dragon Crossing the River!”

As soon as this martial artist attacked, it was with his ultimate final killing blow. His saber came slashing towards Lin Ming with overwhelming momentum. In that moment, all of the space around Lin Ming seemed to be locked in place. This Vast Universe Heavenly Palace disciple actually used the Concept of Space, moreover, his attainments weren’t low; he had steadily entered into the fourth level Concept.

“Blue Lotus Flame Dance!”

Without expression, Lin Ming swept his spear out. The Fire Laws fused together and a wild and savage spear light gathered into a shimmering beam that instantly broke through his opponent’s saber light!

Compared to Lin Ming the difference was simply too great. With the suppression of Laws and also absolute strength, there was no way for him to resist.

“What!?”

The Vast Universe Heavenly Palace disciple stared with wide eyes. Even though he knew he wasn’t Lin Ming’s match, it was only now when he faced him that he discovered how great the disparity was.

Woosh!

Lin Ming shot out his second spear strike. This spear strike ripped open his opponent’s protective true essence and sent him flying backwards.

“Lin Ming, victory!”

The World King powerhouse managing this arena said without any surprise. Thus, with this, Lin Ming won 15 matches and successfully passed the pre-finals.

Lin Ming had now entered the true finals.

Chapter 1286 – Three Swords

“19th match, Dragon Fang against Yuwen Bo!”

Vast Cosmos loudly announced from above the martial stage. Dragon Fang had come from the same Gravemoon Star contest area as Lin Ming. Their strength was similar, thus the two of them had their first matches at similar times. After Lin Ming was Dragon Fang.

Dragon Fang’s opponent was Yuwen Bo. Yuwen Bo came from the Vast Universe World and was the direct bloodline descendant of Vast Universe World’s Great World King, the Wide Universe World King. During the pre-finals rankings, he was someone who far surpassed Nether Limitless.

Dragon Fang’s tremendous strength was clear to everyone who could see. And now, after Lin Ming defeated Frost Moon, very few people believed that Yuwen Bo would win. Even so, the moment Yuwen Bo entered the stage, he immediately aroused cheers from the audience. Since Vast Universe World was the host world of the First Martial Meeting finals and this land was where Yuwen Bo came from, he naturally had many supporters.

“Please advise.” Dragon Fang bowed.

Facing Dragon Fang, Yuwen Bo’s complexion was grim.

As soon as the match started with Vast Cosmos’s announcement, Yuwen Bo struck out with his entire strength. He knew that his chances of defeating Dragon Fang were extremely small; if he didn’t start with everything he had then there wouldn’t be any chance at all for him.

“Thousand Mile Blade!”

Yuwen Bo’s sword slashed and the sword light gathered into a beam that was compressed to the limit. All around the sword light, space began to distort and the sword light itself was nearly invisible, as if it was hidden in the twisted space.

With this extreme speed and nearly imperceptible attack trajectory, it was nearly impossible to avoid.

However, it was a pity that his opponent was Dragon Fang.

As that Thousand Mile Blade neared Dragon Fang, the flow of time around Dragon Fang rapidly slowed to a crawl. Correspondingly, Yuwen Bo’s sword light also slowed down.

Dragon Fang calmly avoided that sword light as his own sword light slashed down at Yuwen Bo’s chest.

Humm –

Energy whistled. Yuwen Bo’s pupils contracted as he rapidly drew backwards.

But at the same time, Dragon Fang’s body split into four copies as he attacked Yuwen Bo from four directions. Spatial mirror images were not illusions but true avatars that contained a portion of the true body’s striking power.

Four swords gathered as one. Yuwen Bo shouted out, revolving his true essence to the limit to resist this strike, but the difference in strength was simply far too great.

Peng!

The sword light exploded and Yuwen Bo’s body flew backwards. He had suffered a fast and easy defeat.

“Dragon Fang, victory!”

Vast Cosmos cast a deep look at Dragon Fang. This result was already within his expectations. During the first rounds of the finals, before the first tier of 10 people was chosen, the true peak geniuses would obtain victory without any difficulties.

“This Dragon Fang is too strong! Those two fellows that came from Gravemoon Star, Lin Ming and Dragon Fang, are both freaks!”

“I heard that Dragon Fang has some strange eyes. Once he releases them, his combat strength will multiply. But he didn’t even activate them. His disparity with Yuwen Bo was too great; he didn’t need to use them at all.”

People didn’t understand the Three Lives Pupils, but they could sense that there was something formidable about Dragon Fang’s Laws.

“20th match, Lan Ling against Jun Bluemoon!”

Vast Cosmos announced once again.

Lan Ling was a disciple of Empyrean Freespirit!

In terms of status and strength, Empyrean Freespirit was considered in the upper reaches amongst the Empyreans. In the previous First Martial Meetings, the disciples of Freespirit Heavenly Place had attained superbly wonderful results.

Lan Ling confidently stepped onto the arena stage. And across from him, Jun Bluemoon still had his sword strung across his shoulders, a pot of wine hanging from his waist. He held a cute and lovable little bunny in his hands.

“Little Bunny, stay here for a short while. I will be back as soon as possible.”

As Jun Bluemoon spoke, he placed the small bunny onto his chair. He lovingly traced the body of the small bunny and then grasped his sword as he moved towards the arena stage.

As Lan Ling saw this his mouth curved up in a joking smile, ”At this time, you’re still in the mood to raise a bunny?”

Jun Bluemoon didn’t reply.

Lan Ling was immediately angered after being ignored like this. “Why don’t you admit defeat?”

“Admit defeat? Why would I admit defeat? I believe that to defeat you, three sword strikes should be enough.”

The entire audience was shocked by Jun Bluemoon’s words.

“Three swords!?”

Lan Ling wasn’t someone on the same level as Yuwen Bo. He was a true and blue Empyrean descendant, moreover, his strength wasn’t weak amongst the Empyrean descendants either. There were even some people who believed that he had the qualifications to struggle for a spot in the top 10. In this situation, just how arrogant was Jun Bluemoon to say those words?

“What background does this boy have? Is he insane?”

“Three swords to defeat Lan Ling? Only someone like Xiao Moxian would dare to speak such words!”

“This is too crazy!”

Many spectators widened their eyes until the whites showed. Before, besides being first in his semifinals contest, Jun Bluemoon hadn’t shown any amazing performance at all. And, being first in his semifinals division didn’t mean anything at all. Many people didn’t even think he would enter the top 50.

“Hahaha!”

Lan Ling wildly laughed. “Interesting, how interesting! I don’t remember how long it’s been since someone has spoken such arrogant words to me! Defeat me in three swords? Good! Great! Then show me just how you’ll defeat me!”

Qing!

Lan Ling drew out a saber. Although he was smiling, his smiling expression was icy cold and a killing intent exuded from his entire body. From this point, one could see that he wasn’t really smiling at all, but rather filled with murderous intent from Jun Bluemoon’s mockery of him!

Jun Bluemoon quietly flourished his sword. His sword was four feet long and the edge did not shine with a glimmering sheen but was completely stained with dust-colored rust. These rust stains made it look like a common mortal sword that was stained by blood for a long time and ended up being dyed in it.

Jun Bluemoon grasped his sword and stood proudly on the arena stage. His clothes were as white as snow. His looks were handsome and delicate, as if he were a lonely and melancholic scholar. If it weren’t for the sword in his hands, then if he were found in a mortal nation, it would be easy to imagine him as someone participating in a test for national office. In truth, even though he had a sword in hand he still didn’t seem to resemble a martial artist because that sword was far too shabby. Even if one were to throw it out in the street no one would pick it up.

“You think that sword can defeat me? I think you’re the insane one here.” Lan Ling sneered as he looked at that sword.

From appearances alone, that sword seemed like common metal. But, Lin Ming could actually faintly feel that it contained some special divine power, an indescribable feeling that was even similar to the Divine Seal Altar.

“That sword…” Lin Ming frowned, “Just what background does Jun Bluemoon come from?”

“The first sword! Light!”

At this time, Jun Bluemoon finally moved. With a wave of his sword, light began to be swallowed up. All of the surrounding rays of light were completely twisted up by this sword, gathering onto it. In that instant, the entire space in a 10 mile radius around Jun Bluemoon had become a jet black world!

“This is…” Lan Ling suddenly paused, startled. Without enough time to react, Jun Bluemoon’s sword edge began to emit a flaming brilliance. This light starkly contrasted with the world of absolute darkness, blinding to the eye. This light was not ordinary at all. Even if a martial artist didn’t look at it they would still be burnt by this radiance.

Even Lin Ming couldn’t help but close his eyes in this situation. And not too far away from him, Dragon Fang’s pupils had shrunk, becoming as small as the tip of a needle. He had opened the Three Lives Pupils.

“Light manipulation?”

A martial artist cried out in awe.

“No, those are the Yin Yang Laws!” Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. He had experienced heavenly tribulation and the last two levels had been a simultaneous yin and yang tribulation. He certainly knew how strong the Yin Yang Laws were.

Within the Divine Realm, the Space and Time Laws were considered some of the strongest and most difficult Laws to practice, but they were only two of them; they were not the true kings of the Laws. There were some Laws that could absolutely stand on equal footing with them. For instance, the Yin Yang Laws!

Yin yang energies were the foundation of all existence. In fact, there were even less people that cultivated the Yin Yang Laws than those that cultivated the Time and Space Laws.

“Free Spirited King!”

As this dual yin yang divine light seemed to swallow everything, Lan Ling roared out. A red saber light split through the skies like a pillar that held up the heavens, nearly cutting the skies in half. As many martial artists saw this saber light they felt their hearts rapidly racing in their chests.

“Transcendent divine might! That is a transcendent divine might!”

“That’s right, this is Empyrean Freespirit’s own transcendent divine might, the Free Spirited King! Although this transcendent divine might isn’t yet complete, it is still a transcendent divine might. There are few that can match it in power!”

Lan Ling used his transcendent divine might in order to break through Jun Bluemoon as well as his Yin Yang Laws! But, this was also proof that Jun Bluemoon was too strong, leaving no choice but for Lan Ling to fight with everything he had.

For a martial artist of common origin to reach this step was already an accomplishment to be proud of.

“The second sword! Cut!”

Jun Bluemoon aimed at that blazing red saber light and slashed out with his sword. It was unknown what move he used but the world trembled as if the sun and moon had disappeared, as if this sword had discolored the world, leaving nothing but absolute black and absolute white. The saber light that Lan Ling shot out was torn apart by Jun Bluemoon’s sword light, completely disintegrating!

But at the same time, Jun Bluemoon’s sword light also melted away. The sword light and saber light mutually cancelled each other out, both attacks simultaneously disappearing.

“The third sword! Defeat!”

And unimaginably, after Jun Bluemoon struck out with two nearly unrivalled sword strikes, he actually slashed out for a third time in less than a split second!

This third sword strike was even stronger than the first and second attacks combined!

As for Lan Ling, after using the incomplete transcendent divine might that Empyrean Freespirit had created, he had used up his strength and wasn’t able to summon up any new strength yet. He could only watch helplessly on as Jun Bluemoon’s sword came cutting down at him!

“How could this be possible?”

Lan Ling’s face was filled with disbelief. He couldn’t believe that Jun Bluemoon would have such powerful strength that he was able to launch three terrifying sword strikes in rapid succession. Did he hold inexhaustible world power within him?

But there was no longer time to think about such things. Jun Bluemoon’s last sword strike easily ripped through his saber light and broke through his protective true essence.

With the faint sound of an explosion, Lan Ling’s protective true essence collapsed and he was sent flying backwards like a broken ragdoll.

Lan Ling spat out a great mouthful of blood, heavily crashing into the ground, completely defeated.

The entire audience was shocked.

After saying he would defeat Lan Ling in three swords, Jun Bluemoon had not used one strike too many or one strike too few. He had defeated his opponent exactly as he said he would.

Moreover, his opponent was a true Empyrean descendant. Even amongst Empyrean descendants, Lan Ling hadn’t been that weak, but he had still lost miserably.

Just what sort of background did Jun Bluemoon have?

Even Lin Ming who had long since noticed Jun Bluemoon was surprised. Lan Ling was indeed strong, but his strength only served to further contrast the freakish strength of Jun Bluemoon.

Lin Ming even began to wonder, between Dragon Fang and Jun Bluemoon, just who was stronger?

“This Jun Bluemoon… I heard that he is a common martial artist. How is that possible?”

It was known before that Dragon Fang came from a common origin, but in truth he was also an Empyrean descendant. Now it was said that Jun Bluemoon also came from a mortal background, but how could a martial artist of such a humble background reach this boundary?

Chapter 1289 – The Final Battles Begin

“That Lin Ming, he sent Ram Saber flying back with a single spear!”

The audience was bewildered; Lin Ming was too fierce. In speed, Laws, and everything else he was an outstanding genius, and even his frontal combat skills were terrifying. He was a versatile martial artist with seemingly no weakness at all.

“It seems Lin Ming’s speculated ranking will rise.”

“You’re very powerful.” Ram Saber said. He suddenly stood up and ripped off his tattered clothes with his hands, revealing a dark and thickly muscled body that seemed forged from metal. It was unknown just what special physique he had, but after his bloodline was activated, his originally skinny body grew to epic proportions. His muscles bulged out and his strength rose to a ridiculous level.

Ram Saber was like a wild beast as he stared at Lin Ming and wiped the leaking blood from the edges of his lips.

“Mm? You can still stand?” Lin Ming was surprised. That strike was nearly his complete physical strength just now, but it seemed that Ram Saber’s resilience and defensive capabilities had surpassed his imagination. To be able to be included in the Divine Seal 12 Children, this Ram Saber was truly extraordinary.

He could already imagine that the fights from now on would be much more difficult! Dragon Fang, Xiao Moxian, Frost Dream, Hang Chi, none of those powerhouses were easy to deal with.

“In truth, I have already lost this battle. Master was right; there is no limit in this universe. There is always a higher heaven and a stronger person. My cultivation is still not enough. But, I will not allow myself to quit like this. I still have one final strike. If you can receive it then I will admit defeat!”

Originally, for matches on the arena stage, they were not meant to be overdone. After being defeated by one move, in the strictest sense that was already a loss.

Ram Saber lifted his arms, his hands suspended high above his head. As he did this, his aura suddenly changed, becoming far more bloodthirsty and maniacal, just like a demon. His eyes revealed a look of utter bloodlust.

“Blood Prison Saber Sutra, the first move – Demon Slayer!”

Ram Saber spoke out each word of his technique as clearly as possible because of the respect he held towards his master. The Blood Prison Saber Sutra was the transcendent divine might created by his master!

“This junior Ram Saber actually managed to cultivate the Blood Prison Saber Sutra. This transcendent divine might is the total knowledge of Saber Sovereign’s saber dao. There are numerous techniques contained within it and even more Laws. However, the Blood Prison Saber Sutra is different from most transcendent divine mights – the threshold to train in it is absurdly high. I never imagined that Ram Saber would be able to successfully learn the first move.”

On the honored seating area, a blue-clothed old man slowly spoke. Every transcendent divine might was extremely comprehensive and the contents contained within them were rich beyond description. After all, they were the life summaries of everything an Empyrean had learned.

At this time, Ram Saber moved. His body faded into a red shadow as the thick saber in his hands slashed straight down. This saber seemed to cut apart the world, swallowing all!

As this saber chopped down, a trace of longing flashed in Ram Saber’s pupils. For that moment, between the heavens and earth, it seemed as if only this saber existed. Even though the audience was dozens of miles away, they still felt an illusion as if they were cut by this saber. They were affected by the saber light and felt their blood energy tumble in chaos.

Lin Ming, who had to bear the brunt of this attack, suddenly felt as if all the blood vessels in his body were about to explode and like the flow of his blood was reversing. He was finding it hard to withstand.

These were the Blood Laws. By using the Laws, one could direct a person’s blood flow. If this saber strike were to cut down at a million man army, it could cause all of their blood to rush out from their blood vessels and rain down into the air. Their bodies would be reduced to nothing but ruined flesh and rivers of blood would form, gathering together into a true blood pond hell!

The name of Blood Prison Saber Sutra partially came from this. In the past, Saber Sovereign had relied on this sword technique to kill countless people!

“Die!”

Ram Saber shouted out. A crimson saber light as thick as a python chopped down heavily!

In that moment, Lin Ming opened all seven of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates in his body. The Heretical God Force erupted and the blood of the Ancient Phoenix combusted, his fighting strength reaching the limit.

Lin Ming thrust out his spear. From behind him, the phantom of a giant divine tree appeared, the crown towering into the heavens. Underneath the shroud of this divine tree phantom, Lin Ming’s power of blood suddenly stabilized. No matter how crazy or fierce the Blood Prison Saber Sutra was, Lin Ming remained as solid and steady as Mount Tai.

“Explode!”

Thunder and fire crossed together and a powerful strength burst out. Lin Ming’s strike smashed into Ram Saber’s crimson saber light, causing the saber light to explode into countless fragments that fell down like endless rose petals, even pulverizing the stone floor into pieces!

Puff!

Ram Saber spat out a mouthful of blood, his body shaking as his complexion turned paper white.

“I have lost, convincingly and fully!”

Ram Saber used his thick saber to support himself, barely managing to stand up. That strike just now had created too great of a burden on his body and he had also been struck by Lin Ming’s counterattack, making his injuries even worse! For him to still be standing here was completely because of his special bloodline and formidable body.

“Without standing on the stage of the entire Divine Realm, I would never have imagined that so many extreme characters exist. What Master says is right: the road ahead of me is still long.”

Ram Saber closed his eyes, thinking to himself. Before he came, the Saber Sovereign had already warned Ram Saber that he would only be coming here to gain experience and temper himself; it would be impossible for him to obtain first place.

Ram Saber had originally refused to accept this, but now it seemed that his master was correct!

He had been one of the Saber Sovereign’s 22 disciples, and after undergoing countless life or death tribulations, he had emerged as one of the only two surviving. His body had a special bloodline and his physique was comparable to that of an ancient vicious beast. Not just that, but his perception was extremely high, allowing him to practice the Blood Prison Saber Sutra’s first move at only the late Divine Sea realm. And with the Saber Sovereign personally teaching him, he lacked neither resources nor inheritances. But even in such a situation, he had completely lost. He wouldn’t even be able to enter the top 10!

It could only be said that there were too many geniuses in the Divine Realm. There were those extreme characters with a great destiny gathered upon their body, a destiny that would bring them to an unimaginable future.

As Ram Saber suffered his sad defeat, the audience fell into a deep silence, many of them not expecting such a result. Although Ram Saber’s last strike had been extremely strong, it had still been blocked by Lin Ming. Lin Ming was like a great mountain, steady and unshakeable!

To this point, the performances Lin Ming had revealed so far had been inferior to Jun Bluemoon and the Monster Prince. Even so, he had never been defeated. This caused many people to be unable to determine just where his limits were.

“Divine Seal 12 Children… no, it should be called the Divine Seal 10 Children now. This Lin Ming might be able to rank in the top six.”

“What do you know? Don’t just blindly guess with what you see in your eyes. You’ll be like everyone else that is reaching conclusions based upon a tiny amount of incomplete information. Lin Ming definitely didn’t give his all just now. However, Jun Bluemoon isn’t an exception – he is also hiding his strength. It is impossible to truly tell who is stronger and weaker so far. And as the finals continue, Frost Dream and Xiao Moxian will likely have an unshakeable status. As for Hang Chi, he has yet to reveal his true strength, but each of the rumors swirling around him is more terrifying than the last.”

“There is no need to doubt Hang Chi’s strength. He has always kept a low profile and has never revealed anything unnecessary. As for his strength, there are several high level figures that can guarantee he is extremely strong. You can’t judge him so far based upon his current performance in the First Martial Meeting.”

The final ranking results of the Heaven Proclamation were impossibly confusing. No one could say whether there would be an even darker horse to appear from amongst the 10 final people. As for those several Empyrean descendants with the greatest limelight on them, it was hard to judge who was stronger and weaker.

“Lin Ming, victory!”

Vast Cosmos solemnly declared. As the finals continued on, even Vast Cosmos was finding it hard to maintain his calm. This round of the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting had far surpassed all other times in the past. The several top ranked characters here would all have high chances of becoming Empyreans in the future.

In the past First Martial Meetings, the first ranked Empyrean descendant on the Heaven Proclamation would at most become a half-step Emyprean in the future. As for the first ranked Great World King disciple on the Earth Proclamation, they would usually become a Great World King in the future.

Only in a single First Martial Meeting every million years or so would a true future Empyrean be born.

But in this current First Martial Meeting, three young Empyreans had already appeared. Moreover, once these people became Empyreans, they would not be ordinary Empyreans either. Among them, Xiao Moxian had the greatest potential. In the future, there was a high chance that she would become someone outstanding even amongst the many Empyreans. Although she might not be able to stand on par with Empyrean Divine Dream, she should at least be able to stand evenly with Empyrean Demondawn! This was an unthinkable event.

As Vast Cosmos saw so many young Empyreans appear before him, how could he maintain a tranquil mood? “Heroes rise in turbulent times. With so many geniuses appearing, is this a sign that the great calamity approaches?”

In the last round of the qualifying finals, there were many winners who obtained an unbroken winning streak, all of them glorious!

After Lin Ming finished his match, White King, Dragon Fang, Jun Bluemoon, and the rest also smoothly defeated their opponents, directly joining the final battle list!

Lin Ming wasn’t surprised by this at all.

At the end, Shiku defeated the last person of the Divine Seal 12 Children and smoothly entered the next stage.

Thus, for the final deciding battles, the 10 people were –

Frost Dream, Xiao Moxian, Hang Chi, Lin Ming, White King, Dragon Fang, Jun Bluemoon, the Monster Prince, Shiku, Hua Xuan.

Although one couldn’t exactly determine the final ranking results, one could still make guesses based on what they knew. According to these speculations, Vast Universe Heavenly Palace opened a gambling house.

In the past it was only some World King influences making some small bets, and this time it was a gambling house directly managed by an Empyrean influence. With Vast Universe Heavenly Palace conducting this event, it was naturally their right to do so.

The compensation rates were –

Frost Dream’s odds to be first place were 1 to 1.5.

Xiao Moxian and Hang Chi’s odds were 1 to 2.

Jun Bluemoon’s first place odds were 1 to 6.5. His odds to reach the top three were 1 to 2.

Lin Ming and the Monster Prince’s first place odds were 1 to 7. Their odds to reach the top three were 1 to 3.

Dragon Fang’s first place odds were 1 to 8. His odds to reach the top three were 1 to 4.

Shiku’s odds to reach the top three were 1 to 10.

Hua Xuan’s odds to reach the top three were 1 to 15.

Finally, for White King, as a disciple of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, he was excluded from the gambling house and his odds for ranking in the top few also weren’t included. This was to prevent others from gossiping. Although an Empyrean influence wouldn’t do something as ridiculous as throwing a match for profit, it was still best to immediately put an end to anyone who would try to use that as a pretext for speaking ill of them.

As these compensation rates came out, it immediately caused a furor.

Frost Dream, Xiao Moxian, and Hang Chi did not have any odds to reach the top three because it was already widely recognized that their chances of reaching the top three were a near guarantee. As for Shiku and Hua Xuan, they didn’t have any odds of winning first place because it was universally agreed to be impossible for them.

This caused Hua Xuan and Shiku to both feel very depressed. “These people from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace really consider us worthless.”

“They only have Lin Ming and Jun Bluemoon in their eyes. They look down their noses at us far too much!”

Hua Xuan and Shiku didn’t publicly complain; they could only rely on their own results to earn back their honor.

However, there were so people that were definitely not happy.

“How come my odds are only 1 to 7?” The Monster Prince laughed as he saw these gambling house odds, “Who was the mentally ill retard that arranged these odds? And who the hell is this Lin Ming to think that he can compare with the likes of me? And that Jun Bluemoon too; his odds are actually above my own!”

The Monster Prince’s voice was loud and brash. Both Lin Ming and Jun Bluemoon could hear him.

Jun Bluemoon ignored him, simply continuing to hug and pet the little bunny in his hands. But, Lin Ming’s eyes turned icy cold as he looked at the Monster Prince.

Chapter 1293 – Enraging the Monster Race

Virtual Disintegration was Lin Ming’s self-created skill. Using virtual fire to attack an opponent’s mind, all of their anger, hatred, and jealousy would become Lin Ming’s weapon. He could use it to burn down his opponents and swallow them alive!

And, the Monster Prince was someone who was incomparably arrogant and easily lost his temper. If the Monster Prince’s flames of anger and jealousy were used to attack him, then the power of Virtual Disintegration would multiply!

Hu – !

Virtual flames burned. Lin Ming’s spear was like a homing missile, unable to be dodged!

The Monster Prince’s pupils shrank. He only felt as if all the anger in his body was being ignited by this spear, attacking his mind!

Virtual Fire!

The Monster Prince had an extraordinary level of experience and naturally recognized this type of fire. It was the fifth level Concept of Fire – Virtual Fire. The Monster Prince was also well aware of his own weaknesses and shortcomings. If he was struck by this spear, victory and defeat would be instantly settled!

From the point when Lin Ming had used the Heretical God fire and thunder to tear open the space cage and attack the Monster Prince with Virtual Disintegration, his series of attacks had been so fast that it was nearly impossible to react to.

As the Monster Prince saw this spear coming at him, his eyes sharpened. His entire body erupted with energy!

“10,000 Monster Domain!”

The Monster Prince roared. In that moment, countless horrifying sounds filled the air! These sounds were like the cry of a dragon, the roars of a tiger, a long and endless sonic wave that spread past the horizon!

Awhoo – !

From within the Monster Prince’s body, countless monster phantoms rushed out!

These great monsters were as tall as a hundred feet and as small as a palm. Their shapes also came in all sorts of strange and macabre styles. Some looked like lions, ghosts and zombies, some had vicious horns and spikes, and some were dripping with tentacles of blood!

In that instant, 9999 monster spirits rushed out from the Monster Prince’s body, covering a scope of several miles around the Monster Prince!

Lin Ming’s virtual fire that he sent out was torn to pieces by those monster spirits and swallowed up!

“Mm? This is…” Lin Ming was startled. After he joined in on the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, not only did he encounter all sorts of unimaginable geniuses, but he witnessed all kinds of mysteries techniques. This ability in front of him seemed like a type of domain, there was actually this sort of domain!

“Haha, how do you like my 10,000 Monster Domain? I want to see just how you break through it!”

The Monster Prince crazily laughed!

“10,000 Monster Domain, I never imagined that this Monster Prince would be able to use the 10,000 Monster Domain…” In the honored seating section, an extraordinarily experienced person spoke out. He had a great deal of understanding into the monster race’s cultivation methods.

“Genius martial artists of the monster race, because of the royal bloodline within their bodies, have the ability to attract the worship of monster spirits, forming a monster spirit domain. There are different levels, from the 100 Monster Domain, 1000 Monster Domain, 10,000 Monster Domain, and even the legendary 100,000 Monster Domain. The last stage is only a legend, and the 10,000 Monster Domain can be called the top of all monster domains.”

A white-clothed old man spookily said. Beside him, another thin middle-aged man nodded his head, saying, “With 9999 monster spirits as well as the Monster Prince himself, that is a total of 10,000 monster spirits, forming a perfect 10,000 Monster Domain. It is known as an unbreakable domain! Not only does it have immense striking power, but at the same time, any person that steps into the 10,000 Monster Domain will be swallowed up within it. Once the 10,000 Monster Domain is used, that is the same as having to deal with 10,000 monster spirits. This sort of offensive and defensive ability is far more profound than Ram Saber’s Saber King Domain.

“But even if Lin Ming’s momentum is destroyed here, it still won’t extinguish the glory and fame he’s gained so far. Lin Ming is amazing. He is able to use Thunder and Fire Laws to tear apart Space Laws of the same level. No matter how this battle ends, there is no loser. This generation of juniors is truly far too strong.”

The monster race’s 10,000 Monster Domain was the pride of the royal bloodline. In a chaotic battle of armies, if a monster of the royal family were to open their 10,000 Monster Domain and rush into the midst of an army, they could have their 10,000 monsters swallow up their enemies’ flesh and blood, becoming unstoppable. Moreover, the more flesh and blood these monster spirits ate, the more brutal and vicious they would become. In the end, even an army of a million could be completely killed off by a single person!

The Monster Prince coldly sneered at Lin Ming, “Hehe, my 10,000 Monster Domain can annihilate all life in the world. You, human, are nothing but a fat mouse, barely enough for a bite! Now die!”

As the Monster Prince spoke, he grasped his halberd and rushed at Lin Ming.

“Halberd Shattering the Universe!”

The Monster Prince’s falling halberd came down like a collapsing mountain. At the same time, all of the monster spirits around the Monster Prince also hurtled towards Lin Ming!

Together with the Monster Prince, that was 10,000 monster spirits. In addition to that vicious and desolate halberd, this terrifying attack even caused the audience that was dozens of miles away to shake with fear and awe. If they were placed within that 10,000 Monster Domain, they might be instantly eaten up until nothing was left remaining!

A single person to fight 10,000 monsters, how could one possibly continue fighting!?

In that instant, facing the aggressive threat of the Monster Prince, Lin Ming’s expression still didn’t change. He held his Phoenix Blood Spear straight, all of his true essence and world power erupting from his inner world!

As 10,000 monster spirits howled, Lin Ming stood tall and proud, his body straight like a spear!

“Bloom in splendor – Prime Emperor Lotus Flower!”

In that moment, a blood red lotus flower slowly bloomed behind Lin Ming, so red and lush it seemed as if it would drip blood!

This was the Primordius martial intent!

The thick and vast grandmist space erupted, rolling outwards like a spreading storm. The boundless aura turned into a mighty tsunami that flushed towards those 10,000 monster spirits!

Grandmist space was able to annihilate everything. Flesh and blood, Laws, souls, not even monster spirits were an exception!

This was nearly the highest level domain in the Divine Realm, the domain that stood at the greatest heights. Even the 10,000 Monster Domain was suppressed!

Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng!

Underneath the shroud of the grandmist space, monster spirits began to emit pitiful and miserable screams before they collapsed into ash, gone forever!

The massive numbers of monster spirits that were destroyed turned into elementary grandmist energy!

“What!?”

The Monster Prince was shocked. His 10,000 Monster Domain had been broken! Not only was he astonished, but the entire audience was dumbstruck. Lin Ming’s domain was actually so fierce! Just how many techniques did he have in the end?

“My monster spirits!” The Monster Prince’s eyes were bloodshot with rage. If his monster spirits died he could still create more, but he had to use enough flesh and blood to do so. It was extremely troublesome.

“You are courting death!”

As the Monster Prince saw the countless monster spirits that he had raised himself being killed off by Lin Ming, he grasped his desolate halberd and smashed it down at Lin Ming’s head!

But after entering the grandmist space, the Monster Prince found his strength rapidly fading away. An incomparably thick atmosphere made him pay several times the strength in order to complete a single movement.

“This damned domain!”

The Monster Prince was surprised. He felt as if he had fallen into a thick swamp as his speed rapidly dropped.

At the same time, Lin Ming rushed towards the Monster Prince.

“Just die. Virtual Disintegration!”

Lin Ming thrust out his spear. Underneath the suppression of the grandmist space, the Phoenix Blood Spear’s spear light shot right towards the Monster Prince!

“You small fry!”

The Monster Prince was utterly enraged. His body emitted more crackling sounds as a crimson color washed over his entire body. It seemed that he had used some sort of arcane skill!

He forcefully cast off the shackles of the grandmist space and smashed his halberd out at the Phoenix Blood Spear!

Peng!

Spear and halberd crossed. A terrifying force swept outwards!

In that instant, the Monster Prince felt strange flames drill into his body like a viper!

These flames looked ordinary, but once they rushed into his body, they caused his mind to fall into illusion.

Hu – !

His anger exploded into an inferno, completely subsuming his rational mind. The Monster Prince’s eyes turned blood red and blood vessels popped out from his entire body as if he would explode at any moment.

This was the might of virtual fire. Moreover, Lin Ming’s virtual fire came from the Heretical God Tree; it was far above ordinary.

“You’re done!”

Lin Ming coolly said. The spear in his hands came smashing down!

Peng!

The heavy shaft of the Phoenix Blood Spear struck the Monster Prince’s body. The Monster Prince’s protective true essence instantly collapsed like an eggshell!

“Stop!”

An old voice suddenly echoed through the arena.

However, Lin Ming ignored this voice. He pulled back his spear and struck the Monster Prince’s chest, causing his ribs to break apart and sending him soaring away.

Peng!

The Monster Prince fell onto the floor like a pile of hashed meat. His body skidded back on the ground for several tens of thousands of feet, causing countless tiles to shatter until he finally fell off the side of the arena stage.

The entire audience was left silent. Lin Ming was far too fierce, He had broken through the Space Laws using Thunder and Fire Laws of the same level. Moreover, he had a strange domain of his own that broke through the 10,000 Monster Domain, and now he had defeated the Monster Prince. As he stood there, his momentum was like a rainbow, unstoppable!

“Young Master!”

Two old monster race men rushed over to the Monster Prince’s side, quickly inspecting his wounds.

The truth was that with the monster race’s royal bloodline, the Monster Prince’s regenerative abilities were no weaker than Lin Ming’s. Even if all of his ribs had shattered it still wouldn’t take too long to recover. If there were superb medicines used, the effects would be even better.

“You!” A monster race World King suddenly stood up, eyeing Lin Ming like a poisonous snake. “Human, I ordered you to stop, are you deaf!?”

The monster race old man was extremely overbearing, even reprimanding Lin Ming right here.

As Lin Ming heard this monster race old man’s words, he was startled. He had seen overbearing before, but never to this extent. Although his natural character was to remain low-profile and he didn’t like to needlessly quarrel with anybody, as he faced this ridiculous monster race old man, he simply angrily smiled and said, “Who the hell are you? Why should I listen to you? I think an old bag of bones like you has gone insane.”

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, the monster race old man’s eyes suddenly flashed with killing intent, “You are courting death!”

As he spoke, he prepared to rush up onto the arena. The people of the monster race, especially the royal family, were all incomparably arrogant and conceited. In their minds, everyone needed to respect them and everyone needed to submit to them. All that refused should be put to death.

However, just as the monster race old man stepped onto the arena stage, he felt a terrifying strength crash into him. This strength was extremely formidable; there was no way for him to resist it. The monster race old man suddenly shook as he was sent soaring backwards, smashing into the arena wall and coughing up a mouthful of blood.

“Who!?”

Although the monster race old man looked miserable, the truth was that he wasn’t seriously injured at all. Coughing up some blood wasn’t anything to the likes of him.

Vast Cosmos slowly walked over, looking at the monster race old man as he would a fool. He coldly said, “Me! Without permission, no one can rush onto the arena stage of the finals. Consider this a light warning.”

Vast Cosmos had a half-step Empyrean cultivation. Compared to an ordinary World King, the disparity was immense!

Chapter 1294 – Seeing Through the Laws

“Vast Cosmos, you actually dare to attack me. Do you really want to take on the burden of being the one to instigate a war between humans and the monster race?”

The two monster race old men only had World King cultivations, but they didn’t fear the heavens or the earth. In fact, there were many kings of the monster race that were like this. They wouldn’t endure insults nor would they fear powerhouses. They were a crazy and wild race. In the past, there were people that abducted children with the royal bloodline in order to refine pills. Finally, the monster race completely exterminated the influence that person came from as well as their entire planet.

Many people knew that the monster race was crazy. Within their bones was buried the nature of a beast. They were like mad dogs; once someone provoked them they would crazily retaliate until their body perished.

However, Vast Cosmos didn’t fear any of this at all. He calmly said, “Both of your lives aren’t as valuable as you think. Be careful with your words or I’ll break all of your bones before I kick you back to the monster race. In my territory, you best be more respectful!”

Many humans couldn’t acclimatize to seeing the monster race, demon race, or the other different races. In history, there were also wars that exploded between humanity and other races. But in order to truly exterminate the enemy, one had to pay an enormous price. It was simply impossible to do.

Thus, in the Divine Realm, there were several races that still coexisted side by side. In the Sky Spill Continent, the giant demons, imps, and goliaths were all offshoot branches of the demon race. As for the fey, they were faintly related to the monster race, but the truth was that they were much closer to the human bloodline. The Sky Spill Continent had simply been isolated for far too long. After their bloodlines multiplied and spread out for tens and hundreds of thousands of years, they began to slowly dilute themselves.

The two monster race Elders’ faces were filled with a cruel light. They looked at Vast Cosmos and then towards Lin Ming, their eyes shining with killing intent.

“We’re going!”

The two monster race Elders brought down the Monster Prince but didn’t leave just because of this. The monster race’s arrogance also didn’t allow them to do something which would weaken their own momentum like that.

They would continue to participate in the matches. Fighting and killing was one of the ways in which they lived.

“Lin Ming, victory!”

Vast Cosmos loudly announced. He looked towards Lin Ming, his eyes filled with appreciation. When Lin Ming had mounted the summit of the Divine Seal Altar, he had been opportunistic, using some shortcuts, thus Vast Cosmos wasn’t panicked at all. But now, Lin Ming, at the middle Divine Sea realm and with a 31 year skeletal age, had defeated the Monster Prince. After reaching this step, he could be called a million year rare genius of the Divine Realm. If it weren’t for the fact that he was born in an era when countless unrivalled geniuses were rising up, then Lin Ming’s light might have overshadowed everyone by far!

“Lin Ming is too strong! Heh, what a good fight, that felt so great! I wonder just how that crazy monster kid will continue fighting.”

“This is incredible. If this continues then Lin Ming might have a chance of reaching the top three!”

“Top three? That would be struggling for the championship against the likes of Xiao Moxian, Hang Chi, and Frost Dream. Just look at the three of them. Which one do you think Lin Ming could possibly replace?”

Xiao Moxian, Frost Dream, and Hang Chi had all pierced through the hearts and minds of those present, giving off an unsurpassable feeling.

“We have no idea how strong Hang Chi is, and although it is said that Xiao Moxian is extremely fierce, we have never seen her strength with our own eyes. But, we can clearly see Lin Ming! That Monster Prince isn’t weak at all but he was still equally destroyed by Lin Ming.”

Lin Ming proved his strength again and again. He didn’t rely on rumors and gossip, nor did he rely on some influence behind him that raised him up. Rather, he had convinced people through his sheer victories in combat, convincing them without leaving a single doubt behind.

Moreover, Lin Ming came from a minor influence, which earned him an extremely favorable impression from many young elites of World King influences and ordinary Hold Lands. Originally, the Empyrean descendants were a great mountain that pressed down on the disciples of the World King and Holy Land influences. Whether it was in talent, resources, or inheritances, all of them couldn’t help but develop thoughts of inferiority, making them feel as if it were impossible to fight against them. But now, Lin Ming had used his strength to tell everyone in the arena that even someone from a small influence could equally become an extreme genius.

This was truly inspiring!

Of course, while some people worshipped Lin Ming, there were also many people that envied him. No matter what happened, Lin Ming stood on the greatest stage of the entire Divine Realm. Throughout every great influence of the Divine Realm, there was no one who didn’t know of him.

Lin Ming walked down from the stage and began to meditate. The Monster Prince wasn’t weak at all. Although Lin Ming had still kept back some moves, victory hadn’t come easily.

“Lin Ming, take a good rest. In the first round you will take a victory, but in the next round you will be the first one on stage after two battles. Frost Dream, Xiao Moxian, and Hang Chi have all taken a bye for this round. After the first round finishes there will be a one hour rest. Do you have any problems with that?”

Vast Cosmos’s true essence sound transmission echoed in Lin Ming’s ears.

Lin Ming and the Monster Prince’s match just now had been temporarily inserted into the schedule. Because Lin Ming hadn’t yet fought in the first round, this caused there to be a change in the match order. Because the Monster Prince fought in two matches, this caused there to be an odd number of remaining contestants so it was not possible to finish the games. Thus, Vast Universe Heavenly Palace had simply allowed Frost Dream, Xiao Moxian, and Hang Chi to all draw byes.

Of course, this method was to ensure fairness. Three of them had undeniable strength and whoever bumped into them would likely suffer a loss. Even though Vast Cosmos believed that Lin Ming had the capabilities of fighting against them, he would still have to use every card in his hands, which would cause him to suffer a disadvantage in the later fights. In this situation, allowing the three of them a bye was the best method.

“I have no problems. May I ask who my next match is?” Lin Ming asked Vast Cosmos. Lin Ming’s restorative ability far surpassed what Vast Cosmos imagined. He simply hadn’t used a significant amount of energy in fighting against the Monster Prince.

“Your opponent is… Dragon Fang!”

Vat Cosmos said, stretching out his words. As Lin Ming heard the name of his next opponent he felt his heart quicken.

Dragon Fang!

He would finally battle Dragon Fang. He and Dragon Fang could be considered fated to meet. Both of them had grown together in the preliminaries, and because Dragon Fang had opened the Three Lives Pupils there, the range of his growth had been even greater than Lin Ming’s.

Whether it was in the preliminaries or the semifinals, the two of them hadn’t fought for a variety of reasons. But now, the time for their battle had finally approached.

This would likely be an extremely tough battle! It was also because of this reason that Vast Cosmos had advised Lin Ming to rest well.

“I understand.”

Lin Ming cupped his fists together, feeling a bit impatient.

The third battle of the first round was between Dragon Fang and Shiku.

There was an extremely small number of people that believed in Shiku, even though Shiku was also an impressive person.

“Shiku… a dual body and energy cultivator to fight against Dragon Fang’s Three Lives Pupils. This is going to be interesting. This brat Shiku has come across some fortuitous encounters, otherwise it would be impossible for him to cultivate dual body and energy to this level.”

Vast Cosmos thought with a smile. Lin Ming was also paying attention to Shiku.

As Dragon Fang and Shiku stepped on stage, a wave of cheers washed over the entire arena. Most of them were shouting Dragon Fang’s name and only a small number of people were cheering for Shiku.

Dragon Fang was handsome and delicate with extremely pale skin. As for Shiku, he was tall and burly-looking, like a roughly hewn stone. Because of this, Dragon Fang won the hearts of most young female disciples, not to mention that the strength he had revealed so far had surpassed Shiku.

“These fellows really think I’m worthless or something. I don’t believe I can’t defeat this pale little dandy boy!”

Shiku thought to himself. He wouldn’t underestimate Dragon Fang. Dragon Fang’s strength was truly amazing, but he was also confident in himself.

“Hah!”

Shiku shouted out loud and his aura erupted to endless levels. In that instant, he was like a mountain that stood atop the arena stage! He cultivated the Earth Laws, and his Earth Laws had reached large success of the fifth level Concept.

“Sky Mountain Seal!”

Shiku grasped a staff and took the initiative to attack. This strike utilized the Earth Laws he comprehended to the max. As this attack came out, it was like a falling mountain, able to sunder the world!

Dragon Fang held the Dragon Fang Blade in his hands, an indifferent expression across his face. His pupils had already turned into the shape of needle tips – this was the Three Lives Pupils.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Endless earth origin energy gathered together, forming a mass of brown light in the sky that became a 100,000 foot mountain that began to fall down at Dragon Fang!

As the audience saw this they cried out in alarm. The weight of a 100,000 foot tall mountain was nearly inestimable. With the infusion of endless amounts of earth energy crashing down together, the earth would collapse! How could a martial artist possibly defend against this?

This attack was unmatched!

Everyone looked towards Dragon Fang. Dragon Fang still looked as calm as before. Within his eyes, he could clearly make out the circulation of Shiku’s Earth Laws.

In that instant, Dragon Fang attacked. Without using any Laws at all, he simply poured true essence into his blade and then lightly thrust towards that 100,000 foot tall mountain.

“What!?”

“He wants to use that four foot long sword to resist Shiku’s 100,000 foot tall mountain!?”

“He’s too crazy! Shiku’s Earth Laws have long reached the boundary of substantializing his origin energy. This mountain is not a phantom but a true mountain of origin energy. If this attack connects, then Dragon Fang’s arms will be torn off!”

As everyone was speaking, Dragon Fang thrust his sword into an exact point of that mountain. In that moment, everything seemed to fall silent as if time itself had stopped.

Dragon Fang’s energy completely poured into that giant mountain. It was much weaker and smaller than the energy Shiku had erupted with, but at this time an incredible scene occurred.

From the point where Dragon Fang had stabbed his sword, a crack appeared in the giant mountain. Then, countless cracks began to climb all around the massive mountain like a never-ending spider web.

Rumble rumble rumble!

With the sound of collapsing mountains and rivers, the entire origin energy mountain turned into endless crushed stone as it completely disintegrated!

“What!?”

“How did he do that?”

“A single sword strike to crush a 100,000 foot mountain!”

The entire audience was shocked, and even Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. If Dragon Fang had suppressed Shiku using absolute strength then he would have thought that was reasonable. But, a single casual sword strike had completely shattered Shiku’s attack.

“Those eyes…” Lin Ming noticed Dragon Fang’s pupils, “Those eyes can see through the Laws. In front of Dragon Fang’s eyes, there is no place for Shiku’s Laws to hide!”

Lin Ming didn’t know where Dragon Fang’s eyes originated from, but he could guess some of their abilities. Many of the powerhouses in the audience were also able to do the same.

“This Dragon Fang is able to see through the Laws, thus he instantly found a weakness in Shiku’s attack and was able to crush that origin energy mountain that he had formed. If all Laws are seen through by Dragon Fang, how could you still fight? That is a nearly invincible position!”

“I also heard that this Dragon Fang has practiced the Laws of Space and Time to an extremely high level. He can see through the Laws of his opponents and then attack with his own Space and Time Laws. What a terrifying young man!”

“I thought that Lin Ming could reach the top three or even the top four, but now I’ve changed my mind. These dark horses are each darker than the last! I have no idea just who is stronger and weaker between Lin Ming and Dragon Fang.”

Chapter 1295 – Impossible to Unravel

Dragon Fang’s two pupils were chilling to the bone. All moves and all Laws were seen through by him, making one unable to summon any courage to face him.

As Shiku saw his finishing blow, the Sky Mountain Seal, be defeated like that, his complexion turned extremely ugly.

“You are fierce, but my strength is more than just the Earth Laws. By depending on those eyes alone, you cannot defeat me.”

Shiku shouted out loud and popping sounds emitted from his entire body. He directly opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and a giant turtle phantom appeared behind him.

This turtle had a massive snaking dragon head and its shell was round like a dome. Its four legs were like those of an elephant and its body was larger than a mountain.

“That’s a Dragon Turtle phantom!”

Of the nine sons of the Heavenly Dragon, the Dragon Turtle was one.

“Shiku has opened seven of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, the same as me. Moreover, he can summon the phantom of a Dragon Turtle. I fear he obtained a lucky chance related to the Dragon Turtle.” Lin Ming thought.

Shiku suddenly laughed, “Ten years ago I explored a divergent mystic realm. Deep within that mystic realm, I found a deeply slumbering Dragon Turtle egg. Using a special technique, I slowly ate up that Dragon Turtle egg. Ignoring the Laws I’ve comprehended, just my bodily strength has reached the highest pinnacle!”

As Shiku spoke, the entire audience was shocked. Shiku’s luck was too good!

A Dragon Turtle egg was more valuable and precious than the supreme dragon bone that Lin Ming had obtained. Although the bloodline of the Dragon Turtle was inferior to the Azure Dragon, Shiku had still obtained a Dragon Turtle egg that was filled with the life vitality of a dragon. Compared to the bone of an Azure Dragon that had been dead for countless years, it was far more precious!

If a Dragon Turtle egg were to appear, even Great World King powerhouses would crazily fight for it.

“So that’s how it is… no wonder Shiku was able to open the first seven of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates.” Lin Ming silently thought. Underneath the current rules of the Heavenly Dao, it was impossible to open up the Eight Inner Hidden Gates to such a degree without a lucky chance.

In truth, the advantages the Dragon Turtle egg gave to Shiku were far more than helping him open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. The Dragon Turtle was originally an earth-attribute God Beast, and thus it complemented Shiku’s Laws, allowing him to instantly leap into the ranks of the top masters.

Shiku originally thought that he could rank in the top three of the First Martial Meeting, but now he realized that experts here were like clouds in the sky. Any one of these people he had to face would force him to use his complete strength.

As Shiku spoke, he glanced over at Lin Ming, a faintly superior feeling in his eyes.

Lin Ming was startled, but immediately understood his meaning.

When Lin Ming fought he had summoned the phantom of an Azure Dragon, and that scene had naturally fallen into Shiku’s eyes. Shiku had swallowed the Dragon Turtle egg and this allowed him to faintly feel the intensity of the Azure Dragon bloodline within Lin Ming. He guessed that Lin Ming had obtained something like a dragon bone or dragon blood, and in terms of lucky chances, the Dragon Turtle egg he found naturally surpassed Lin Ming.

All body transformation martial artists needed lucky chances to open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. Thus, Shiku naturally compared himself with Lin Ming’s lucky chances. Since Lin Ming was inferior in this regard, Shiku naturally felt superior by having a greater destiny on him.

Even though his strength couldn’t be compared to Lin Ming’s, his lucky chance was still better than his, thus the reason he glanced at Lin Ming with that expression just now.

“So it’s like that. But… so what?” Dragon Fang calmly asked Shiku.

Shiku frowned as he saw Dragon Fang’s response, “Humph, stop posturing!”

Dragon Fang quietly wiped the edge of the Dragon Fang Blade, coolly saying, “Lucky chances and destiny are indeed a component of one’s talent, but they do not account for everything. If you believe that just because you stumbled across a great lucky chance, that will allow you to become an extreme master of the Divine Realm, then you are sorely mistaken.”

In Dragon Fang’s opinion, those like Lin Ming and Jun Bluemoon that had come from common mortal backgrounds must have come across heaven-shaking lucky chances to stand where they were now. But, they did not reach this boundary through just the quality and quantity of lucky chances they found. With so many lives in the Divine Realm, there were countless individuals that found lucky chances, but out of all those people, only a few geniuses were able to stand here.

At present, Shiku was one such person who had come across a great lucky chance. But, when compared to Lin Ming and Jun Bluemoon, he lacked many things.

“You sure speak a lot of crap. Make your move. With my body transformation technique, I simply have no need to rely on my Laws. I want to know just how you’ll see through my weaknesses!”

Shiku’s body suddenly bulged out, making him look like an ancient beast as he hurtled towards Dragon Fang!

At that instant, Dragon Fang’s mind was like a lake without ripples. He gently traced the hilt of the Dragon Fang Blade and quietly said, “If you won’t use the Laws, then I will.”

Just as Shiku’s staff was about to strike Dragon Fang’s body, time suddenly slowed down! The power of time around Shiku was twisted by Dragon Fang!

Shiku rapidly responded. Popping sounds burst out from his body as tens of millions of jins of strength erupted. He wanted to use brute force to break free from the shackles of the Time Laws!

Ka ka ka!

Shiku’s muscles rose and his blood vessels stuck out as he broke through the power of time. However, at that moment, he felt himself plunging into a vortex of time. There was no past, no future, and even the present had come to a near halt. Dragon Fang’s attainments in the Time Laws had far surpassed Shiku’s imagination.

If it were a normal martial artist with weaker Time Laws, then Shiku would have easily broken through it with his strength. However, Dragon Fang was far too strong. Whether it was the intensity of true essence or Laws, he was on a higher level than Shiku. It was impossible for Shiku to contend with him.

Woosh!

Dragon Fang’s figure flashed as he struck at Shiku. The Dragon Fang Blade ripped apart Shiku’s protective true essence, leaving behind a thin line of blood on his neck.

Shiku stiffened, his entire body going ice cold. In that instant, he felt as if he had died. When Dragon Fang’s sword cut towards him, it was like the coming of the death god!

And what scared Shiku the most was that even if his speed was inferior to Dragon Fang’s, he still had his protective true essence and his body transformation technique to protect his body. But in front of Dragon Fang, all of that had been as fragile as paper. Dragon Fang’s sword silently tore through Shiku’s protective true essence along with the surface defense of his body. If that sword had cut forwards three more inches then Shiku’s head would have been cut off!

“How… how is this possible…” Shiku’s eyes widened, his entire body dripping with a cold sweat. “How can my defense not resist you at all.”

Silence fell over the entire audience. Dragon Fang’s attack was far too sharp. Even though they were so far away, they still felt a cold chill crawl up their backs!

This was Dragon Fang’s true strength?

“What a dangerous attack!” Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. Dragon Fang’s attack was far too sharp. Even with Lin Ming’s defensive capabilities, he didn’t believe he had the confidence to withstand such an attack. In other words, if he were to fight Dragon Fang, he couldn’t allow himself to be cut or he would receive a severe wound!

Dragon Fang put away his sword. He lightly glanced at Shiku and coldly said, “What cut apart your defense was not my blade, but space.”

From the start, Dragon Fang’s sword had never touched Shiku’s skin. Rather, he used the power of space to cut apart Shiku’s defense.

After reaching Dragon Fang’s boundary, by utilizing the Space Laws he didn’t need to use his sword to kill others. With the power of space he could kill people from a hundred steps away. Space was invisible and formless; wanting to dodge it was extremely difficult!

A martial artist skilled in the Space Laws was terrifying, but a swordsman skilled in the Space Laws was even more terrifying. This was because space was sharper than a sword edge!

“Is this Dragon Fang… human?”

‘Shiku is absolutely not weak, but compared to Dragon Fang, the disparity is too great!”

Nobody believed that Shiku was weak. He himself was an Empyrean descendant, and although he came from one of the weaker Empyrean palaces, he had a heaven-defying talent and even swallowed a Dragon Turtle egg. Just how many people in the universe would ever have such a lucky chance? And this Shiku was actually defeated in such a miserable manner by Dragon Fang!

“He’s too much of a freak! With that strength, he might even be stronger than Lin Ming!”

When Lin Ming fought the Monster Prince they had fought for some time. Although Shiku was likely weaker than the Monster Prince, he had been thoroughly defeated without the tiniest ability to resist.

“Dragon Fang might have the strength to compete for the top three rankings… I have nothing to say. Even I can’t say who will be in the top three now.”

At the beginning. Everyone thought that Xiao Moxian, Hang Chi, and Frost Dream were guaranteed to be in the top three rankings. But now, Lin Ming and Dragon Fang each gave more and more formidable performances, as if they were invincible. Like this, with so many variables, it was impossible to unravel what the final rankings of the tournament would be.

“Don’t forget that there is also Jun Bluemoon. Just look at him. From the start until now he’s simply been holding that bunny. Even though there were so many intense fights and those freaks Lin Ming and Dragon Fang both stepped on stage, his expression didn’t change at all. Do you suppose he is weak?”

Jun Bluemoon had defeated an Empyrean descendant within three moves, and that Empyrean descendant hadn’t been a nobody either. After being defeated by Jun Bluemoon, that Empyrean descendant had emerged victorious in his next 17 matches, and his results in the second tier were also at the top. There was even a chance that he and Ram Saber would fight to determine who had the qualifications to challenge the first tier. With that, it was unlikely that Hua Xuan would be able to maintain his position.

Such a ruthless person had been pitifully defeated by Jun Bluemoon. From the beginning until now, Jun Bluemoon had maintained a faint and uncaring expression, as if nothing mattered to him at all. Even the provocations of the Monster Prince and his opponents hadn’t affected him in the least. And, what was most strange was that he had always held onto a little bunny, slowly stroking that little bunny’s fur. This was something that normally only little girls would do. Wasn’t this Jun Bluemoon a bit too much like a young girl?

Or was there something special about this bunny?

“This First Martial Meeting has already reached unprecedented levels of intensity.”

“I can’t wait! I really want to see them fight!”

As everyone spoke, Vast Cosmos stepped onto the arena stage once more. He loudly announced, “Fourth match, Jun Bluemoon against White King!”

These words caused the entire audience to bubble over with excitement!

This was another battle of heavyweights. There was no need to mention the accomplishments of White King. He was the most outstanding disciples to appear in Vast Universe Heavenly Palace for the last several hundred thousands of years. One of the great reasons that Empyrean Vast Universe stepped forward to help manage the First Martial Meeting was because of White King.

As the one representing the glory of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, White King’s strength was naturally amazing.

Moreover, the gambling house hadn’t listed the odds for White King. This caused many others to look forwards to seeing just how strong White King was.

“White King, will you be okay?”

Before White King stepped on stage, several of his senior-apprentice brothers spoke to him. Although they were confident in White King, this Jun Bluemoon was far too abnormal. Wanting to defeat him wouldn’t be easy.

“I’m fine.” White King took a deep breath.

“Mm, it’s fine as long as you try your best. This Jun Bluemoon is not easy to deal with. Just the strength he’s exposed so far is no trifling matter.”

“I understand.”

White King slowly picked up his hand strap and shouldered his sword as he stepped onto the arena stage.

In this battle, the pressure on him was not small at all!

Chapter 1297 – In a Spark of Time

Dragon Fang stood on the arena stage, his black clothes fluttering around him. His hands were wrapped in white bandages and as he stood there with the Dragon Fang Blade in his hand. His complexion was still pale and delicate like before, and his eyes seemed as bright as the stars.

Lin Ming stood across from him, dressed in blue. He grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear, his body straight like a spear.

“You’ve caught my attention for a long time.” Dragon Fang suddenly said.

Lin Ming smiled, “Same here.”

“I’ve always wanted to fight with you, but on the Divine Seal Altar we both weren’t in our peak conditions and in order to climb up the 33rd step, we both had to save our strength. The result is that I’ve waited until now. I’ve been looking forwards to this battle for a long time and I will put my best into this battle.”

“As will I.”

Their conversation revealed just how much Lin Ming and Dragon Fang valued each other.

“Lin Ming!”

“Lin Ming!”

“Dragon Fang!”

“Dragon Fang!”

Before the match had begun, the audience was already cheering at the top of their lungs. Those that shouted these two names were all young elites of different great influences. They were certainly crazy because of this fight. A battle of this level might not happen for even 10,000 years! To them, it was a lucky chance if they were able to observe and emulate these young heroes. They could study their techniques, their abilities, and broaden their horizons.

“It’s so lively!” In the contestant area, a bright voice like silver bells echoed out. Everyone turned to see a black-clothed girl emerge out of thin air like a ghost. No one had seen where she had come from, as if she had always been there from the start.

“Xiao Moxian!”

Many people instantly recognized this young girl. She was the direct bloodline descendant of Empyrean Demondawn as well as someone who possessed half the inherited bloodline of a phoenix. In terms of potential, she could be called number one within the entire Divine Realm!

And beside Xiao Moxian was another young woman dressed in white and clad in a dreamy illusion, her entire body exuding a holy aura. Without needing to mention it, everyone knew she was Frost Dream.

Frost Dream’s face was blurred, as if a layer of fog perpetually shrouded her.

And not too far away from these two women there was a tall and thin bald youth. He wore straw sandals and loosely hanging cloth robes. There were nine Buddhist scars that marked his head; this youth was Hang Chi.

Frost Dream, Hang Chi, Xiao Moxian – the three great masters had all come out to watch Lin Ming and Dragon Fang’s battle. From this point alone, one could see just how extraordinary this battle would be!

“Junior-apprentice Sister Xiao Moxian!” As White King saw these three people, he walked forwards to greet them. They were all old acquaintances.

“Senior-apprentice Brother White King, you lost a bit too miserably.”

Xiao Moxian loved to poke at one’s wounds. White King awkwardly traced his nose, saying, “If my skill is inferior to others’ then I have lost fair and square. Junior-apprentice Sister Xiao Moxian, do you have the confidence to face Lin Ming, Dragon Fang, and Jun Bluemoon?”

“Hehehe…” Xiao Moxian clucked her tongue, playfully saying, “Guess!”

“Eh…” White King’s voice stalled in his throat before helplessly shaking his head. Although he had known Xiao Moxian for some time now, he didn’t know just how far she had grown. In his opinion, although Lin Ming, Dragon Fang, and Jun Bluemoon were all formidable existences, it wouldn’t be easy for them to defeat Xiao Moxian at all. The growth of Xiao Moxian’s strength was astronomical. She was someone who would grow stronger just by eating and sleeping, and even her Laws would rise to a higher level without her doing anything at all. Just who could compare to the likes of her?

It was a pity that Xiao Moxian never seemed to grow up and always had a playful mentality. Otherwise, if she was diligent in training like Hang Chi was, then she would be much stronger than she was now!

On the arena stage, Vast Cosmos slowly announced, “Match, begin!”

In that instant, Dragon Fang moved.

His speed was extremely high. To cross the distance between him and Lin Ming, he only needed a tenth of the blink of an eye.

Woosh!

As Dragon Fang flew forwards, his figure divided into four!

Spatial mirror images!

Four Dragon Fangs each cut down with the Dragon Fang Blade. For a time, every location for Lin Ming to dodge to had been sealed off!

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. He knew that back on the Divine Seal Altar, Dragon Fang already had the ability to transform into eight spatial mirror images. But now he had only formed four; it was clear that he was just testing the waters with an exploratory attack. But this tentative attack was also incomparably swift and violent. Compared to several months ago when Dragon Fang had summoned eight spatial mirror images to defeat Bloodless Sword, the difference was like the heavens and the earth!

Those four crimson lights shot forwards at incredible speeds, all of them piercing through Lin Ming’s body at once.

Ca!

As the sword lights penetrated through Lin Ming’s body, they thrust into the ground behind him, causing the ground to shatter. The audience cried out in alarm. They didn’t believe that the match would end like this. However, this sense of shock was too strong. Although they had correctly guessed it was an afterimage, Lin Ming’s speed was too fast. No one could tell whether it was an afterimage or not!

“Your speed has indeed not disappointed me.” Dragon Fang said with a dignified tone. Rather, to be more accurate, it was four Dragon Fangs speaking up at once. Their expressions were completely identical and they spoke with one voice.

As Dragon Fang continued speaking, Lin Ming’s afterimages began to slowly fade away.

Several hundred million people watched the four Dragon Fangs on stage. The young martial artists simply weren’t able to tell which ones were fake and which one was real. This was because the four Dragon Fangs were spatial mirror images and not illusions. Like a person reflected in the mirror, their movements and expressions were all the same.

The eyes of the four Dragon Fangs began to transform at the same time. Their pupils condensed, condensed, and condensed more until they were the size of needle tips. Their eyes were covered with mysterious patterns and even the blood vessels in the sclera began to bulge.

He had opened the Three Lives Pupils.

As Lin Ming saw these eyes, his expression was also solemn. In this condition, Dragon Fang was at his most terrifying state.

“My cultivation is known as the Three Lives Pupils!” Dragon Fang suddenly said, “This is the strongest secret ability that my Honorably Master taught me. With the Three Lives Pupils activated, I can display my Space and Time Laws to their greatest degree of strength. Now, I will make my attack!”

Before Dragon Fang made his move he had actually warned Lin Ming. This was the epitome of his confidence!

Of course, this was also to ensure the fairest battle. Only by utilizing their abilities to the limit could they engage in the greatest of showdowns!

The entire audience’s eyes popped wide open, unblinking, lest they miss any movement at all. Dragon Fang’s techniques involved the Space and Time Laws, and Dragon Fang was also a freak who had cultivated both the Space and Time Laws to the fifth level Concept. If these two Laws joined together, it was unknown how strong they would be!

Many people were sweating nervously for Lin Ming, because what Lin Ming had exposed so far was only the fifth level Concept of the Fire Laws.

At this time, Dragon Fang began to slowly move forwards. His steps were strange, both slow and fast, without a determined direction as if he were walking through a space maze. The four Dragon Fangs began to slowly separate as they moved forwards, each one dividing into two, four of them dividing into eight!

Dragon Fang had created eight spatial mirror images.

The might of eight spatial mirror images was over two times stronger than four spatial mirror images!

Ca!

At this time, a dark gray light shimmered above the blood red edges of the eight Dragon Fang Swords – this was the substantialized power of space!

Hum hum hum –

Space trembled as Dragon Fang attacked!

With eight swords, each one transformed into thousands and tens of thousands of sword lights!

For a time, shadows of the Dragon Fang Swords filled the air. These sword shadows were not illusions but spatial mirror images!

To use space to project sword lights, this was an omnipresent attack.

The several hundreds of millions of people in the arena gasped as they saw this. This was tens of thousands of sword lights, blocking off every possible route to dodge. Moreover, each sword light had a faint touch of the Time Laws. It was simply impossible to judge their trajectory. No matter how quick one was, they could not be avoided!

As for defending against them, that was an even greater joke. If these sword lights fused as one, even a mountain made of divine stone would be turned to ash!

How could one block this!?

At this critical moment, in Ming suddenly erupted with the Heretical God Force, releasing it to the limit, even as he opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and burnt the Blood of the Ancient Phoenix. Facing Dragon Fang as his opponent, he had to go all-out!

“In full bloom, Prime Emperor Lotus Flower!”

With a resonant dragon roar, the phantom of an Azure Dragon appeared. Behind Lin Ming, a deep blood red Prime Emperor Lotus Flower slowly blossomed. Grandmist space exploded outwards, crashing into those endless sword lights!

Chi chi chi chi chi chi!

As the sword lights pierced into the grandmist space, they violently collided with the elementary grandmist energy!

The elementary grandmist energy that was as heavy as a mountain was twisted apart by the sword lights. But at the same time, the sword lights were also destroyed, vanishing into nothing.

Grandmist space was a complete offensive, defensive, and suppressive ability. Even though Lin Ming had only obtained a third of the inheritance, it still possessed an incomparably terrifying might!

Peng!

An explosive force surged outwards. Out of Dragon Fang’s tens of thousands of sword lights, over 99% of them collapsed as they entered the grandmist space!

As the remaining sword lights rushed around Lin Ming, Lin Ming simply swept out his spear. Like the tail whip of a divine dragon, the spear point drew an arc in space, and with a series of explosive sounds, all of those sword lights were crushed to nothing by Lin Ming!

All returned to nihility!

The countless young geniuses watching this were dumbstruck.

“Heavens! He can actually defend against that!”

Under everyone’s gaze, that nearly unstoppable sure-kill move was actually broken through by Lin Ming! The all-annihilating grandmist space was indeed one of Lin Ming’s strongest techniques. Once he used it, it was hard for anyone of his level to match it.

In that instant, Lin Ming suddenly stepped forwards. The grandmist space spread forwards, completely covering Dragon Fang!

And Dragon Fang had just attacked so his old strength was used and he hadn’t caught himself yet. His front was wide open!

Lin Ming certainly wouldn’t miss out on such an opportunity. His speed rose to the extreme as he hurtled forwards, his spear thrusting outwards!

Hu – !

As the grandmist space enveloped Dragon Fang, Dragon Fang’s strength began rapidly fading from his body. True essence was decomposed by the grandmist space, and even those spatial mirror images began to blur.

Lin Ming only needed a thousandth of the blink of an eye to determine which was Dragon Fang’s true body!

“Chasing Thunder!”

A thrust of the spear, a flash of electric light!

Lin Ming didn’t use a move with a stronger striking power like Virtual Disintegration or Blue Lotus Flame Dance, but the fastest attack in his arsenal, Chasing Thunder. Every fleeting moment of battle was different from one to the next. What he needed now was speed!

The speed was so fast that it surpassed the ability of everyone to react. Dragon Fang’s eyes flashed with a sharp light as they immediately turned cold.

“Fantastic, but what a pity…”

In that moment, the eight Dragon Fangs combined together. His sword suddenly reversed as he slashed back at an unbelievable angle…

Chapter 1298 – The Greatest Battle

Dragon Fang’s attack path was extremely strange. He didn’t attack Lin Ming nor did he attack Lin Ming’s sword light; what he attacked was the void!

As his sword thrust out, a sharp light flashed in Dragon Fang’s pupils!

In that instant, every circulating flow of energy within the grandmist space was reflected in Dragon Fang’s Three Lives Pupils.

Power of space!

The power of space attached to the Dragon Fang Blade suddenly erupted. With a loud cracking sound, several strands of elementary grandmist energy were cut apart by Dragon Fang. In that instant, the pressure on Dragon Fang rapidly fell. With a quick movement of his feet, his figure flashed at unimaginable speeds!

Peng!

Dragon Fang broke through the grandmist space and flew away. At the same time, Lin Ming’s spear struck empty space as it crashed into the ground.

The surface stone of the arena stage was shorn off; crushed rubble flew into the skies!

“Mm? He broke through my grandmist space!”

Lin Ming looked at Dragon Fang with surprise in his eyes. In truth, Lin Ming’s grandmist space was not unbreakable. The closer the grandmist space was to Lin Ming, the more intense it was. The further away the grandmist space was, the weaker it was. It wasn’t strange that Dragon Fang could break free from the shackles of Lin Ming’s grandmist space with absolute strength.

But, what Dragon Fang used just now to break through the grandmist space was not absolute strength. Rather, he used the Three Lives Pupils to see through the circulation of the energy within the grandmist space and then cut it apart. That was truly an incredible feat.

“My grandmist space… I’m not fully proficient in it yet. Or, I should say that I haven’t completely learned it at all!”

Lin Ming thought to himself. He didn’t believe that the grandmist space was inferior to the Three Lives Pupils. Even Empyrean Primordius himself was someone who was in no way inferior to a ruthless master like Empyrean Divine Dream. There was no questioning his strength. The transcendent divine might that he created would undoubtedly be terrifyingly powerful.

But, the problem was that Lin Ming wasn’t considered a full descendant of Empyrean Primordius. When he had entered the Eternal Demon Abyss and ventured into the Road of Emperor, it was unknown whether Empyrean Primordius was still alive and all that was left over was some inheritances and ancient relics.

At that time, Lin Ming didn’t possess the ability to pass Empyrean Primordius’s tests. His cultivation was too low and his talent was lacking; it was natural for him to fail.

Thus, Lin Ming had only scratched the surface of the Primordius martial intent.

On the other hand, Dragon Fang was the sole disciple that Three Lives Old Man had accepted in 300 million years. With Three Lives Old Man personally teaching him, there was nothing that wasn’t explained. Every cultivation ability was revealed in absolute clarity and all sorts of precious resources that Three Lives Old Man had gathered in his life were freely spent on Dragon Fang.

There was simply no comparing them!

Because of this, it wasn’t strange for the Three Lives Pupils to see through the grandmist space!

“I can easily pass through your domain. The Three Lives Pupils is the king of 10,000 Laws. Underneath the gaze of my eyes, there are no Laws that can hide!”

Dragon Fang confidently said, his blood red sword firmly grasped in his hand.

As Lin Ming heard Dragon Fang’s words, he faintly smiled. “Is that so? Unfortunately, I am also confident in my Laws. Why don’t we give it a try!”

Lin Ming’s astonishing words left the entire audience stunned for a moment.

Dragon Fang had just said that the Three Lives Pupils was the king of 10,000 Laws. Although many people found this hard to accept, they didn’t have the means to question it. After all, the facts were placed in front of them. Whoever fought with Dragon Fang would lose all confidence. If your techniques were broken through, how could you possibly continue fighting?

And this Lin Ming actually said he was confident in his Laws?

It was well known by all that Lin Ming’s weakness lay in the Laws.

Lin Ming had reached large success in the fifth level Fire Laws, and his Thunder Laws were slightly worse. Compared to Dragon Fang and Jun Bluemoon, who were exceptionally skilled in the Space and Time Laws and the Yin Yang Laws, he was a bit lacking. In truth, it wasn’t that Lin Ming was weak, but that everyone else was too freakish!

It was truly difficult to judge Lin Ming and Dragon Fang’s strength. But after thinking about it carefully, Lin Ming was a versatile genius skilled in all aspects. Whether it was endurance, defense, Laws, striking power, mortal body, soul, will domains, everything he possessed was approaching the highest levels.

But that was only approaching the highest levels, not the true peak. This made everyone feel that Lin Ming didn’t have a true ‘strength’. Although he was skilled in various aspects, he wasn’t invincible with them.

And Dragon Fang possessed the Three Lives Pupils. In the aspect of Laws, he was invincible.

No one would want to use their Laws to fight with Dragon Fang, otherwise they would be seen through! But if a martial artist didn’t use their Laws, how could they fight?

Moreover, Dragon Fang had mind-boggling accomplishments in the Space and Time Laws. If you were to fight with Dragon Fang, and he were to use the Laws while you couldn’t, wasn’t that just standing there waiting to be beaten up?

Now, Lin Ming’s strongest grandmist space was also seen through by Dragon Fang. Many people were fearfully sweating for Lin Ming, feeling that he was in a very bad spot.

“Is that right? Then let me experience your Laws.”

Dragon Fang gripped his sword and split into eight forms. The seven spatial images seemed to emerge from Dragon Fang’s body. After his Space Laws had reached this boundary, he was already able to freely use the spatial mirror images with skill and ease.

Lin Ming spun the Phoenix Blood Spear. True essence converged into his inner world as the Heretical God Tree crazily grew.

Behind Lin Ming, the phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared!

This 100,000 foot tall divine tree pierced into the heavens!

The audience didn’t know what sort of transcendent divine might the Heretical God Force was, but they still had an extremely deep impression of it. When Lin Ming had summoned this Heretical God Tree, he had used the Thunder and Fire Laws to break through the Monster Prince’s space cage.

At the same level, the Fire Laws had broken through the Space Laws. What sort of concept was that? It was no minor matter at all! And now, Lin Ming was using this Heretical God Tree to deal with Dragon Fang.

“Virtual Disintegration!”

Lin Ming thrust his spear out, summoning virtual fire to coat the Phoenix Blood Spear. Purple and red beating flames danced on the spear as it thrust towards Dragon Fang.

These were flames that faintly surpassed the Heavenly Dao; they were beyond ordinary. Facing these monstrous flames, Dragon Fang’s expression didn’t change. His needle-like pupils swept over Lin Ming, seeing through all!

“What!?” Dragon Fang was startled. He discovered that the path of this virtual fire was only faintly recognizable, and it was extremely difficult to see. Even with the Three Lives Pupils, he could feel the heat of the flames burning into him, causing a needle-like pain to stab into his mind!

“Flames of virtual fire? Lin Ming’s Fire Laws are truly different from an ordinary martial artist’s, even his Laws are at a higher degree. Even my Three Lives Pupils were nearly unable to see through them. However…”

Three Lives Pupils – All Existence to Void!

Dragon Fang had opened All Existence to Void! On the Divine Seal Altar, Dragon Fang had done this once before. All Existence to Void was a single state of the Three Lives Pupils transcendent divine might. The Three Lives Pupils had many different states and they could even be opened in tandem. When one cultivated the Three Lives Pupils to the limit and all states were opened together, even the Heavenly Dao Laws would fall silent.

Although Dragon Fang was far from reaching this boundary, just the state of All Existence to Void was able to increase his ability to see through the Laws several times over!

“I can see it!”

Within Dragon Fang’s field of vision, the energy circulation path of the virtual fire was clearly seen through by him!

“Break apart!”

The eight Dragon Fangs simultaneously slashed their swords. The eight Dragon Fang Blades erupted with a tremendous power of space as all of this energy rushed towards Lin Ming as if it had a mind of its own!

The power of space was the sharpest weapon. It was omnipresent, able to cut apart all!

And underneath Dragon Fang’s control, this power of space completely stabbed into the weakest points of the virtual fire!

After these monstrous purple flames were pierced through by this power of space, they suddenly shivered before exploding with a loud bang!

Purple flames dimmed as endless purple lights shot out. Lin Ming’s Virtual Disintegration was also broken through!

Hu – !

Dragon Fang let out a long and deep breath, a stabbing pain throbbing in his eyes. Even some meridian channels in the corners of his eyes had ruptured and were leaking deep red blood. Even though Dragon Fang was at the late Divine Sea realm, he was still barely able to use All Existence to Void. Not only did it consume a great deal of true essence and world power, it also created a tremendous burden on his eyes. As long as he activated it, the pressure on his eyes would be unbelievable. The blood vessels in his eyes would blow up over time and even cause him to gradually lose his eyesight.

Thus, Dragon Fang was only able to maintain this state for a very short time.

Dragon Fang grasped the long sword in his hands. At this time, his eyes were burning with flames, like two suns were contained within them. And all around his eyes, meridian channels bulged upwards, seeming just like sunlight.

The current Dragon Fang exuded a savage aura.

As he looked at Lin Ming, he grimly said, “Lin Ming, your virtual fire is truly amazing. I now understand that it is a transcendent divine might, otherwise you could never have reached such heights!”

The Heretical God Force was a transcendent divine might and was more complete than the Primordius martial intent.

But, Lin Ming didn’t expect it to be complete. Those transcendent divine mights that were dug up in ancient ruins were often incomplete. It was only that Lin Ming hadn’t cultivated it to a high enough boundary so he was unable to determine whether or not it was complete. Also, practicing the Heretical God Force was not easy. He needed to constantly absorb divine flames and thunder in the world in order to nourish the constant growth of the Heretical God Force.

Just as it was, the Heretical God Force’s exquisite profoundness in the Laws was extremely exaggerated. It wasn’t even easy for Dragon Fang to see through it.

Dragon Fang said, “You have forced me to open All Existence to Void, and with that, this battle will approach its finale. This is because in this state, I can only maintain myself for half an incense stick of time.”

As the eight Dragon Fangs spoke, they slowly stepped forwards. But as they stepped forwards, another mind-boggling scene occurred.

The bodies of the Dragon Fangs split apart once more, each dividing into two, eight of them dividing into 16!

16 Dragon Fangs had appeared in front of Lin Ming!

“What!?”

The entire audience was completely bewildered. Even those Holy Lords and World Kings were utterly shocked. 16 spatial mirror images meant that Dragon Fang had touched upon the sixth level Concept of the Space Laws!

Although he had only touched the sixth level Concept, he was still many steps away from reaching it. Even so, this accomplishment left one trembling in fear!

“These juniors are too terrifying!”

“An ordinary half-step Holy Lord would have reached this level! In terms of the comprehension of Laws alone, Dragon Fang has reached the standard of a half-step Holy Lord!”

“Old, we are far too old. The geniuses of this era have already surpassed our understanding.”

To touch upon the sixth level Concept at just 36 years of age, that was simply unimaginable. The Space Laws that Dragon Fang practiced were famed for being difficult. This left the heroic young elites present feeling far too inferior. This disparity was too great!

“The match is over. In this state, I can only attack one final time. But, that will be enough.”

The 16 Dragon Fangs looked towards Lin Ming, all of them indifferently speaking as they raised their Dragon Fang Blades.

Chapter 1301 – Hang Chi

“Little witch, you dare!?”

As the two World Kings from the monster race heard the Monster Prince scream in pain, it was only then that they realized what was happening. They simply didn’t recognize the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art from the start.

The two World Kings moved at the same time.

But at this moment, Vast Cosmos’s figure flashed as he arrived between them and Xiao Moxian. With a wave of his sleeves, the two monster race World Kings were swept away by a surge of wind.

At the same time, Vast Cosmos turned around and struck out his palm. A fierce and strong palm wind shut down the energy connection between Xiao Moxian and the Monster Prince.

As the referee of this match he naturally couldn’t sit around idly and allow this sort of matter to continue. Xiao Moxian absorbing the Monster Prince’s energy and blood vitality was simply going too far.

Xiu xiu xiu!

The Dragon Tendon Whip instantly withdrew. With a loud thud, the Monster Prince fell to the ground.

Xiao Moxian fluttered backwards like a black butterfly, lightly landing on the ground. She looked at the pale Monster Prince and a diabolical smile bloomed on her beautiful face, revealing a pair of cute white canines.

As the audience saw this, all of the martial artists felt a chill crawl down their spines. This Xiao Moxian was definitely not easy to deal with. She was sufficiently cruel in her actions. Just because the Monster Prince had harassed her with some words, she used the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art to deal with him.

Moreover, from the very start, there wasn’t the least bit of anger or killing intent coming from Xiao Moxian. All she did was smile as if this were all an enjoyable little game to her.

Even some heroic young elites who took Xiao Moxian as their heart’s love shrank their necks backwards. They began to wonder whether or not their cheap lives were enough for Xiao Moxian to toss about like that.

Without sufficient ability, if anyone dared to provoke this sorceress then they would have no idea how they would die.

“You little witch, you – !” The two monster race World Kings fumed with anger.

“What did I do wrong?” Xiao Moxian coquettishly blinked her large black eyes, her face one of pure innocence.

“What did you do wrong? You know just what good deeds you have committed! This matter will absolutely not end like this!” The two monster race World Kings had already examined the Monster Prince. He had lost 15% of his total true essence in that attack just now.

This was permanent loss. Even his inner world and the Laws he had comprehended had been swallowed up by the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art. If he were to make up for this loss it would take one or two years of hard work and effort.

This loss was far too great for a genius! It would delay their growth!

Xiao Moxian pointed at the pale-faced and nearly unconscious Monster Prince. She began to speak as if she were the one being wronged, “How can you blame me for this? Didn’t you hear him brag about how fierce he was just now? He said he was more powerful than the top master in the Divine Realm and he would become the Monster Emperor in the future. Moreover, he even refers to himself as Lord Monster, an Empyrean of the monster race! I’m just a weak little girl, I was very nervous going on stage!

“I was scared that I wouldn’t be able to beat him so I had to go all-out… my most powerful move is the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art, and I thought that someone like him would be able to easily block it, but who knew that this would be the result…”

Xiao Moxian shrugged, her cute mouth curved upwards. Her night-black eyes seemed to speak the truth, appearing innocent to the extreme. Just looking at her made one feel as if she was really telling the truth, and that because she was far too naïve to the world she hadn’t been able to determine the Monster Prince’s true strength thus her attacks had been too heavy-handed.

The two monster race World Kings almost choked on themselves as they heard Xiao Moxian’s explanation.

As for the heroic young elites present, they were dazed for a moment before suddenly bursting into laughter.

Although they were all aware that this Xiao Moxian was a cruel and ruthless little witch, her cute appearance and coy words combined with her movements made everyone feel she was extremely lovable.

Even Fairy Frost Dream was smiling. This Xiao Moxian was absolutely a little imp who loved to court disaster. But with Empyrean Demondawn standing behind her, no one would dare to move against her no matter what she did.

“You… very well, this old man doesn’t care whether what you say is true or false. Now hurry up and return the true essence you stole from our young master!” One of the two World Kings roared.

“I can’t give it back.” Xiao Moxian shook her head. “I also want to return it but I just don’t have that ability. Once I absorb someone’s energy, it will press into a specific location of my inner world and become my own demonic energy that others cannot use.”

The Heaven Absorbing Demon Art could swallow the cultivation of others in order to strengthen oneself. But, it couldn’t increase one’s power infinitely. Within the inner world of a martial artist that cultivated the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art, their world power was separated from the world power of others. This was to ensure stability in their foundation.

The two World Kings found it hard to give up like this. But at this time, Vast Cosmos’s icy cold true essence sound transmission echoed in their ears, “I advise you both to stop where you are. Xiao Moxian’s grandfather, Empyrean Demondawn, is also watching everything that is happening from deep within Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. That senior has a fickle temperament that can change at a whim and the number of people he has killed is countless. As for whatever war between humans and the monsters, you can simply forget about trying to use something like that to scare him, because he doesn’t care at all. If you both wish to return alive, then you had best know when to give up.”

Vast Cosmos’s words were like a bucket of cold water that poured over the two World Kings, immediately sobering them.

They were used to being arrogant, but today they had really kicked a wall.

This Xiao Moxian’s background was extremely tough!

“That monster is nothing but an idiot, nothing but a toad wanting to eat swan meat. He needs to tuck his tail between his legs and scurry back to where he came from!”

“Hahaha, this is awesome! First Lin Ming beat that idiot to a pulp and now Xiao Moxian has sucked away his strength. This feels too great!”

All of the young heroic elites were ecstatic. They were long sick of seeing this Monster Prince. Since the First Martial Meeting finals started, this was the most enjoyable battle by far.

“Xiao Moxian’s strength is terrifying…”

During this battle, what Lin Ming cared about was not how Xiao Moxian happily ruined the Monster Prince, but how strong she was.

The Heaven Absorbing Demon Art that Xiao Moxian had used had the ability to absorb the Monster Prince’s true essence and blood vitality. That was already terrifying enough, but the true strength of the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art was clearly not limited to this alone. The absorbed strength was not wasted, but stored in a certain part of Xian Moxian’s body. It was likely that this strength could be used. It might even be able to be used to directly attack an opponent – that would probably be the strongest attack of the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art.

Then, the third match of the second round began.

Jun Bluemoon against Hua Xuan.

This was a match without tension. Hua Xuan simply came up on stage and admitted defeat.

The fourth match: White King against Frost Dream.

White King didn’t hesitate either. He also came up and admitted defeat.

The two matches had far too great a disparity. There wasn’t really any reason to right.

The audience members that wanted to see Frost Dream fight were disappointed.

Before this, Frost Dream had never met a worthy opponent thus she hadn’t revealed any of her strength. No one in the audience knew what Frost Dream’s Laws were or what techniques she used.

Even though Jun Bluemoon and Lin Ming also gave off an unfathomable feeling, at least their general abilities were known.

Those that hoped that White King would be able to force Frost Dream to display some of her abilities were disappointed. The battle didn’t even occur.

“This White King’s luck is really poor…”

Mo Eversnow commented from within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea. This should have been the year that Vast Universe Heavenly Palace was able to blossom into wondrous glory. Vast Universe Heavenly Palace wasn’t considered to be amongst the top Empyrean influences, and it was extremely difficult for them to produce a genius like White King. The reason that Empyrean Vast Universe stepped forwards to help conduct the First Martial Meeting was likely because he thought his Heavenly Palace could obtain the limelight.

But now, far too many geniuses had appeared. Every time White King went on stage he would lose. Moreover, it was likely that he would continue losing. Chances were he would even lose to the Monster Prince.

After losing so much on his own home grounds, even though White King had a good mentality and a positive outlook, he would likely feel somewhat embarrassed.

The second round, last match: Hang Chi against Shiku!

This Shiku was a man of much character; he wasn’t willing to admit defeat.

“Hang Chi! Everyone says you are strong, but I believe that I am also strong. Admitting defeat without fighting it out isn’t my style at all!”

Shiku extracted his staff and aimed it towards Hang Chi.

Hang Chi’s 10 fingers and two palms were touching in prayer. He respectfully bowed and slowly said, “Benefactor must be joking. Although Mount Potala’s inheritance is deep, my skeletal age is less than 40 years. The amount I have learned is still limited.”

As Hang Chi said this, many people in the audience also felt this was true. Mount Potala had inheritances gathered over 3.6 billion years, and the number of cultivation methods and rare techniques had long been countless. However, having many cultivation methods didn’t mean that one’s descendants would be strong. Even though there were endless cultivation methods to choose from, one would still only choose a few. Where would they have the time to study more?

Hang Chi said, “Mount Potala possesses six transcendent divine mights and 108 extraordinary skills. I began studying martial arts when I was six years old, but my martial talent is low and I am dull-minded. Until now, I’ve only learnt a tiny bit of a transcendent divine might and of the 108 extraordinary skills, I have only practiced two to a barely adequate level – Backboxing Fist and Leopard Climbing the Wall.”

As Hang Chi said these words, Shiku was a bit dumbfounded. Even the audience was left speechless.

The names of these cultivation methods were… too basic!

No matter how one listened to it, it seemed like the most low level martial arts of the mortal world. It didn’t seem at all similar to the mainstream cultivation methods of the Divine Realm.

For instance, hearing about Xiao Moxian’s Heaven Absorbing Demon Art or Dragon Fang’s Three Lives Pupils, they had extremely domineering and mysterious names, as if they were packed with world-shaking powers.

Compared to them, Backboxing Fist seemed as if it would fall apart at any moment.

“Backboxing Fist? Good! Then let me experience it!”

As Shiku spoke he immediately attacked, instantly opening all seven of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and combining that with Earth Laws, bringing about his peak combat state. Facing Hang Chi, he simply didn’t dare to underestimate him.

Facing the menacing threat of Shiku, Hang Chi unfolded his arms as his entire body emitted crackling sounds.

“Universe Staff!”

Shiku smashed out with his staff as the phantom of a Dragon Turtle appeared behind him.

But facing this staff, Hang Chi only used his bare hands.

His moves were electric, not giving enough time for anyone to react. His hand simply grabbed Shiku’s staff and spun it around. Although this move seemed simple and plain, it actually touched upon one of the staff’s greatest weaknesses.

This staff was pushed away by Hang Chi!

…What?

Shiku was shocked. But before he could respond, Hang Chi had already punched out a fist, smashing into Shiku’s protective earth essence barrier.

Ka ka ka!

Shiku’s earth essence barrier began to crack apart after a single fist from Hang Chi!

Shiku began to panic and fear at the same time. The way his battle unfolded with Hang Chi had completely surpassed his imagination!

Shiku swept out his staff towards Hang Chi’s waist, but Hang Chi suddenly floated away like a piece of cotton, as if he were blown away by the wind around Shiku’s staff. He moved like ghosts and gods as he appeared right behind Shiku, his fist pounding out once more.

Peng!

Shiku’s protective earth essence barrier completely shattered! Then, one of Hang Chi’s fingers gently poked a spot on Shiku’s back.

This single poke caused Shiku’s entire body to go numb. Even the staff in his hands fell to the ground!

“You let me win.”

Hang Chi’s figure flashed and he returned to the point where he stood at the start, as if he had never moved to begin with.

Chapter 1302 – Lin Ming VS Xiao Moxian

“Hang Chi, victory!”

Vast Cosmos loudly announced. Even so, the audience still hadn’t recovered from their shock.

Hang Chi hadn’t used any Laws from the start to the end. He hadn’t even used any true essence. It was hard to imagine how he had defeated Shiku.

“This Hang Chi, did he rely on just his movements to win?”

Lin Ming felt this was unbelievable. Hang Chi’s actions attacked the weakest point of Shiku’s martial skill. He had used a simple attack to overcome him, not wasting a single ounce of strength or even using his Laws. It was simply incredible.

And Hang Chi had done all of this easily. The reason he had been able to easily expose his opponent’s flaws and counter was all because of his movement skill – Leopard Climbing the Wall.

In the legends, the agile leopards could fall down from an extremely high pagoda and not die. Hang Chi’s movement technique was known as Leopard Climbing the Wall. Although this sounded very low-class, the truth was that it was simple and straightforward. It was a movement technique that utilized the simplest and most direct movements to the greatest effect. An unrivalled movement technique in truth did not need some magnificent name to prove itself. This Leopard Climbing the Wall was even superior to Lin Ming’s Golden Roc Shattering the Void.

“I wonder which senior from Mount Potala created this set of martial arts and gave it such a casual name…” Lin Ming wondered as he sighed with emotion.

At this time, Mo Eversnow suddenly responded, “The disciples of Mount Potala consider themselves austere ascetics. The seniors of Mount Potala spend their entire lives diligently praying and cultivating, studying Buddhist texts and cultivation methods. Each and every one of them is considered a martial arts grandmaster, and after creating a set of martial arts, they simply do not care too much about the name, only coming up with something on their whims. This is how the martial artists of Mount Potala pursuit their road of martial arts. Even if the martial arts they create are brought to fame by their descendants, they wouldn’t care about this at all. Most of them don’t even leave behind their names on the cultivation method jade slips.”

“I see… no wonder why Mount Potala has managed to continue on for such a long time. They are a low key sect and their background is so deep. Even the martial artists in their sects spend all their efforts cultivating without caring for external conflicts. Who would dare to provoke such an influence?”

Lin Ming suddenly realized. A vicious and crazy sect who wildly provoked others could arouse fear, but after a long time passed they could also fade away. In this world, there would always be another influence that was even more ruthless. But, a low profile sect like Mount Potala never provoked others and was also strong themselves; this type of sect was the most likely to last.

“Hang Chi is also a terrifying opponent, and he didn’t even use Laws in his moves just now. I wonder what level his Laws have reached?”

Lin Ming thought to himself. If he were to fight Hang Chi, he simply couldn’t say what the results would be.

At this time, the second round of the finals came to an end.

Vast Cosmos stepped onto the arena stage, loudly proclaiming, “The second round has come to an end, and now we shall give special notice to the first match of the third round. Vast Universe Heavenly Palace has specifically opened up a separate gambling bet for this match. Everyone may place bets, and these bets will not affect the previous bets placed.”

As Vast Cosmos spoke, everyone in the audience was suddenly excited. If this was a match worth opening up a separate bet for then it was naturally going to be a battle of heavyweights.

“The match for the separate bet is… Lin Ming against Xiao Moxian!”

As Vast Cosmos said this, the entire audience was stirred up in a frenzy!

This match was truly worth looking forwards to!

Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming.

One was the number one genius girl of the Divine Realm. Her cultivation methods were cruel and callous, and she was a sorceress capable of eating someone up without leaving behind any bones.

As for the other, he had a mysterious history. Since the First Martial Meeting began, he had yet to be defeated. No matter how strong his opponents were, he rose to the challenge to strike them down. Especially in the last battle. After defeating Dragon Fang and his Three Lives Pupils, his fame had risen to unprecedented heights.

The two of them exuded an unfathomable and invincible aura. But if one invincible person were to fight another invincible person, there would inevitably be someone that died.

As Lin Ming heard Vast Cosmos’s words, he turned to glance at Xiao Moxian. He just happened to meet Xiao Moxian’s own gaze. She playfully smiled at him.

“I didn’t think I would need to fight Xiao Moxian so soon. I thought my next match would be Jun Bluemoon.”

In the third round, he would have to fight one of the top three seeded players!

This battle was basically a battle for the top three!

Vast Cosmos said, “The odds for this match have been set. Xiao Moxian’s victory has a 1 to 1.4 compensation rate! Lin Ming’s victory has a 1 to 2.9 compensation rate!”

Gambling on the outcome of an unknown battle was extremely electrifying. Moreover, the compensation rates that Vast Universe Heavenly Palace put out were very fair. If one were to bet 100 million violet sun stones on Xiao Moxian and another 50 million on Lin Ming then no matter who won the losses wouldn’t be too great.

This naturally motivated people to bet even more.

“From the compensation rates, it seems that Vast Universe Heavenly Palace favors Xiao Moxian’s victory more! However, even if Lin Ming loses he still might be able to rank in the top four.”

“It seems more likely that Xiao Moxian will win, but Lin Ming cannot be underestimated either. No matter who he fought he still won. He might be able to score an upset against Xiao Moxian.”

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian were both undefeated. Of course, if one had to choose sides, Xiao Moxian seemed the superior choice. She was the granddaughter of Empyrean Demondawn and her mother was a true God Beast. The descendant of a person and a God Beast was an existence that might not be seen even in 100 million years. It could be called a miracle of life!

“Hehe… Lin Ming!” Xiao Moxian chuckled at Lin Ming, taking the initiative to greet him, “I hope you’ll show me some mercy on stage!”

Xiao Moxian playfully smiled. Lin Ming also laughed, “I would also like to show you mercy, but I’m afraid I don’t have the qualifications to do so.”

“Haha, I know you still have some cards you haven’t used. Why don’t you give me a little clue?”

Hearing Xiao Moxian’s words, Lin Ming was left a tad speechless. She actually directly asked someone else what cards they still had hidden. “I have almost nothing left. Dragon Fang was very strong. It was impossible for me to hold back against him.”

“How stingy. I knew that you weren’t going to say anything.” Xiao Moxian rolled her eyes before swiveling around.

After having this conversation, Lin Ming didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry.

“Lin Ming, how confident are you in this battle?” Mo Eversnow asked from within his spiritual sea.

“I have no idea. There is no way I can estimate the limit of Xiao Moxian’s strength. She is at the middle Divine Sea realm and I am at the middle Divine Sea realm. If I lose to her then I have truly lost, there is no excuse or reason to give!”

Growing up until now, this was the first time that Lin Ming hadn’t had full confidence in being able to defeat someone that was at his cultivation level. Moreover, Xiao Moxian was even younger than Lin Ming by a great deal, so her talent could be seen from this alone.

“Don’t look down on yourself, Xiao Moxian has had a much better environment to grow up in. She was born in one of the greatest influences within the Divine Realm and her talent is truly too formidable. As for you, you wasted an immense time with your life starting at the Sky Fortune Kingdom. For instance, at 15 years of age, most Empyrean descendants would have been exploring the Divine Realm. They would have already reached the Xiantian realm, perceived the Laws, and even trained in transcendent divine mights. As for you, you had to diligently train in the Seven Profound Martial House as a student, and your growth afterwards was filled with countless trials and tribulations. You obtained the Nirvana Dragon Root at the Demon God Imperial Palace by risking your life to struggle with Xuan Wuji and the others who were countless times stronger than you at the time. But even so, to these Empyrean descendants, a medicine of the level of a Nirvana Dragon Root is nothing but a joke. You spent a great deal of wealth to purchase the Boundless World Pill, but to Xiao Moxian and the others, that is merely a common pill.”

Mo Eversnow’s words defined how difficult it was for a common martial artist or a martial artist from the lower realms. For any one of them to grow to the degree at which they could battle an Empyrean descendant was already a miracle! This sort of probability was so negligibly low that it could basically be ignored. Only by adding the incalculable number of lives in the Divine Realm and lower realms combined together could such a singularity appear.

“Miss Mo, the tribulations I experienced in the lower realms, they may have been difficult and I may have wasted a great deal of time there, but they are still a precious wealth of mine. If I didn’t begin in the lower realms then I would never have obtained the Magic Cube, I wouldn’t have obtained the inheritance of Empyrean Primordius, nor would I have been able to temper my will. A person’s destiny, their karma, all of their causes and effects cannot be forced or faked. If I didn’t originate from the lower realms and was born into an Empyrean influence of the Divine Realm, then my current achievements would have been far from what they are now. I would only be an Empyrean descendant, someone similar to Hua Xuan, and even that might have been exceptional.”

Lin Ming’s words were his philosophy of living. Mo Eversnow also nodded, “You’re right. As long as you can maintain your path then you can definitely create an even greater miracle. Especially now that you have comprehended the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. In the future, there is a slim hope that just maybe you will be able to reach the boundary of Empyrean Divine Seal!”

“Empyrean Divine Seal…” Lin Ming took a deep breath. He found it hard to imagine just what the world was like 3.6 billion years ago, but he knew that Empyrean Divine Seal was the most terrifying Empyrean that he knew of, even more horrifying than Empyrean Divine Dream or Empyrean Primordius!

He might have even surpassed the boundary of an Empyrean altogether.

Of course, these matters were still too distant for Lin Ming; there was no need to think of them. He closed his eyes and began to meditate, preparing himself for the upcoming match.

The noise of the audience and their discussions could not affect him at all.

One hour later, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open. The time for his decisive battle had arrived!

Many high level figures of the Divine Realm were paying attention to this match. Even Empyrean Divine Dream, Empyrean Vast Universe, and Empyrean Demondawn were the same.

The audience was even more zealous. Before this, a massive number of people in the audience joined in on the gambling bet between Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian. With several hundred million people present, even if only 10% of them participated and each person only bet 10 billion or so, that was still hundreds of thousands of trillions of wealth. That was hundreds of thousands of nine sun jades. And to the disciples of these great sects, 10 billion was nothing at all.

This massive gambling bet was something that only an Empyrean level influence was able to handle. There was no smaller influence that would dare to host this sort of bet, because if they lost, then they would really be finished.

Lin Ming stepped onto the arena stage, grasping the Phoenix Blood Spear. Xiao Moxian stood a thousand feet across from him.

Xiao Moxian playfully smiled as before. No one knew what cards she had hidden or what the limit of her strength was. She seemed completely confident in her abilities.

“Match, begin!”